Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
You're showing some interest in the female body.
That's very good, Rito-san.
Momo! You could've knocked before you came in!
It doesn't necessarily have to be your body.
I'd be happy to show you mine.
Every last inch of it.
It may be embarrassing, but I'm willing to put up with it for you.
N-No, th-that's not...
You're so cute!
Even as a girl, you're still my type.
B-By the way, where's Mea?
She already left.
She asked me to tell you bye for her.
What do you think?
What did she come all the way here for?
She might've... just... wanted to see the house...
I'm still not convinced.
Why is she so friendly with you?
What?
It'd make more sense if she saw you as an enemy. You are Yami-san's target, after all.
Momo!
I don't get a chance like this very often.
Let me teach you about the secrets of a woman's body.
Momo!
Stop...
As the lord of a harem, it might come in handy.
Hey! Wai— Momo!
Please stay still.
Stop!
Momo!
So this is the real you, Momo-chan.
My "pretend to go home" plan was a huge success!
You both found out who I really am, right?
Yami-oneechan told you, didn't she?
If that's the case, can you let me in on your secret too, Momo-chan?
My secret?
What are you talking about?
The real side of you that you can't show at school.
Psycho Dive!
If I merge a part of my body with
someone else, I can get into their mind.
Before Nana-chan introduced you to me,
I found you napping on the school's roof and paid you a visit inside your dream.
Your dream was based on a recent experience that took place inside a bathroom.
When I looked for the memory
associated with it, I ended up seeing it all.
Momo-chan, in school you're so cute and proper. All the boys love you.
But in Senpai's dream, you clung to him and did that!
In my dream?
Do you remember now?
In your dream, you touched me like this!
Stop!
So Rito-san even does those kind of things in his dreams. Why am I not surprised?
Well? What's your point?
"Don't get in my way or I'll tell everyone?"
Nope! Actually, I've come to like you two a lot since then.
I just want us to get along!
I'll be staying in town for a while.
Spending my time alone here would be boring.
And Yami-oneechan told me it's
important to interact with people.
Is that really what you think?
Or is that just what your master told you?
I don't know!
But I can help with your harem plan too.
I'm not in any position to help you get Yami-oneechan though.
How is it, Senpai?
How do you like this?
I'm not sure about this...
But it doesn't sound like a bad idea.
If I want to lure her master into the light,
it'd probably be a good idea
to keep in touch with Mea-san.
Not to mention that if she knows about my harem plan,
it'd be too dangerous to just leave her be.
I should go along with this.
I understand.
Let's get along.
We should make our time
at school as fun as possible.
Wonderful!
By the way, Mea-san...
Yeah, Momo-chan?
When you're licking it,
it's more effective to mix up the pacing like this.
You know your stuff, Momo-chan!
So I lick it like this?
Yeah, that's it!
But if you do it like this...
I see!
Do you like it, Senpai?
Stop it already!
Rito, Lala-san said it's about time for your body to return to norm—
Momo-san? Mea-san?
Uh, we were just helping Rito-san change clothes.
Huh? Weren't we just licking him?
Why would you even say that?
I don't even care! Just get out!
Rito, put on some clothes!
Okay!
I wonder what all the fuss is about.
Look, it's Run-chan!
Are you here to hang out?
Yay! Come in, come in!
Um...
Oh? Run-san?
You're Momo-chan, right?
Ah, she's the one from Memorze?
Yeah! Run-chan is the girl and Ren-chan is the boy. They change every now and then.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Wait, Run-san!
What happened?
Um...
There's something I need to talk to Rito-kun about.
I'd be delighted to set something up for you!
Really?
I'll be sure to tell Rito-san.
Thank you so much!
You're so smart!
I can hardly believe you're really Lala-chan's sister!
Right?
Thanks so much!
How can I ever repay you?
H-Hey, didn't I warn you about clinging on to me?
It's fine. Don't worry.
I managed to get Rito-san on a date with Run-san!
This must be what they mean when they say "pennies from heaven".
This is a big step forward for my harem plan.
But...
Can you three remind me why you're here too?
I invited them!
Please don't mind me.
I need to make sure Rito doesn't do anything weird to Run.
Wh-What?
I knew it. You like him too, don't you, Nana?
Don't be stupid! I couldn't care les—
I care! I'm so curious!
Are Senpai and Run-san going to kiss?
Run-san can be quite pushy. They might
end up doing something even more amazing.
Something even more amazing? Like what?
Rito-kun... Can we go to my place?
Are you sure?
No one's home. We can do whatever we want.
First, we should take a bath together.
It could even come to that!
What are you two imagining?!
What did you want to talk to me about?
Uh... Um...
Rito-kun, what if, hypothetically speaking,
someone told you that you mustn't fall in love.
What would you do?
That's what my manager told me backstage the other day.
He said that I'm already a successful idol,
so I shouldn't even think about getting a boyfriend.
I can't really explain it, but I felt so depressed after he said that.
I didn't know idols had to put up with stuff like that.
Yeah...
I can't say that I know how you feel,
but I don't think you should let it bother you.
It'd be such a waste if you ruined
your health by worrying too much.
You're worried about me?
You're so kind, Rito-kun.
No, I'm just...
I'm getting a good vibe from those two.
What's he being so spoony about? Stupid Rito...
Having tea every once in a while at shops meant for commoners is an important social experience, Aya.
You're so wise, Saki-sama!
Oh my, isn't that Yuuki Rito and Run?
It's been so long, Saki-senpai!
I heard you're doing well as an idol.
I wish you the best of luck!
I gave up my ambition of becoming
an entertainment queen just for your sake!
Yeah, thanks...
W-Well, Run and I will be on our way now.
Y-Yeah.
Saki-sama!
Kujou-senpai...
Damn you, Yuuki Rito!
I'm so sorry!
We'll leave the money here!
Hold it!
That's...
Yuuki-kun and Run-san?
What are they doing?
I'm sorry, Run! I'll pay you back for my part.
Don't worry about that.
Are you okay?
I-I'm fine.
You look pretty worn out.
I just haven't run in such a long time.
Look, Rito-kun! The sunset's so beautiful!
The sunset?
Yeah. Watching the sunset from Earth always feels so wonderful.
You're exaggerating.
I'm sure your planet has pretty sunsets too.
It doesn't.
Huh?
Memorze has two suns, so there's no night.
Eighty percent of the planet is a huge, dry desert.
It's a pretty severe environment if you ask me.
It's said that as a result of evolution,
we Memorzians are born with both genders in one body to survive in that environment.
I had no idea.
Normally, we swap genders every month or so,
but Ren and I have changed from living on Earth for so long.
Wow.
Having your gender change so suddenly must be a pain.
Not once you get used to it.
Ren and I switch based on our own rules.
My job's been our top priority recently.
Our personalities go to sleep when we're not in control,
so that we'll interfere with each other's private lives as little as possible.
Our friend Kyouko and a few people from work know about me and Ren, and they're helping us.
But it's still a lot of work.
For example, I'm not supposed to sneeze during my shows.
Yeah, it'd turn into a huge scandal if you transformed there.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
I just realized that I hardly knew a thing about you.
Do you want to?
Do you want to know more?
So long as it's you, I'm fine with it.
Run-san's on the move!
What's gonna happen now, Momo-chan?
Rito-kun, come this way!
You're the only one I'll show it to, Rito-kun.
You can touch it if you want.
Don't be so rough!
Maybe something like that!
You two...
Lewd, aren't they?
Don't look, Yuuki Rito!
Let me make it clear that I'm not wearing this willingly!
I know! I know!
Sorry, that was an accident.
Wow! She really changes into a boy when she sneezes!
So much for the great mood...
Momo-chan, they're leaving!
I changed to Ren in front of you again.
I manage to hold back when I'm working,
but I guess I let my guard down when I'm around you.
I shouldn't expect you to treat me as a normal girl, should I?
Come on, don't say that! I'm not—
Run...
You know...
I considered Lala-chan my rival in love.
But to be honest, I already knew deep down
that as long as I'm sharing my body with Ren,
I can never compete equally with Lala-chan.
Working in the entertainment business is fun and rewarding,
so I thought I'd just immerse myself in that.
I locked away my feelings for you in my heart.
But in the end... I just... I just can't do it!
I want you to look at me!
I love you just as much as Lala-chan does!
Run!
Sorry...
I guess I'm really not feeling well.
I think it's because I've been so busy with work lately.
Just rest over there for a while.
Hold on to my shoulder!
Where could they have gone?
Should I call a pet who can trace their scent?
Yeah, that's—
Girls, hide!
I feel so hot...
Run, you're sweating like crazy.
Help me... take my shirt off...
Okay!
Wh-What are they doing?!
Could Rito-san have fallen for her idol aura...
Rito-kun, what if someone sees us?
...and awakened his manly side?
You lecher!
That's against school regulations!
Kotegawa-san?
What are you doing here?
Wh-What about you girls?
Was that Kotegawa and Nana just now?
Is Momo there too?
Uh...
Perfect timing!
Run-san?
Wh-What happened?
She suddenly started feeling sick.
Rito-kun!
Run, are you okay?
Run...
What's going on, Momo?!
I don't know! I've never seen anything like this!
We should take her to Dr. Mikado!
Okay!
Rito-kun...
Run, hang in there!
No...
This is probably...
R-Run-san? Why are you naked?!
Huh?
Ren-san?
But how? Run's over there...
What's going on?!
According to this Encyclopedia of Galactic Species,
Memorzians fully mature by developing their unique, tertiary sexual characteristics
in addition to their primary and secondary ones.
This is known as "metamorphose", when they split into an independent male and female individual.
Congratulations, Run Elsie Jewelria.
We should celebrate tonight.
Hurray! Rito-kun, I've finally become an adult!
Rito-kun!
Finally! I'm finally free!
Hey, Run-san! You need to put on some clothes!
I didn't know they split when they grow up.
Isn't this a wonderful development for you, Momo-chan?
Yeah, I guess.
That's one less obstacle keeping Run-san from joining the harem.
It's like those pennies came with a few pounds.
Rito-kun! I'm very determined!
I'll become the greatest idol ever and melt your heart!
Oh man... This isn't exactly what I'd call an improvement.
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
A happy invention.