See you!
Bye!
Done!
Here you go, Nana.
Thanks, Sister!
It works now!
What're you girls up to?
Nana's phone was acting up, so she asked Onee-sama to take a look at it.
Sorry about that. You had to spend your whole break helping me.
It's okay. I don't mind.
Nana, you're too rough with your gadgets.
You always broke your toys when you were smaller, too.
Is there something wrong with that?!
I just wish you'd grow up at least a little...
Don't say that while looking at my chest!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't give me that! I know you were making fun of me!
Nana!
I made just the thing for you!
Look!
It's Booby Bang-kun!
Booby?
It's still in the experimental stages, but give it a try!
What the—
Sister, what just...
My boobs are...
...a big success!
You're awesome, Sister!
Well, you were just so conscious about your boobs.
O-Onee-sama...
My boobs are... gone!
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Rito-san.
Please, do what you want.
You'll catch a cold if you're dressed so lightly, Momo!
Are you okay, Momo?
Don't look at me like that, Rito-san!
Like what?!
Looks like I had it in me to grow big boobs after all!
Don't let it get to you, flatty!
And don't be so mad.
There's no need to be such a kid.
My boobs vanished!
Oh? The effects wore off already?
I guess I have to do some more research.
B-But...
I'm sorry, Nana.
I understand your feelings a little better now.
Dammit!
Don't make me use your experimental gadgets, Sister!
Sorry!
Jeez...
Wow!
Lala-san makes some interesting gadgets, doesn't she?
My goodness. I'm sorry you had to witness something like that.
No, it didn't really bother me.
I made some tea for you!
It's good!
Yeah.
Mikado-sensei taught me how to make it.
Anyway, Lala must really love inventing things.
Was she like this when she was younger?
Yes, she was. For as long as I can remember, at least.
Deviluke Royal Palace, 7 years ago
It was your fault, Nana!
No, you should say you're sorry, Momo!
I'm older than you!
That doesn't matter! We're twins!
Nana-sama, Momo-sama, could you please stop figh—
Shut up, Zastin!
I'm sorry!
Nana, Momo!
My machines are running wild! Stop them!
Nana, get the ones over there.
Okay!
You need to be more careful, Lala-sama.
Sorry!
Thanks! You two really helped me out.
Our days back then were full of stuff like that.
It's pretty much the same now, isn't it?
She's the same child, but in a bigger body.
Oh, Momo-chan! Senpai!
There you are!
Hey, do you know where Nana-chan is?
She went to the school store.
I see! Thanks!
Oh yeah...
You're Dr. Mikado, right?
Wonderful.
That was Kurosaki Mea,
Yami-chan's "little sister", right?
Yes.
Sensei, did you find out anything about her?
Well, as an underground doctor,
I have my own network of contacts.
However, Yami-chan's former organization was destroyed years ago,
so I can't really look anything up.
If only we could find Tearju...
It's nothing. Don't mind me.
I'll keep looking around.
Please look after Yami-chan for me.
Whoa, this is where you live, Mea?!
Sorry for disturbing on a holiday.
Nana wouldn't stop insisting.
You said you wanted to see it too!
It's fine! I don't have anything to do on holidays anyway.
My place is empty, though.
Ta-dah! Welcome to my home!
You weren't kidding when you said it was empty.
Yeah, I told you.
Do you live here by yourself?
Yup!
A little gift for having us over, Kusosaki Mea.
Thank you!
Don't you find living alone to be inconvenient?
Where do you get your food?
There's a convenience store nearby and I can get candy whenever I want, too.
I've lived alone for a long time, so I'm used to it.
I'll get you some soda.
I only have paper cups, though.
Let me help!
Mea said she has an older sister,
but they aren't living together.
Isn't she lonely?
Time to eat!
I see.
So you went to Mea-san's place...
Yes. I was kind of hoping we would discover something about her master.
If she was that easy to catch,
she would've showed herself already.
Um, you all look like you get along very well with Mea-san.
Wouldn't she tell you if you just asked?
Not a chance.
Master's existence means everything to Kurosaki Mea.
Really? I thought she was getting along with us pretty well.
No. That's not something that can be changed so quickly.
To be honest, I have yet to completely understand who she is.
Even if we're getting along well on the surface,
I feel like she still has a huge wall between us and her heart.
I think we can only understand each other when that wall comes down.
But whenever I try to get closer to her, I feel anxious...
As though I was staring into some dark abyss...
Is that your woman's intuition speaking?
I don't know.
I've never felt this way before.
Mea and I are both weapons made for the sole purpose of fighting.
The heart of weapons and people might be essentially different.
Yami-san, that's not what I meant!
Yami.
Mikan is my one and only, dear little sister.
Our parents are always busy, so we've supported each other. It's always been just the two of us.
I consider her to be more than just my little sister.
You might be feeling the same way when you worry about Mea.
I mean, she's your little sister and you finally found her.
If you think that's something special,
then your heart is no different from ours.
You're not just a weapon.
Rito-san, that was such a wonderful thing to say!
It must be because he's such a nice person that Haruna-san and Lala-san...
I hate perverts!
I didn't even—
A dog! A dog!
Oh my.
Oshizu-chan, calm down!
Oh!
I'm killing him!
It wasn't his fault, Yami-san!
Wait! Hey!
He's a hopelessly lewd animal!
Oh my.
I'll go home before you today.
Did something happen?
I wanna figure out why my latest invention failed.
Could you pick up Celine-chan for me?
Sure thing.
No matter how many times she fails, she just tries even harder the next.
Yuuki!
Ren?
This is a sample of the new CD that Run's releasing soon.
She's working today, so she asked me to give it to you.
Oh...
Thanks!
Yuuki...
I've been meaning to ask you something.
What do you think of Lala-chan?
She's a lot more kind and pure than you think.
She's like an angel, who heals everyone around her.
Aren't you just letting yourself be spoiled by her kindness?
I...
Whatever.
What I'm saying is, don't ever make a girl cry. That includes Run.
He may have a point...
I intended to sort things out when I told Lala that I love Haruna-chan,
and in spite of that, I feel relieved that she's still around.
That goes for Run too.
But still,
I can't...
Let me help you assemble your very own harem!
It's the perfect solution to a lot of our problems!
I'm so stupid! I shouldn't even be imagining things like that!
I can't believe I'm seriously considering Momo's offer!
Lovers
Watch out!
Reinforce morals!
Rito!
Dinner's almost ready.
Can you you go get Lala-san and the other girls from upstairs?
All right.
However...
Watch out for Momo-san.
That's odd...
Lala! Mikan said dinner's almost ready.
Okay, I'll be down in a minute.
Your room's a mess as usual.
This is so weird.
Why didn't it work?
Lala...
Why did you start inventing?
Huh?
Well, it just dawned on me that we've never really talked about it before.
Oh, you're right!
But it's nothing special.
Life in the royal palace was so boring. I just wanted to liven things up a bit.
Once the war was over and peace followed, all there was for me to do was study.
Run-chan was the only one who'd come around every once in a while to hang out.
And I was making a mess of the Deviluke battleships since I was little,
so I have experience working with machinery!
That's more than what I'd call a childish prank.
I obviously rebuilt it afterward!
You still overdid it!
Is that Rito-san's voice coming from Onee-sama's room?
Don't say that!
Could it be?!
Rito!
L-Lala?!
I love you!
Rito!
Probably not.
She's just a kid on the inside.
But what are they talking about, then?
What are you doing?
Shh! Shh!
What? Momo said that?
Yeah, I remember!
They fought all the time back then too.
And your inventions would fail and only make Zastin angry.
I can't tell who's the eldest sister among you three.
You're wrong about that!
That robot's rampage wasn't Lala-sama's fault.
She was showing her love for the two of them!
Love?
Back then...
I'm older than you!
Lala-sama, your sisters!
That doesn't matter! We're twins!
Jeez, they're at it again.
Guess I'll have to step in.
Okay, I'll use these!
So she did it on purpose to help them make up?
Exactly.
They are my dear little sisters.
I can't just leave them be when they're fighting.
Zastin would just get mad at me instead.
I see!
She must have had the same thing in mind when she let out her new invention earlier today.
She's a lot more kind and pure than you think.
Huh?
Why is my heart racing all of a sudden?
You okay?
Your face is red.
You're too close!
Rito! Are you okay?!
Lala!
That's the Bindy-Ropey-kun!
It automatically binds anything and makes packing painless!
Don't just explain it like it has nothing to do with you!
Rito! Don't look!
Lala! I-I really can't bear to look!
Stupid rope!
Rito, untie it!
It's your invention!
Why do your inventions always do stuff like this?!
I never realized...
she was watching over us like that all this time.
I thought she was childish,
but out of the three of us, I'm the one who was being a child.
Now that I think about it, didn't we we run away and come to Earth
partly because we were lonely after she left?
I guess.
Momo.
I'm glad I'm her little sister.
Me too.
Why aren't they coming?!
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
Bonds of happiness.