Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Is jam okay?
Here you go.
Rito!
Rito, are you up?
Get out of bed already or you'll be late!
Jeez...
Rito-san, Mikan-san is calling you.
I'll do something naughty if you don't get up.
Good morning.
Oh, my.
Momo! When did you sneak into my bed?!
Guess!
Oh, so you are awake.
Mikan asked me to wake you up.
Hey, Nana.
What the hell are you doing with Momo this early in the morning?!
She came in here on her own!
Yeah, right!
Get back here, you beast!
Nothing beats a morning bath.
Hey, Rito! Good morning!
Lala! How many times do I have to tell you not to walk around the house naked?!
But...
Now you're messing around with Lala?!
Oh, boy...
What's the matter, Rito?
You don't look so good.
Of course I don't.
This is my everyday life.
I can't seem to stay out of trouble ever since I met Princess Lala of Planet Deviluke,
which governs the galaxy.
And things have only gotten worse ever since her twin sisters,
Nana and Momo, moved in with us.
Lately, I've had to be extra careful around Momo,
the third princess of Deviluke.
Unlike the ditzy and innocent Lala and Nana,
Momo can be pretty devious and sinister at times.
Well, she might just be playing around, but to someone like me,
What's up, Rito? Good morning, Lala-chan.
who isn't used to being around girls,
Momo's behavior is a little overwhelming.
Good morning.
She isn't the least of my worries, either.
Golden Darkness!
Hey, Yami-chan! Good morning!
Good morning, Princess.
What are you doing here?
I'm returning a book to the library.
She's terrifying.
I've run into all kinds of aliens ever since I met Lala,
but I still get nervous whenever I see that one.
The legendary assassin, Golden Darkness.
I bet she still wants to kill me.
Good morning, Lala-san.
Oh! Good morning, Haruna!
Haruna-chan!
Good morning, Yuuki-kun.
Good morning.
Ah, her smile is so comforting!
A-Are you okay?
Good morning, Lalacchi.
Did they get bigger?
Good morning.
Risa, cut it out!
Hey there, Yuuki!
So, what did they all say?
What are you talking...
Oh!
N-No! That was a misunderstanding!
A misunderstanding?!
You jerk! And here I thought—
I didn't even say it to you!
Oh, really?
What are you guys talking about?
Well...
Rito! Rito!
Here's your chance!
Tell her how you feel!
Good morning!
Morning!
Hey!
Do you even know what you just said?!
Relax!
I know it'll work out just fine!
If all goes well, Haruna and I will both marry you and we'll all get to live together!
Didn't you tell me the other day that you like me?
Like I said, that was just—
Am I wrong?
Well...
You like me, don't you?
Well, you could say that.
I knew it! Yay!
Congratulations, Lala-sama!
We need to prepare for the wedding—
But the law in Japan is that marriage can only be between two people!
The law?
What are you two doing over there?
As a member of the discipline committee, I cannot overlook indecent behaviors within the school!
Yui!
We were just chatting!
I have my doubts.
This is pretty heavy.
You were taking these to the classroom, right?
I'll do it for you.
Th... Th... Tha... Thanks...
Aren't you sweet?
Stop that!
Celine-chan?
Pervert!
Oh, wow.
Why does he always dive right for the panties?
An amazing fall, as usual.
Nana! Momo!
Why are you wearing the school's uniform?
Because we're transfer students! Today's our first day.
We wanted to surprise you, so we did it in secret.
What? Really?
This is awesome! I had no idea!
Keeping Celine and Momo company at home while you were gone was so boring.
You've transferred? So you're freshmen now?
I had no clue you two were old enough.
The principal was willing to let something that small slide, so transferring here was a cinch.
Yami-chan!
I love having you here at this schoo—
So there you have it, Kotegawa!
Nana! Mind your manners!
You need to be polite to your upperclassmen.
And try to get along with everyone.
Right, Rito-senpai?
Was Momo actually...
How am I going to deal with this?
I was able to tell Lala how I really feel, but...
Even if I tell Haruna how I feel,
it's going to look like she's my second choice unless I settle things with Lala first.
Lala's advice about just taking the both of them was nice, but it all sounds too good to be true.
I wonder about that.
I don't think it's too far-fetched.
Momo?! What are you doing in here?
We need to talk.
Don't worry. I've already washed my body.
Hey, Rito-san.
I guess you're not aware,
but there are actually a lot of girls who have a crush on you.
What?!
You can make a lot of girls happy
depending on how you handle things.
Wouldn't that be wonderful?
You're the best candidate for the next King of Deviluke, after all.
I don't see a problem with a king who has concubines.
I'm...
getting out!
You don't even need to think about it!
Let me help you assemble your very own harem!
That way, everyone can be honest with their feelings!
"Assemble a harem." That's what she suggested.
What if she was actually being serious back then?
No, there's no way...
Later! Make sure you behave yourself, Celine!
All right! Let's go!
Okay.
I'm kinda nervous about going to a school on Earth.
I know how you feel.
Well, Rito-san, let's work hard.
I'm Nana Aster Deviluke!
I'm Momo Belia Deviluke!
Nice to meet you!
Momo-san, can we talk?
Talk to me too!
Are you seeing anyone right now?
How is she so popular?
Oh, please! You guys are too much!
What a little goody two-shoes.
Whatever. Guess I'll check out Lala's class or something.
What are you doing?
I'm watching those two.
Oh, the birds.
They're flying together, so I was just wondering if they're friends.
They're saying, "Let's fly south today!"
You can understand what they're saying?
Yeah. I was born with the ability to read the minds of animals.
It's kinda like telepathy, I guess.
I was able to befriend all kinds of animals from across the galaxy with my ability.
I-I'm telling the truth!
That's wonderful!
Huh?
You must be really gifted to be able to talk to animals!
I'm surprised I have a classmate who can do that!
Wait. You are my classmate, right?
Don't you remember? I greeted you all this morning.
It's my first day.
Oh.
She seems pretty laid-back.
What's your name?
I'm Mea.
Kurosaki Mea.
What's yours?
Nana.
Nana Astar Deviluke!
Nice to meet you!
Nana-chan...
Nice to meet you too!
I'm exhausted.
Those boys from homeroom don't know how to show any restraint.
They obviously had ulterior motives.
They could learn a thing or two from Rito-san about how to treat a girl.
Sorry I took so long!
Come on. Let's get something to eat.
Sure.
We'll create a harem and make Rito-san manly.
Rito-san likes Onee-sama, but he also likes Haruna-san.
It didn't go so well, but he tried to confess his love to Haruna-san at the pool.
He also told Onee-sama how he felt about her that day.
I figure that he wanted to do things properly.
Earthlings may consider that "common sense,"
but there are many kings on many different planets
who have concubines and love many different women at the same time.
Rito-san will be the next king of Deviluke, so he's capable of loving all of them.
He might even love me too.
I'm going to have to make him change his Earthly "common sense."
I'm hoping for something that will last forever. Something that will make everyone happy.
Rito-san, you don't know it,
but you have so much potential.
I know, because when you're half-asleep, you...
A marshmallow...
It's a marshmallow...
First things first!
I need to take care of the obstacles.
Yami-san!
How can I help you,
Princess Momo?
After transferring here, I thought it was about time I made friends with my fellow aliens.
You want to be friends...
with me?
Yes!
I'm not looking for friends.
I have Mikan, and she's all I need.
Well, I knew Golden Darkness wouldn't be easy to deal with.
She's a legendary assassin with the "Trans" ability, which transforms her entire body into a weapon.
Her real name and identity are unknown.
Ever since she came to Earth, she's been targeting Rito-san.
But I have dirt on her.
Her favorite food is taiyaki.
The person who introduced her to that was...
I know! You need a key to beat that level!
What's the matter?
Nothing. Let's go.
It's good.
If you were that hungry, you should've told me earlier.
No, I wasn't really hungry.
Yami-san?
Why don't you transfer here too?
Transfer?
I have no reason to.
Don't say that!
You'd get to wear the school uniform and participate in all kinds of school events!
Uniform... Events...
Yeah! The school festival, the swimming pool, and all sorts of other stuff!
You might even be able to get close to Rito-san!
I'd rather not.
Damn, I came on too strong.
Uh...
Something wrong, Rito-san?
Momo!
They're...
Wh-What do you guys want?
Saruyama and the others were acting normally until a minute ago.
We found you... Golden Darkness...
You wanna play a little game?!
Rito-san!
His strength's abnormal.
Someone's controlling him.
They're fast!
No, that's not it.
I'm just too slow.
I've become too comfortable with life on Earth.
Yami!
I'm coming to save you!
I'm on... my... way...
Don't look!
Rito-san!
I hate perverts.
Wh-What's going on?
It's okay now.
What is that?
You forgot already? I have the ability to communicate with plants.
I've been collecting hundreds of different plants from all over the galaxy ever since I was little.
I can control them all at will.
Just as I thought.
You haven't killed any of them.
I guess what I heard is true. Living on Earth has dulled your fangs.
Who are you?
Someone who knows what you really are.
Open your eyes, Golden Darkness.
This is no place for you.
Your true nature is darkness.
You exist for no other reason than to spill blood.
Wake up from this naïve dream.
Your target is within your reach.
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
Doubt and dish.