Menu
Log
Save
Load
Options
Menu
Log
Save
Load
Options
Can I... stay here tonight...?
Mori Mami:  I missed... the last train...
I missed the last train.
Can I stay here tonight?
Ooh, this is it!
It turned into a sleepover!
I see how it works now!
Oh, there were other situations that could be useful for the Harem Plan.
Gotta write them down!
Momo Velia Deviluke...
The third princess of Deviluke
and a member of Class 1-B at our school, Sainan High.
She's 151 centimeters tall, with bust, waist, and hip measurements
estimated to be 80, 54, and 79, respectively.
Gentlemen!
We are all comrades who fell for this beautiful, innocent girl.
However, no one would benefit from us fighting amongst ourselves for Momo-san's love,
which might even break her tender, caring heart.
Hence, we hereby form an assembly of gentlemen who love Momo-san equally.
Venus Momo Club.
VMC! VMC! VMC!
Mori Mami:  Please... come to me...
All right!
I'm just about done conquering this character!
I'll save here and call it a day.
Maybe my relationship with Rito-san can progress this smoothly too.
After all, Rito-san...
What are you doing, Momo?
Homework?
Oh, Rito-san!
I'm looking for portable plant seeds that I can use for self-protection.
Oh?
You're pretty amazing, Momo.
Huh?
I mean, you're always saving
Mikan or me when we're in trouble.
I'm just stunned by how dependable you are.
I'm flattered.
And you're studying like this so you can be prepared in case of an emergency, right?
I can tell that you're very committed.
But I want you to let me know
if I can help in any way.
I might not be able to do much,
being an Earthling and all,
but I don't want to put all the burden on you.
I appreciate you always being there for me, Momo.
R-Rito-san, not here...
So you want me to stop, Momo?
W-Well, I didn't say that, but...
Mikan-san is in the next room.
Onee-sama and Nana are around too.
What's your point?
What...
made me this way?
He completely stole my heart,
and now I can't live without him.
Rito-san...
You're a sinful man.
Momo!
Math
Lemme copy your homework!
Huh?
What's wrong?
You feeling sick or something?
Nana...
How many times must I tell you not to enter my room without permission?!
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Rito-san has been watching me!
Oh, no. I need to pull myself together.
I'm so happy that I can't stop grinning!
Momo-chan, what are those for?
Those flowers are beautiful.
Oh, these?
These are rainbow-colored roses. They're a rarity even in space!
I thought they'd help brighten up the classroom.
Really?
Wow!
That's a princess for you.
Being considerate is important, Momo-kun.
Sensei, I'm flattered.
But it's no big deal.
Momo-chan's so popular!
It's all an act. She's just pretending to be a goody two-shoes.
Momo-san!
We recently formed a fan club in your honor.
We call it the Venus Momo Club!
Or for short...
VMC!
Huh?
Let us know if we can be of any service!
We're even willing to sacrifice our lives for you!
U-Um...
We're here to serve you!
Huh?
Wow, a fan club?
And the leader is Nakajima-kun!
Second-year Kusao-senpai is in it too!
I appreciate your feelings, but...
you need to cherish the bodies you were born with.
Please don't overexert yourselves.
Momo-san is so kind!
Nana-chan!
We're on your side!
What?
After all, we love...
flat ch—
Well, excuse me for being flat-chested!
VMC...
I don't think I'll mind having a fan club.
But I'll be focusing on
Rito-san for the rest of the day.
Oh, right.
Rito-san said he's going shopping to buy something his dad asked for.
I should go with him on the way home.
Momo-san!
We'll carry that for you!
Oh, but I'm responsible for that today.
There are stairs ahead!
Please be careful!
Th-Thank you.
We polished your desk!
We'll open and close the door for you!
Boys who wish to speak with Momo-san will require our permission!
Wow...
This is actually pretty annoying.
I liked the idea of having
my very own fan club,
but it's impossible for me
to go meet Rito-san this way.
Oh, it's Rito-san!
It's been so long since we had
an outing with just the two of us.
An outing?
We're just taking a detour
on the way back from school.
Plus, it's just to help out my dad.
That's all right!
I'll have fun so long as I can be with you!
Excellent!
I'm sure Rito-san will love it!
Oh, Rito and Lala-san aren't coming back tonight.
What?
Dad has a bunch of deadlines to meet,
so they'll be staying there for a while to help.
What?!
The miso soup looks delicious!
Mori Mami:  Please... come to me...
Rito-san...
A-Are you okay, Yuuki-kun?
Yep, these are still the perfect size!
C-Cut it out, Risa!
You were asking for it
when you started spacing out.
You need to be more alert, Haruna.
Sairenji?!
Come on, Risa!
The plan was a success!
Rito!
I'm here now!
You two know better than that!
Illicit relationships are prohibited!
Lala, where were you?
I was busy making this,
to give you a boost!
I'm sure you'll be wide awake after eating some!
Y-Yeah, I bet.
Oh, that's bold!
I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
Yuuki Rito.
Yami, that thing earlier wasn't on purp—
These snacks are for you.
Th-Thanks.
But what's the occasion?
Mikan was worried about you.
Oh...
Rito-kun!
I'm free after school today!
Spend some time with me!
Sorry, I have plans.
What? You do?
Are you still helping your dad with his work?
Yeah, today's the last day.
Rito, thanks for waiting!
All right, let's get going.
I'm not in any rush, though.
Hang in there.
Why am I so frustrated?
I've only been away from him for a little while.
I want to see Rito-san.
I want to talk to him.
I want Rito-san to...
I should have a chance.
Tomorrow will be the day!
All right!
You did it, Nana-chan!
Momo-san is currently changing clothes in the locker room.
Stay on standby here.
Roger!
Changing clothes?!
Momo-san's getting changed...
...right over there, at this very moment.
She's getting changed!
Excuse me, Nakajima.
Something's been worrying me.
What is it, Sugimura?
Yuuki Rito.
He's Lala-senpai's potential fiancé, isn't he?
I don't think he's someone we need to worry about.
Still, this discipline committee member's report has me concerned.
Yuuki Rito is a man who knows no shame. He's on par with the principal.
He's been a topic of discussion many times in our meetings.
What?!
He's that shameless?!
Then could it be that...
the pure and innocent Momo-san is...
Momo!
Rito-san, is that...
Come! Eat this ice cream before it melts!
I'm your master!
Call me Master!
Master!
Have mercy!
That despicable pervert!
Calm down, Nakajima!
You're the pervert here!
We've got a problem, guys!
The girls are done changing,
but Momo-san's gone missing!
What?!
It's Momo.
She said it's important.
I wonder if she found out
something new about Mea.
Hey, Momo?
Welcome!
Momo?
You sure took your time.
Oh, sorry.
So, you had something important to...
Why are you in gym clothes?
Rito-san's face!
His voice! His scent!
I missed this feeling.
Why does seeing him
make me feel so warm inside?
Momo?
Rito-san!
Right, I'm here to do more than just see him.
It's about the Harem Plan.
I wanted to talk to you about it in private.
So this isn't about Mea?
How does it feel, Rito-san?
You're lying on a mat in the gym
equipment shed, alone with a girl.
As the king of a harem, are you excited by this in any way?
N-No, I'm not really...
Rito-san's heart is beating so fast.
Are you telling me the truth?
W-Wait!
M-Momo...
Are you sure?
This is embarrassing!
It takes real courage to
tease Rito-san when he's awake.
But I need to keep going.
I'll render him unable to think rationally
and turn him into a pleasure seeker.
Momo!
Mo... M-Momo!
Mo... Momo!
Mo...
Rito-san!
I-It's all right.
I'm not scared.
I was always prepared for this when I tempted him.
This is bad.
I'm starting to feel strange.
I need to stop her.
Huh?
N-No!
I shouldn't be afraid of Rito-san!
Have you finally got into the mood?
Well...
I'm...
Rito-san, you should be
more honest with your feelings.
Momo!
So...
Momo-san!
There she is! She's alive!
Damn you, Yuuki Rito!
What?
You're going to pay for this!
Prepare yourself!
How'd they get in? I had tied the doors with ivy!
Mea-san?
Get away from Momo-san!
Rito-san!
You're safe now, Momo-san!
We, the VMC, shall give this pervert an appropriate punishment!
We'll give him a punishment so severe that
he won't dare to do something like this again!
Severe?
What?
I was only talking with Rito-san.
Rito-san is not the kind of man you think he is.
So...
apologize to Rito-san.
Right this second.
Yes, ma'am.
We were fools!
Forgive us!
Scold us more, Momo-sama!
Punish us, Momo-sama!
Ow...
Are you okay, Rito-san?
Jeez, you ruined everything, Mea-san.
Well, it was not fair of you
to flirt with him in secret!
Not fair?
I'll never understand the way she thinks.
I should be more careful next time.
Back there, why did I...
I'm pathetic.
I guess I still lack determination.
Why did she react like that earlier?
And why does she insist on
assembling a harem for me?
Was she being honest when she said that as the third princess of Deviluke,
she wants to work out the issue of who will take the throne and help Lala earn my love?
Or was she...
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
atama no naka kimi wa dare to randebu shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Good morning.
M-Momo?!
Rito-san!
I should share this happiness with everyone, right?