Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Where am I?
Is this my bathroom?
I could have sworn I was just at school...
What am I touching?
It tickles, Senpai!
Who are you?! Why are you in my bathtub?!
What's gotten into you?
We're just inside your dream, Senpai.
"Senpai"?
Wh-Who are you?!
A beast!
What are you staring at?!
This happens to guys all the time, right?
Let me get a closer look!
I feel so hot.
Is this what being turned on feels like?
No, it's...
"Turned on"?
Wait! If this is a dream, what's some girl I've never seen before doing here?!
Oh, that's simple, Senpai.
It's because our hearts are connected now.
A dream is a world that the imagination creates from memories.
I'm here bathing with you like this because of how strongly you're recalling something.
Something like...
A girl...
a bath...
and being turned on.
Were you in some kind of shocking situation like this not too long ago?
What happened?
Tell me, Senpai.
You're the best candidate for the next King of Deviluke, after all.
I don't see a problem with a king who has concubines.
Let me help you assemble your very own harem!
You could have us all to yourself, you know.
Even Yami-san.
A harem plan...
Your second-generation transformation abilities are impressive.
You can even merge with other living beings and connect with their minds.
Nevertheless, I will warn you:
If you ever raise a finger against him,
I will consider you my enemy.
I love that look in your eyes!
Don't worry.
I'd never steal your target.
I don't want Master to get mad at me.
Yuuki-senpai really is a beast.
That was an amazing dream.
And...
I found out something interesting.
Momo-chan's true self, which she never reveals in school, is just as Nana-chan described.
And the Harem Plan.
Momo-chan's trying to add Yami-oneechan to Rito-senpai's harem.
That's the exact opposite of Master's and my Darkness Plan.
Whose plan will succeed?
It's like a game.
Wonderful!
So you're Nana's new friend?
Let me introduce her to you.
She's Kurosaki Mea.
Nice to meet you!
Let's get along!
Oh, I think we've met before.
Thank you for your help yesterday!
You know her, Sairenji?
What about you, Yuuki-kun? I thought you knew her.
Me?
Well, it does feel like we've met before.
You need to be mindful of him.
That man has no shame to speak of.
That's right! He's a beast!
How is he shameless?
He acts like a pervert! Didn't I tell you already?!
What's wrong with that?
That's perfectly natural behavior for a living creature.
I'm interested!
Please teach me everything you know, Senpai!
What are you saying, Mea?!
That's quite a bold thing to say to someone you've just met.
Kurosaki Mea-san, was it?
Maybe I should consider adding her to the harem plan.
But Kotegawa-san...
Hey, Mea-chan!
Yes?
You know, Nana is really happy about being friends with you.
So make sure to get along with her, okay?
Lala, it's embarrassing when you put it that way! Stop!
Relax! It's fine!
Stop it!
My goodness.
What's wrong with that Kurosaki girl?
She's so shameless.
I can't let my guard down.
There are already more than enough dangerous elements around Yuuki-kun as it is.
Oh?
You're heading home too, Kotegawa?
Y-Yuuki-kun?
You're alone? Where are Lala and the others?
They said they were doing something with Momo and her friends.
Mikan went to clean up our dad's workplace,
so I thought I'd go home early and get some dinner ready.
Oh...
Mikan's away as well...
She said that Dad's place was really messy.
She couldn't bear looking at it.
You live in the same direction as me, right?
How about walking home together?
Honestly, my sister is so hopeless.
She told me she had something important to show me,
but it was just a Magical Kyouko costume show.
If I had known from the start, I'd have gone straight home with Rito-san.
Mikan-san will be coming home late today,
so Rito-san and I can do anything we want and much more!
What a marvelous way to spend time together!
Oh no, I'm drooling...
Look at that!
A chance to move my Harem Plan forward!
Considering where Kotegawa-san lives, they'll eventually have to go different ways.
I need to make a move before that!
I found a great book in the trash!
I'll bring it back to my office and enjoy it thoroughly!
I'll use this Adrena flower that
intoxicates you with just a whiff!
This brings back memories...
Excitement Park
We took shelter from the rain in that thing once, didn't we?
Y-Yeah, I think so.
I was so surprised when the principal popped up out of nowhere!
We'll have to part ways soon.
That was so short.
I feel absolutely amazing!
Wh-Why is he naked?
Let's run, Kotegawa!
Oh, yeah. He saved me like this once before too.
You never disappoint, Rito-san!
Running away while holding her hand...
How romantic is that?
Now she's heading toward Rito-san's place too.
Your work here is done, Mr. Principal.
Thanks for your help.
Well, now...
Kotegawa-san doesn't look very discontent.
Whoa, a sudden shower?!
Keep it up, my little rainflower!
We're getting soaked!
Kotegawa, my place is close by! We'll stop there for a while!
Yuuki-kun's home?
B-But no one's there right now!
Lala and Mikan aren't home yet.
I'll go get you a towel.
O-Okay.
Would you like to take a shower?
You'll catch a cold if you don't warm up.
Just throw your wet clothes in the dryer while you shower.
Um...
O-Okay.
Even my underwear is soaked.
I never dreamed that I'd be taking a shower in Yuuki-kun's house.
Not to mention we're home alone.
If he did something dirty now...
Kotegawa?
Yes?!
I can only give you my own clothes for now.
I'll leave them here by the door.
Please put up with these until Lala and the others get home.
Okay.
Man, it's pouring out there.
I hope the girls are all right.
I've changed the sight outside your windows to CG, Rito-san.
Now I only need to use this transmuter barrier emitter, and...
Okay! This'll buy me some time, even if Onee-sama and the rest get home.
Perfect!
This is what he gave me to wear?!
Rito's room
Looks like the rain isn't letting up.
Yuuki-kun!
Oh, have you warm—
Th-Thanks for... letting me use the shower.
Why are you dressed like that?!
What do you mean? This is what you gave me to wear.
Lala and the others aren't back yet?
No...
This is weird.
I'm sure I gave her a sweater with matching pants.
Oh, right! Want something to drink?
I'll go get us something.
O-Okay.
Nothing but a white shirt is standard clothing for this kind of situation, Rito-san.
Next up is...
How cute.
Sorry for the wait.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's nice and warm.
The girls sure are taking their time.
Yeah...
It's getting dark outside too.
Um... I'm sorry, Kotegawa.
Are you okay with wearing that?
Yeah...
A blackout?
What?
Ouch!
Sorry, Koteg—
No! You knocked her over too early, Rito-san!
This is bound to end in the way it usually does.
Wh-What should I do?
I have an aphrodisiac flower too,
but it only lasts for so long...
Kotegawa?
I can't move... like this...
That's perfectly natural behavior for a living creature.
I...
I can't stand shameless people.
I've been like this for as long as I can remember.
It's always the shameless boys who pull on the girls' skirts and ruin the class's atmosphere.
I've always stood up for the weak girls,
but it's normal for boys to behave that way.
And I've come to realize that
it doesn't make them bad people.
If...
If you promise me you won't do anything shameless to any other girl,
I'll...
P-Perfect! She's on fire!
I never thought I'd see the day when the epitome of seriousness herself
would act this boldly from merely being knocked down!
No, she's a true girl under that disciplinary officer mask of hers!
I should've seen this coming!
They might even...
They might even end up going all the way!
Go on, Kotegawa-san!
Be brave now!
Take the next step!
Go on and show Rito-san your everything!
Huh?
There's an invisible wall in front of the house!
Is this another one of your weird inventions, Lala?
They're back already?
But they won't be able to come inside right away since the barrier is still up.
The barrier broke?!
Wait, Kotegawa!
Y-You've got it all wrong!
I don't do shameless stuff on purpose!
Well, sure, I am interested, but...
I mean, me pushing you down a while ago was just an accident too, so...
You're so dumb.
I was obviously joking!
I was only testing you.
Really?
Of course!
Could you be any more shameless?
That was close.
What was I thinking?
But... surprisingly enough, he can be serious too.
The lights came back on!
Rito, are you in your room?
Thank goodness.
We're back! Sorry we're late!
We brought some... food...
Rito, what have you done now?!
I didn't do anything!
We just got soaked in the rain, so I lent her some clothes!
Huh? But it didn't rain today.
What? That can't be. I'm sure—
Rito, could you at least put some effort into your stupid lies?!
Momo-san, was this your doing?
And here I thought they would make some progress.
Anyway, why did the barrier break?
That beam...
Was it an attack from outside?
Mea, why are you playing around?
Hm? I'm not playing, Master!
I'm still observing them, just as I should.
I just thought I'd throw a wrench in Momo-chan's Harem Plan.
Don't forget why you're there.
It's almost time for the greeting.
She'll be arriving in the Solar System soon.
An inhabitant of the darkness just like us.
A guest from the galaxy.
A guest, huh?
How will Yami-oneechan respond?
I can't wait to see!
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
The past, friends, and smiles.