Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Welcome to Earth!
Are you Nemesis?
Nope, I'm Mea. I'm here as my master's representative.
A representative?
I came all the way out here to this
backwater planet for Golden Darkness,
and all they send to welcome me is this little girl?
What are you hoping to accomplish by having us fight?
How should I know?
I just said what I was told to say.
Well, whatever.
Let her know she can expect me to produce results, little girl.
What's wrong with her?
She's so unpleasant.
Let her do as she pleases.
Master?
She's Azenda the Tyrant.
She was once a renowned assassin in the Tahal Galaxy.
However, after tasting defeat at the hands of Golden Darkness,
she fell into disgrace.
Her lust for revenge is exactly what we need to ignite Golden Darkness's fighting instincts.
That will eventually lead to Yuuki Rito's elimination.
Rito-senpai's elimination?
What's wrong?
Nothing. I was just wondering how Nana-chan would react if Yami-oneechan disposed of Rito-senpai.
You're overthinking the issue.
Both you and Golden Darkness are weapons created for the sole purpose of fighting.
You can only live inside the darkness.
Yes. I understand, Master!
How long has it been since I came to this planet?
How long can I stay here?
This is not the place for you.
Is that really true?
Oh, boy! I found Yami-chan!
Why don't you come work up
a good sweat by jogging with me?
When we're done, I'm gonna lick and fondl—
It's morning already?
Huh? Where's Celine?
I wonder when she woke up.
Rito-san, you really know what you're doing!
I'm not holding back, Momo!
Don't be so rough!
No! No!
Momo, I...
Rito-san!
Momo!
Rito! I can't believe—
Hey. Good morning, Mikan.
Good morning!
You're playing games?!
Celine woke me up to play.
I was sleeping in my room until she dragged me over here.
Okay, okay. We'll get back to playing.
That had me going.
I get the feeling something like this happened before, though.
Were you expecting to see something else?
How could you, Mikan-san?
I'm supporting my sister's love for Rito-san.
You have absolutely nothing to worry about!
She's so suspicious.
I'll take your word for it.
But do something about your habit of sleepwalking into Rito's bed.
Sure!
I'm not only supporting my sister though, Mikan-san.
I'm done bathing!
Okay, Onee-sama!
I'm still concerned about the barrier failing the other day.
Was it really hit by an attack from the outside?
That would mean someone is targeting Rito-san.
Or am I overthinking the whole thing?
No, I can't afford to be optimistic.
Someone's definitely trying to use Yami-san to kill him.
It looks like I need to get closer to Yami-san, after all.
For Rito-san's sake as well.
Please look after her for me, Momo-san.
Is this why she won't open up to me?
What are you doing with my bra?
If you ask me, you're still not ready for one.
Shut up! I won't be flat forever!
I don't think Rito-san will mind if you aren't curvaceous.
Why are you bringing him up?!
Morning, Yami-Yami!
I'd appreciate it if you refrained from
touching my breasts when greeting me.
What's the matter? It's not like it'll make them shrink.
Wait, you aren't wearing a bra?
Rito-kun!
It's been so long!
Oh, it's Runrun!
I'm finally back from my tour!
Run, you're an idol! You shouldn't be clinging to—
You're worried about me?
I'm so happy!
Run-san! Indecent behavior isn't allowed on school grounds!
Kotegawa-san, you're always so mad.
Of course! It's my job!
Let's just stay calm, Kotegawa...
Why are you taking Run-san's side?
Indecent things wouldn't happen
around you if you didn't act this way!
Haruna, Rito's having fun with the others!
Let's go join them!
But...
Come on, let's go!
Th-That's right! I should be more assertive!
Here I go!
Don't worry, Haruna-san!
If you can't work up the courage to join them, I'll help!
Concentrating willpower!
Ow...
Moving people with willpower
isn't allowed on school grounds!
I-I'm sorry!
Hang in there, Rito-kun!
Man, what are they doing?
Yami-Yami, let's join in too!
No, I'm not in the mood today.
Why did I refuse?
I had no reason to do so.
Sainan 1st Elementary School
Yeah, and—
Yami-san, what are you doing here?
And I haven't seen you in your Sainan uniform before!
This is so cool!
Mikan.
Would you like to go for some taiyaki?
Yeah!
When I get lonely, I want to see Mikan.
I don't know when I started to feel this way.
And it's like Momo-san's been all over Rito lately.
Princess Momo?
I can't figure out what's on her mind.
Yeah...
Sorry! I've just been going on and on about my problems...
It's okay.
Yami-san, you seem down.
N-Not at all.
You sure?
How can she tell?
Oh, right!
This is for you.
Don't you think it's well-made?
I thought of you when I saw it in the shop and just had to buy it!
Ta-da! Now we match!
Thank you, Mikan.
I see.
Just as the intel said, she's let her guard down.
Being with Mikan really soothes me.
Now we match, huh?
Is that you, Yami?
Yuuki Rito?
What are you doing here?
My dad asked me to buy materials for him.
And you?
I see. Good for you.
Thanks, Yami.
Why are you thanking me?
Because you hang out with Mikan.
She gets lonely pretty easily.
Everyone always depends on her since she's mature for her age.
But you're older than her, so she can be herself around you.
You're really important to her.
She might even see you as an older sister.
What's wrong?
Did I say something bad?
No.
I get these warm feelings when I'm with Mikan.
Like everyone else at school.
But something deep down inside of me refuses to accept that.
I lived a lonely life in a world of
darkness before I came to Earth.
These hands will never be clean again.
I mustn't be happy.
That wouldn't fit me at all.
I end up thinking like that.
I couldn't even tell Mikan how I felt, so why am I telling him?
I don't think you should worry so much about it.
You're better off doing whatever you want.
What you've done, at least since you came to Earth,
has been good for both you and Mikan.
I should do whatever I want?
What I want to do right now is kill you.
Just kidding.
I envy your simplicity.
But thanks to you, I feel a bit relieved.
Oh?
What?!
So you can still dodge an attack like that despite having lowered your guard,
Golden Darkness?
Azenda the Tyrant!
So you remember me, huh?
I'm pleased.
I'm going to enjoy exacting my revenge.
Who is she?
An assassin I've defeated before.
She's fast with her whip and she can use psychokinesis.
Like Oshizu-chan?
Yes, but hers is nowhere near as powerful as Murasame Shizu's.
She mostly relies on her whip to attack.
She's no match for my Trans-Ability.
What I'm proud of is my accuracy, not my power.
I can easily use an unconscious human as my puppet.
This girl will help me!
Your precious friend shall help me drag your name through the mud!
Stop, Mikan!
She can't hear us now!
You're on the defensive, Golden Darkness!
Azenda is using her psychokinesis to control Mikan.
That means...
Don't just stop!
Yami!
Is your little friend that precious to you?
Yami, I'll hold Mikan back!
Use this chance to deal with her!
Oh, please. You're out of your league, earthling boy.
I've seen how well you get along with her.
I'm shocked.
When we last fought, you were like an emotionless machine.
And now you're playing friends?
I won't be satisfied with just killing you.
I want to see you cry, Golden Darkness!
How admirable.
You must care about your friend a lot.
I'm sorry for getting you involved in this, Mikan.
I'll save you, no matter what!
Even if it costs me my life.
What are you doing, Yami-oneechan?
Fight back!
Who cares about hostages?
My beloved Yami-oneechan would never lose.
You should see yourself, Golden Darkness.
How does it feel to have your
dear friend play with your body?
Don't worry. I'll put you out of
your misery once I've had my fun.
Wouldn't you two like to go together?
To heaven, I mean.
I lost my name as an assassin in the underworld because of you,
and both my body and soul were ravaged.
And now that girl will die because of you.
You bring misfortune to everyone around you!
You couldn't be more wrong!
Mikan and Yami aren't misfortunate!
They're nothing like you!
I suppose you'd like to die first, earthling boy!
I'm glad I decided to check on you.
Who the hell are you?
Momo Velia Deviluke, the third princess of planet Deviluke.
Deviluke?
You're related to that warlord, Gid Lucion Deviluke?
What do you want?
This has nothing to do with you.
Don't think you'll get away after scraping my face.
You think this has nothing to do with me?
These people are all very important to me.
Then I'll destroy you all together!
What's wrong?!
Is running away all you can do?!
Is this how low the name of Deviluke has fallen?
Please don't get the wrong idea.
I merely prefer not to fight uncouthly when a gentleman is watching.
Besides, you're already done for.
Huh?
What did you do?
What...
Mikan!
It seems the full-body paralysis broke your concentration.
That's no surprise, though.
The thorns of the Black Rose of Zelas are imbued with a very potent poison.
Don't worry. It isn't lethal.
I happen to keep a botanic garden in virtual space.
I can control those plants as I wish.
These are Cannon Flowers, a species of touch-me-nots.
Oh dear. It looks like I missed.
I'll have to take care not to miss next time.
Wait!
Please, spare my life!
I'll do anything you want!
No thanks.
Mikan!
Yami-san?
You're a mess! What happened?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
As long as you're okay...
Thank you, Princess Momo.
Had you not come, the situation would've gotten out of hand.
No such thing! I just did what anyone would!
Thanks so much, Momo.
I couldn't do anything by myself.
It was nothing.
So what do we do with her?
I'll ask Zastin-san to hand her over to the
galactic police, so there's no need to worry.
I think... I may have tried to do too much on my own.
I've learned that whenever I'm in trouble, I should
count on my friends instead of doing everything myself.
Yami-san...
I can't count on you though, Yuuki Rito.
Just kidding.
Why, Onee-chan?
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
Changes.