Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Nana-chan, you're such a fast swimmer!
You were so cool out there!
I'm good at sports.
You should join the swimming club!
What? I dunno about that...
You might even make it to the national championships!
Why didn't you fight back against Azenda?
My Mirror Image
If Momo-chan didn't show up, you might've been killed.
Might have.
I realized I should count on my friends more often
instead of trying to do everything on my own.
Your friends?
Mea, it's true that we're weapons made to fight,
but that's not all there is to our lives.
If you really intend to treat me as your family,
then familiarize yourself with people and the warmth of friendship.
The warmth... of friendship?
We'll be able to understand each other then.
I don't get it.
I've been alone all my life.
Master taught me to live that way.
Mea!
Did you watch me swim?
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
I kinda had a fight with my older sister.
Your older sister?
Wow, I didn't know you had a sibling too!
Don't worry!
Stuff like that works itself out in no time!
How?
Like, Momo teases me all the time and we fight a lot,
but before I know it, we're back to talking to each other like nothing happened!
That's just how sisters are!
That's... That's just because you and Momo-chan have been together your entire lives!
I...
M-Mea? I'm sorry! Did I say something wrong?
You must be having a hard time too, Yami-san.
Not at all.
Now that I know what I must do, I feel relieved.
Really? Glad to hear it.
After the encounter with the assassin Azenda, Yami-san told Rito-san and me
about Kurosaki Mea.
That she's a second-generation Trans user made by an underground organization.
That she's like a little sister to Yami-san.
And that...
Mea is exactly how I used to be.
She believes that she can only live as a weapon in the underworld.
But if possible, I'd like her to understand all the things I've found on this planet.
I'm sure she would change, just as I did.
I understand how you feel, Yami-san.
Regardless, I must still consider her a threat.
That's perfectly fine, Princess Momo.
You're the type to continue plotting behind the backs of others,
so I doubt we could ever get along.
Nonetheless, I'll be counting on you in this matter.
Couldn't you have found a nicer way to put that?
Thank you, Celine-chan.
Rito!
What's up?
Um... Can we talk?
That's it. I may have accidentally made Mea feel even worse.
Do you think there's anything I can do for her?
Mea fought with her sister?
Oh, she must mean Yami.
Are you even listening?
Sorry!
Well, let's see...
How about doing something
that'll let her have some fun?
What do you mean?
Back when we were smaller,
whenever Mikan was feeling down,
I would dance, make weird faces, and do whatever else it took to make her laugh.
Even if you're feeling down, you'll start to feel better once you begin to laugh.
Make her laugh... and have fun...
I'll give it a try! Thanks, Rito!
Rito!
Lala?
You were watching?
Yeah. I figured it'd be for the best if I didn't butt in.
Thanks for helping Nana.
I didn't really tell her anything though.
Nana's more innocent than you may think.
Mea-chan was her first friend in a class where she didn't fit in,
so I'm sure Nana holds her dear.
It'd be nice if everything worked out between them.
Yeah.
Yami's changed so much too.
I'm sure everything will work out fine.
Yami-chan?
What does she have to do with this?
Ah, forget it...
What do you want to show me, Nana-chan?
Just come on!
Look, there!
Hey!
Ouch.
Do you know this doggy?
He's Haruna's pet, Sairenji Maron.
He's got a funny face, doesn't he?
Yeah, you're right!
There, there.
Remember what I told you about Mea?
Please help me cheer her up.
Well, since it's you who's asking...
I'll be expecting two pieces of beef jerky in return.
He's so soft!
And squishy!
Sorry for troubling you, Haruna-san. I know you're busy with your club activities.
It's okay.
Maron seems happy about getting some fresh air.
And it's so nice of Nana-chan to try to cheer her friend up.
It sure is.
Rito-san, Rito-san!
Since Haruna-san's here, why don't you make a move on her?
What are you talking about, Momo?!
I can keep an eye on them on my own.
Oh, I get it. Momo must be worried about Nana too.
Okay, let me show you my pets!
These are animals I met out in space!
Whoa! You have so many!
I have plenty more, but I only
called out the cute ones for now.
This one's adorable!
Kurosaki Mea...
She's smiling as if she's truly having fun.
It tickles!
That's some excellent licking.
For us dogs, licking is the greatest form of affection.
I can't lose to them!
Behold my ultimate skill!
What's he doing?!
Lickity lick!
Amazing!
Stop that, Maron!
Can't you see your licking is bothering her?!
The bastard!
Who does he think he is?!
We have our pride as pets too!
You guys!
Where do you think you're—
Hey!
Don't lick me there!
Cut it... Cut it out!
Nana-chan! Kurosaki-san!
Wh-What happened?!
Sairenji!
Hey, sto—
Sairenji, are you—
Stop! Stop!
Oh my!
Yuuki-kun, stop that!
Sorry, but I can't control my hands!
Oh my! This is so romantic!
Wait, I can't just stand here and watch!
Cut it out already!
Jeez...
Nana, Rito-san and Haruna-san are in a wonderful—
I mean, in great danger! Hurry!
I know!
Huh? Where's my phone?
Where is it?
Hey, give that back!
Nana-chan!
Gotcha!
Nana!
Mea?
If I used Trans now, Nana-chan would find out who I really am.
But it's fine.
I must save Nana-chan.
By killing that...
Sister!
Onee-chan...
Man, talk about a close call.
I'm sorry, everyone.
That whole mess was my fault.
I-It's fine, Nana-chan!
Don't worry about it!
I owe you an apology too, Mea.
Huh? Why?
I had lots of fun!
Animals are wonderful!
Licking's wonderful too!
You should lick me sometime, Yuuki-senpai!
Wh-What are you saying, Mea?!
Everything worked out in the end, huh?
Nana wanted to cheer you up, Mea-chan.
Sister!
Nana-chan did all that for me?
What's going on?
My heart feels so warm.
Is this what Onee-chan was talking about?
Mea really is a good girl.
Would you like to make her a candidate for your harem?
Did you have to bring that up now?
I'm joking.
There are still too many things
I'm uncertain about at the moment.
Oh, okay...
But that would be the most ideal.
If we can have Mea come to our side,
her Master, who's controlling things
behind the scenes, would be forced to act.
Golden Darkness...
It would seem that you're trying to lead Mea on the path of a human.
Is that some kind of sisterly emotion?
A weapon has no need for such things.
But I can use those emotions.
I know that from experience now.
I need to change my methods.
I must show you, Golden,
that no matter how much you adore humans,
you cannot escape your fate as a weapon.
Morning, Yami-san!
Good morning, Kurosaki Mea.
What's going on, Mea? Since when were you two getting along so well?
Mea-san's been talking with
classmates other than Nana lately.
She looks like a normal Earthling girl at first sight.
But...
That pickled ginger was so damn red!
Really?
Hey, Momo-chan!
Wanna hit up a karaoke box with us later?
Ugh, what a pain...
Singing in front of guys would
be way too embarrassing!
Oh, come on!
You gotta be kidding!
I've got Run-chan's bikini poster!
I'll take it back to my office and enjoy every inch of it!
This bikini's as good as nonexistent in my fantasies!
Run-rurun!
Run?
You've never heard of her?
She's a student here and a famous idol.
And she's a childhood friend of Lala's.
So she's an alien too?
Yep, from the royal family of Memorze!
She only has one body, which she shares with her twin brother.
Whenever she sneezes, the female Run and the male Ren switch.
They're an unusual kind.
They switch genders?
What do you mean?
Well, you see...
Rito!
Swappity Snapper-kun!
Rito-senpai turned into a girl!
They swap genders like this in a flash!
Hey, don't just come out of nowhere and turn me into a girl!
I'll change you back right away.
Oh, sorry!
Looks like the Swappity Snapper-kun's battery ran out.
You're kidding me!
Don't worry!
You'll naturally return to being a guy with time!
If Saruyama saw me like this...
What's up, Lala-chan?
Have you seen Rito?
Riko-chan!
I'm not Riko!
Wait a moment, Senpai!
Mea, wait!
Sairenji-san?
Y-Yes?
Have you seen Lala-san and Yuuki-kun?
I don't see their bags anywhere.
Um...
They had to leave early today.
They already left? Why?
It's called an elopement!
E-Elopem—
Yui, you're so naive!
Those two would never do that!
Don't scare me like that!
Maybe I should've went with them...
Why do I have to take school so seriously?
So, I understand that you had to leave school early,
but why are you dressed like that?
Lala forced me to!
Mea-chan wanted to see how cute she was!
Mea?
Your boobs are so big!
Stop! Quit groping me!
Come on, you know you like it!
Um, who's she?
My friend, Kurosaki Mea.
They ended up coming along.
Do you plan on letting go anytime soon?!
You're just too cute. I wanna lick you.
Don't lick me!
Weirdos just keep popping up around Rito...
This is how you beat this stage.
Lickety lick!
Mea-san, would you like coffee or tea?
Tea, please!
You really like your tea that way, Mea?
Yeah, I have a sweet tooth!
Oh, do you want some too?
Here you go.
Hey, Celine, are you okay?
Sorry! You okay, Nana?
Are you making fun of me?!
I'm not!
Then what?!
Calm down, Nana! Calm down!
I'm all sticky from the tea Celine sprayed me with.
I can't keep wearing this forever either.
I've really gotta change.
How do you even take this off?
Jeez, Lala just had to make me wear this pain-in-the-neck outfit.
Calm down! It's your own body!
I know I've turned into a girl a few times before, but I just can't get used to it.
I don't feel like myself.
Are these what Nana is so obsessed with?
They're so heavy. Don't they get in the way?
You're showing some interest in the female body.
That's very good, Rito-san.
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
When you change...