Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Good morning. How do you feel?
I feel great, Tear!
Really? I'm happy to hear that.
I'll read you a book later.
She's your mother?
She is the one who gave me life,
but the word "mother" isn't appropriate.
I am an organism created from her cells through scientific means.
Like... a clone?
Yes.
Tearju was a genius without peer in the field of extraterrestrial biology.
But that's something I found out later.
After I was born, she was...
I-I'll be done soon, so just wait a little longer, okay?
Sure!
I'm sorry.
Eve...
It's really good, Tear!
And so the little girl and her many, many friends lived happily ever after.
The end.
That was interesting!
Really?
But...
What are "friends"?
I didn't really get that part.
Tear?
Um...
Friends are people you can play, fight, laugh and even cry with.
They're people who are important to you.
Tear, do you think I'll be able to make friends?
Of course you will!
When you do, make sure you introduce them to me!
Okay!
Those were happy days, a time of kindness.
Tear taught me many things,
like a mother or sister would.
My heart was full of light back then.
But...
Mikan-san?
Momo-san, where are you going?
I'm just going to the bathroom...
The bathroom, huh?
Go on.
It's late, so go back to your room once you're done.
Wait, Mikan-san!
Are you really okay with leaving those two alone?
Say what you will, but Rito-san and Yami-san are young adults of the opposite sex!
They're in a bed, bound together!
Who knows what could happen?
Wh-What could happen?
Y-Yami...
Y-Yuuki Rito...
My body... feels so hot...
So...
But the two of them would never...
Why not check on them, Mikan-san?
We'll go together!
What happened next?
Where's Tearju-san now?
I don't know.
Not even if she's dead or alive.
What do you mean?
Tear!
Look!
I made this! It's a present for—
Lunatique-kun is gone.
She ran off, leaving you behind.
Why?
You have nothing to worry about.
We'll raise you properly...
as the weapon you're meant to be.
Weapon?
Yes.
You're a weapon created to kill.
You're meant to extinguish lives with your Trans.
On the surface, they were a respectable research institute,
but their only goal was to turn me into the strongest Trans weapon ever.
They wanted to start a new business in the universe torn by centuries of galactic war.
They saw Tearju, who tried to raise me as a person, as an obstacle.
So what happened to her?
They probably chased her off, or worse.
What the hell?!
So they're the reason you're like this?!
Someone's gotta make them pay!
Calm down.
Not long after that, the king of Deviluke united the galaxy for the first time,
throwing their plans into the gutter.
Their entire organization collapsed amid the war's chaotic aftermath.
It doesn't exist anymore.
It's all in the past now.
But if Tearju had raised you,
you might've lived your life differently!
He's so strange.
He knows that I'm after his life,
and yet he gets angry for my sake and encourages me.
I'm even stranger, though.
Why do I feel so safe by the side of my target?
If only I could feel this warmth with my soul...
Do you know the answer, Tear?
We shouldn't do this!
Let's go back, Momo-san!
Why?
It's going to look like we don't trust Yami-san...
But you opened the door on me without hesitating at all!
So you don't mind leaving them alone?
Aren't you aware of Rito-san's bad sleeping habits?
Once that starts up, even Yami-san might...
Thanks for the meal!
...not be able to resist!
Rito-san's amazing when he's asleep!
Momo-san, are you speaking from experience?
I think Yami-san's more composed than that.
Then we have nothing to lose by checking on them.
I can't! I can't let her go!
Mikan-san, not my tail!
I-I can't keep quiet!
What?
No, it's nothing.
I almost told him that I wanted him to embrace me...
What's wrong with me?
My hand's free!
Thank goodness!
It wore off quicker than I expected!
One less thing to worry about!
Are you that happy to get away from me?
Of course! Now we can move free—
Stupid.
It's gotten late, so I'll read the rest tomorrow.
Come on, read more!
Watch it. I don't read to selfish little girls.
Then stay with me tomorrow all day long, okay?
Okay, I promise.
Good night, Tear.
You're so sweet.
Good night.
Find anything?
It looks like she's been in contact with someone for a week now.
But the security's too tough. I can't find out anything else.
So she's being cautious of us.
In that case, it's clear who she's contacted.
Who is it, Master?
Yesterday was such a pain.
When did I fall asleep anyway?
Mikan and Momo looked like they didn't get any sleep...
And Yami was gone by the time I woke up.
I hope she was able to sleep well.
Rito!
Did you hear?
I'm Tearju Lunatique.
Tearju?!
Let's end here for today. Next—
Excuse me, Tearju-sensei!
I have a question!
Are you single?
I am, but—
Is there anyone you like?!
What are your three sizes?!
When's your birthday?
I...
Boys! Stop bothering the teacher!
Yeah!
It's sexual harassment!
I won't allow anything improper!
U-Um...
Everyone, please calm down. I don't...
Are you okay, Sensei?
Y-Yes. That didn't hurt.
Sensei!
Pull yourself together!
A blonde klutz with glasses and huge boobs...
Don't categorize our teacher like that!
Hey...
Why did we get a new teacher all of a sudden?
I was so surprised when I saw her!
She totally looks like Yami-chan, doesn't she?
I think so too!
She's like an adult version of Golden Darkness.
Her personality's completely different though.
Well, I don't think it's that surprising.
There are plenty of people out there with look-alikes.
What really surprised me were those jugs!
Yeah, they were huge! It's not fair!
I like Yami-Yami's small and pretty ones,
but I wouldn't mind getting a handful of Sensei's at least once!
Rito-san!
Oshizu-chan?
Aren't you going to meet Tearju-sensei?
What?
You didn't know?
She's the new teacher for Rito-san's class.
Mikado-sensei told me how special she is to you.
I would've realized it even if she hadn't said anything.
Momo...
If I were that easy to move, I wouldn't be called Golden Darkness.
Oh, I found her!
It's the smaller Yami-Yami!
They really do look alike!
What are you and Momo-chi talking about?
I sense great potential in your boobs, Momo-chi!
Momioka-san, you're embarrassing me.
Your innocence is so cute.
Should I teach you some mature tricks?
If you refined your techniques, you could lead a whole harem of boys by the nose!
Why would I do something like that?
Who is this girl?! She's good!
Want me to grope you, Yami-Yami?
Thanks, but no thanks.
Wait, we're not done!
So you called Tearju here?
Yeah. I told you I'd look into it.
But how did you find her?
With the right qualifications,
getting the information you want is simple.
This is from when Tear and I were in school.
We were about 14 at the time.
Is this really you, Mikado-sensei?
You're so cute!
Tear's always been smart, but she's so clumsy that it's hard to leave her alone.
That's why I was really worried when she told me that
she'd been recruited by some suspicious research facility.
It wasn't much of a surprise though.
I'm coming!
Long time no see, Tear.
Is that you, Mikado?
It's so nice to see you!
It really has been a long time!
Come in, come in!
I'm not here just to see my old friend.
I'm here because of Eve.
Do you know how she's doing right now?
I heard she works as an assassin.
It's all because I left her behind.
It isn't your fault.
And she isn't an assassin anymore.
Finally seeing her again brought back so many memories.
She's still as awkward as I remember.
She hasn't talked with Yami-chan yet.
But I guess she doesn't know how to act.
That's something those two really have in common.
Tearju-sensei!
My glasses...
I'm sorry.
You're...
Sensei...
Please...
Please meet with Yami!
Yami told me everything!
She told me how important you are to her.
I'm sure she'd be happy to see you!
Oh, Yami is...
I spoke with Mikado. "Yami" is her current name, right?
Thank you for taking care of her.
You must be Yuuki Rito-kun.
I want to see her too.
I want to live with her again.
That's why I came all this way.
Mikado helped me a lot too.
But now that I'm here, I can't help but hesitate.
It's because I left her behind that she...
Sensei...
Tearju-sensei!
Principal!
How was your first day as a teacher?
I'm still getting the hang of things, but I'll do my best!
Very good.
Mikado-sensei recommended you, so I have high expectations.
Teachers must always set a good example for their students.
I see you're setting a fine example with your generous bosom!
So soft, bouncy, and...
I'm on fire!
Lead me too! Lead me with your amazing body!
Sensei, run!
Why are we running? He's the principal!
Yeah, but he's also the greatest danger within the school!
Rito-san...
and Tearju-sensei?
Oh, Rito! What's up?
The principal's chasing us! Help!
Okay!
There.
Why did you use Pyon-pyon Warp-kun?!
It can't warp clothes!
It's okay! I fixed it!
Really? I'm trusting you here!
Yuuki-kun, I can't run for very long!
Huh? I can feel something massive and soft above me...
These are...
No way!
No...
I'm sorry, Sensei!
Damn it, Lala! You said you had fixed it, so why are we naked?!
When did you take my clothes off?
I-I don't really know what to do, and we've only just met so... Um...
She's starting to jump to conclusions!
N-No! I-I can explain!
I can explai—
Shut up.
Just get away from her and put on some clothes already.
Y-Yami!
Eve...
What's a "way to live"?