Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
That tickles, Mikado-sensei.
Really?
You have to keep your body clean.
All girls need to do so after a certain age, Oshizu-chan.
I see you've gotten used to your body.
You should be able to fall in love without any problems now.
You really think so?
Well, it's all thanks to you that I can live again even though I'm a ghost.
I'm very grateful.
Oh, I'm very grateful too.
Thanks to you, I was able to gather some data on a precious rare thought entity.
A thought... entity?
An entity of mental energy born from creatures that surpass a certain level of intelligence.
In layman's terms, creatures like you, Oshizu-chan.
Ghosts are being unveiled by cutting edge science in space too.
As energy entities, it's possible for you to vanish if you're mentally exhausted.
So don't do anything too crazy, okay?
I'll be fine! I don't have any problems either!
That's right.
You don't suffer from any problems like that.
You pulled another all-nighter doing a battle drill, Master?
You should let yourself get a good night's sleep once in a while.
I need to polish my skills.
Living in tranquility has made me rusty.
Besides, have you ever seen me sleep in this bed even once after I picked you up from that junkyard?
W-Well, no. That's why I'm telling you to.
Also, Luna...
Yes?
Stop calling me "Master".
Call me "Yami-chan" from now on.
When is the last time I got a good night's sleep?
I can't remember my past very well.
I've never even tried to recall it before.
I'm able to recall every single detail since that time, though.
Kujou-senpai, thank you very much for taking care of Mikan the other day!
It's nothing to thank me for.
I just did what I thought was right.
I should go.
We don't want Saki-sama to see us chatting.
Okay.
I'm glad you got to thank her.
And thank you for calling her out for me.
So, what do you think of Kujou-san?
What do you mean?
What's that?
That thing couldn't be...
Yami, don't touch that!
Yuuki-kun? Yami-chan?
W-What are you two...
D-Don't start assuming things, Sairenji, Kotegawa!
I can explain!
My sister's invention malfunctioned, and now their hands are stuck together.
How did that happen?!
Celine-san brought this here.
This is so interesting!
So there's no way to separate you two?
Well, our hands are like powerful magnets right now...
I guess we've got no choice.
Shall we cut ourselves free?
No!
Calm down, Yami-chan!
Y-Yeah, just give it some time!
The magnetism will wear off eventually.
That means I have to hold hands with you for the time being.
How unpleasant.
H-Hey, where are we going?
I'm going to buy taiyaki.
I always buy some after school.
I'm going with them!
You're so lucky, Yami-chan...
How shameless.
I'm going too!
Let's go, Mea!
Sorry, Nana-chan.
It looks like fun, but I've already got plans for today.
Oh...
I'll see you tomorrow, then!
Yeah!
Walking while holding hands is so embarrassing...
I'm not exactly enjoying myself either.
I see...
Hey there, Yami-chan!
Brought your boyfriend with you today?
N-No! I'm not—
The usual, please.
Coming right up!
Damn, holding hands already!
Doesn't get much more lovey-dovey than that!
Good luck with your boyfriend!
If you dare eat my taiyaki, I'll kill you.
I get it.
They're so carefree...
Sticky Sticky Glue-kun...
I completely forgot about that invention.
Rito-san, everyone's staring!
Th-That's out of my hands!
If I used that invention, I could...
You know, I'm surprised Mea-san didn't come with us.
Knowing her, I thought she'd tag along for sure.
I'm concerned.
But with Yami-san stuck to Rito-san like that, I can't take my eyes off them.
Yeah... Yup...
Okay, thanks.
Mikan invited you over to our place for dinner.
She sounded really excited.
Thank you very much.
By the way, what was your childhood like?
Please don't get ahead of yourself.
I'd never reveal something like that to my target.
I guess you have a point...
I need to save some space in my stomach for Mikan's cooking.
Help me eat these.
Yami-san, you've mastered the chopping technique I taught you!
Next.
You're chopping this one perfectly too!
You know how to peel, too?
I underwent special training.
You're amazing, Yami-san!
Just being able to help you makes me happy.
They're getting along so well!
Yami-san doesn't seem to mind either.
Thanks for the meal!
Sorry for making you help, Yami-chan!
Don't be.
Just sit back and relax until the effect wears off.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Maybe I should...
Wait, why would I ever do that?!
Here.
I'll kill you if you look.
Mikan.
What's up, Yami-san?
I'd like to take a shower.
You want to... shower?
With Rito by your side?
That cannot be avoided.
Can't you go a day without taking a shower?
Taking a shower is part of my daily routine.
And you stink of sweat, so please wash yourself thoroughly.
Of course...
No! Not my face again! Anywhere but there!
What a wonderful idea! Please allow me to help you!
No, you can't, Momo!
I...
I'll go with them.
You will?
Yeah. I'll go to keep an eye on them.
Momo's too forgiving when it comes to Rito.
Is that okay with you, Yami?
Yes.
Don't I get a say in this?!
How are we going to get out of our clothes?
I'll cut them.
I'll repair them later using my Trans ability.
Don't even think about peeking, Rito!
My eyes are covered, but I can still smell them!
I'll wash your back for you.
Why did it have to end up like this?
I'm sorry about this, Princess Nana.
Just call me Nana!
All done.
Hey, I'm not washing you too.
I know!
Just hand me the showerhead...
Here.
What am I touching?
That's my... tail...
Sorry!
I despise perverts!
No way...
Get away from me!
What are they doing in there?
What's wrong, Nana?
N-Nothing.
You laid down mattresses for them in here, Mikan-san?
Yeah, Yami-san said they'd feel too cramped in a bed.
Thank you very much, Mikan.
It was no problem.
Lala-san said the effects will wear off by morning.
Sleep tight! Good night!
Aren't you worried?
If something happens, we won't be able to make it in time from the second floor.
He'll be fine.
He's sleeping with Yami-san, not you.
She's more wary of me than the greatest assassin in space...
Good night!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Is that Mea-san?
She looks just like a normal girl.
She doesn't seem scary at all.
This might be my chance!
I'll turn ethereal
and take a look inside her mind.
That way, I can find out what kind of a person she is!
I can't believe I'll be sleeping next to Yami.
My heart was racing when I slept next to Lala too...
But with Yami, it's for a different reason.
And my hand can't shake off that sensation...
Are you thinking of something lewd?
The next time you do something weird, I'll kill you on the spot.
I'm not gonna do anything!
Are you having trouble falling asleep too?
I can't even remember the last time I was able to be at ease and sleep soundly.
I simply close my eyes and let my body rest.
I don't enter deep sleep.
If you did, you wouldn't be able to tell if you're being targeted, right?
Yes. If I'm not alert at all times, I could lose my life in the blink of an eye.
So that's the kind of world you come from...
Looking back, when we first met...
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
For what you did in the bathroom?
I'm sorry about that too, but...
I've been so pretentious with you time after time.
Sure, I intended to give you serious advice, but still...
I must've come off as an oblivious nobody who thinks he knows everything.
So... I'm really sorry.
Professor Tearju Lunatique.
Huh?
Holding your hand all day made me think about her.
Let's...
talk about the past for a while.
Is this the inside of Mea-san's mind?
Lick me more, Senpai!
I love the way you lick me!
What the heck is this?!
Is this what goes through her mind?!
I need to dive even deeper!
If I could just find something related to her true feelings...
What's that?
You're lookin' for Golden Darkness, huh?
Plan on taking the bounty for yourself, little lady?
We do know where she is,
but we're not kind enough to tell you for free.
We might be willing to tell you in exchange for certain services, though.
'Kay.
She's... just like Yami-san!
Wow. You guys were no fun at all.
But I know where Yami-oneechan is now.
She's on Earth.
Time to put aside my bounty hunter mask.
We're going there, aren't we, Master?
Of course.
Her master?
The one Yami-san and Momo-san are looking for?
If I find out who it is, I—
What?
You should stop, Murasame-senpai.
You're the one helping Dr. Mikado, right?
A thought entity, huh?
It's my first time seeing one.
What you're doing is similar to my Psycho Dive.
But you probably shouldn't stay inside me any longer.
What is this?!
The darkness...
is pulling me down!
You're lucky, Murasame-senpai.
If you stayed inside me just a moment longer,
you might've been destroyed.
Just what are you?!
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
Memories for tomorrow.