As you wish, Saki-sama.
Yes.
Please leave this matter to me.
Enjoy your time with your father.
Looks like today is going to be hot.
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Rito-san, it's already morning...
That isn't ice cream you're licking...
We can't do that just yet.
Not until you're willing.
You sure took control last night.
Next...
What's next?
It's a little too late to hide now!
She barged in really early this time.
I can't keep taking Mikan-san so lightly.
Just when I thought Momo-san was starting to be more prudent...
I told him that I didn't want to go out with him...
Is Momo-san really in love with Rito?
I guess she wouldn't be sneaking into his bed every night if she wasn't.
I thought she was just playing some dumb prank,
but if there are actually
feelings behind her actions...
And if Rito just happened to be in the mood once...
Wh-What should I do?
W-Wait! Why am I even worrying about this in the first place?
Even if it puts a strain on everyone's relationship, it's Rito's problem!
What's wrong with me?
I never used to worry so much.
When did I become so uptight?
Is it because of Momo-san?
No, that doesn't explain anything...
Y-Yuuki-san is glaring at me!
Did I make a mistake somewhere?
I'll become the greatest idol ever and melt your heart!
I'll have to keep a close eye on her now.
Yuuki-kun is already so shameless.
She might corrupt him even more.
Why do I have to keep my eye on them, anyway?
I've already got my work cut out for me on the discipline committee.
Mom? Onii-chan?
Why are you two crying?
Oh, Yui-chan, this drama could make anyone cry!
A person's first love really is the most special one!
Make sure you treasure Yuuki!
What does Yuuki-kun have to do with this?!
Be safe!
See you later, Mikan-chan!
Bye-bye!
It's so hot!
My goodness! They never stop going on about Yuuki!
There's nothing special about him.
Kittens always calm me down at times like this.
Kotegawa-san?
S-Sairenji-san?
What are you doing here?
Oh, just killing time.
I can't tell her about my
recent obsession with kittens...
Well, since you're free,
would you like to hang out?
Um...
I picked that up already, and that...
Oh, yeah. A toothbrush for Rito.
Wait, yesterday...
Rito-san, your old toothbrush looked worn-out, so I bought you a new one.
Oh, thanks!
I'm surprised you noticed.
I'm always watching you closely.
Wh-Why am I getting upset?
It's nice that she's so thoughtful!
I'll help you make dinner!
This is great!
It's nowhere near as good as
Mikan-san's cooking though.
She's been helping with the housework
ever since she transferred to Sainan High.
She pays a lot of attention to
what Rito likes and dislikes too.
It does make my work easier...
But still...
It feels like I don't belong.
Oh... So that's why...
I've been so uptight.
Huh? What's going on?
Everything is...
Uh-oh...
I haven't found such a good game in a long time.
I should hurry home and—
Huh? Is that Mikan-san?
Are you all right?
Huh? Isn't she...
Looks like the heat got the better of you.
You should rest and cool down for a while.
My home's close by.
Welcome!
Our Meow-Meow Campaign is still in session, meow!
Hi, Mio!
Meow?
Oh, Haruna!
I don't see you together with Kotegawa-san very often!
Take your time and relax, meow!
O-Okay...
Th-This is quite an unusual shop.
Sorry! I kinda invited you on a whim.
It has quite a unique atmosphere, doesn't it?
Hey there, Yui, Haruna!
Risa!
Don't scare me like that!
Mio told me I'd be able to
find an unusual duo here.
But you know, we rarely get out this early.
You must be pretty lonely to be
coming here for tea by yourselves.
It's not like I can talk, though!
I-It'd be shameless for students to hang out with the opposite sex!
Here we go!
Everything's shameless to you.
That reminds me, I came here on a date with Yuuki one time.
W-With Yuuki-kun?!
Kujou
This cold shower feels so nice.
Feeling any better?
Y-Yes, I'm feeling a lot better. Thank you!
Good. I'm glad to hear that.
Today's very hot, after all.
I won't take long, so please wait for me.
Sure.
She's so pretty...
The dryer's over there.
Oh, thanks.
She has this aloofness about her.
It kinda reminds me of Yami-san...
The breeze feels great!
This spot's quite drafty.
Rest here while the sun's strong.
Sorry about all of this.
Um...
I'm Kujou Rin.
I'm Yuuki Mikan.
I'm Yuuki Rito's...
...little sister, right?
I remember you.
Kujou Rin? Isn't she...
You weren't with Tenjouin-san
and the others today?
Saki-sama had a lunch
appointment with her father,
so both Aya and I have the day off.
Your feet...
You can sit more comfortably.
But...
U-Um, then excuse me.
You're very proper.
You're a far cry from your brother.
We've refused his advances, but he insists on sexually harassing Saki-sama and me.
Just being around him is dangerous.
And just the other day, he tripped and groped my breasts.
It might've been an accident,
but it's still not easy to forgive.
I-I'm sorry. That has nothing
to do with his little sister.
It's okay. I know you're telling the truth.
How does he behave at home?
My brother's hopeless.
He can't do anything without me around.
That might've changed recently, though.
I might not be needed there anymore.
Did... something happen?
Y-You went on a date with Yuuki-kun?
I invited him out as thanks for
saving me from some skirt chaser.
He came straight to my place that night.
Yuuki, we can't...
You're the one who invited me, Momioka.
Yeah, but I...
Yuuki's got some skills, you know.
Sk-Skills?!
He's a real beast too.
A-A beast?!
Well, all guys are the same.
They can only think of how to get laid.
Yuuki's just a guy in the end too.
I see.
I'd say it's only right that
freeloaders help with the housework,
but at the same time, you feel like you don't belong there anymore.
Momo-san's better at striking up a conversation about gardening and games with him too.
They have a lot in common.
I don't really have a place there anymore.
You've got your mind set on him, don't you?
N-No, it's nothing like that!
I'm just concerned as his little sister!
If you ask me, he's nothing but a pervert.
He seems to be something
different for you, though.
Rito's...
...not like that.
Yuuki-kun isn't like other boys.
He might be shameless, but he wouldn't behave that rashly.
Sure, he's indecent every now and then,
but he doesn't do it on purpose.
Um...
I guess my joke went overboard, huh?
But damn, Yui!
You know Yuuki pretty well, don't you?
Not at all!
That's just what I thought when I checked up on him! My duties require me to!
Oh, really?
Yeah, it's not like that.
I just wanted to tell you.
Yuuki-kun's actually...
...always working very hard.
He always gives his all when
it comes to solving problems.
One time, he took me to the
pool on a dog day like this.
But we lost track of each other at one point.
I didn't even realize I was lost.
Mikan!
Rito?
I finally found you!
I told you not to leave my side!
I looked everywhere for you!
What if some bad guy took you away?
Stuff like that never happens!
You worry too much, Rito.
I'm not worrying too much.
The world's full of scary people!
Whoa, you're sweating bullets.
Were you that worried about me?
Don't be stupid. I just took a dip in the pool!
I could tell from how drenched Rito was that he had been desperately looking for me.
I brushed him off as being silly,
but deep down, I was really happy.
She's talking about their days before I showed up.
You can see his good and bad points better than anyone else.
It's similar to my relationship
with Saki-sama and Aya.
You and Yuuki Rito must see
each other as irreplaceable.
As long as you share that bond,
don't you think that no one can ever
hope to change your place in his life?
You're Yuuki Mikan, after all.
That made me happy.
You know how sincere Yuuki-kun is too.
Y-Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, I do know.
He's shameless, but sincere.
He's pathetic, but dependable.
He's different from other boys.
He's special.
Special?
When did I start thinking of him that way?
I'm... shameless.
Thank you so much for all your help.
I'll be fine from here on.
You don't have to act tough.
I'll go with you a little further.
That won't be necessary, Kujou-senpai.
I'll walk her home from here.
Momo-san!
Let's go home together, Mikan-san!
Okay. Take care of Mikan.
Make sure she gets back to Yuuki Rito.
Of course!
So you can fly too, huh?
Yes. Onee-sama developed
those Half-Gravity Wings.
Were you listening to me talk to Rin-san?
Sorry. I was curious.
You know, Mikan-san, I really envy you.
Huh?
The other day, Rito-san told me...
Mikan is my one and only, dear little sister.
I consider her to be more than just my little sister.
Rito said that?
I can't help but envy you
after hearing Rito-san say that.
You've been together with him a lot longer than my sisters or I have.
You two share memories that we have no idea about too.
Those are bonds which I can never break, no matter how hard I try.
But...
I hope to become someone
Rito-san can call special one day.
I wish for that from the bottom of my heart.
Momo-san, you really are in lov—
Well, now we understand each other's feelings a bit better,
so let's sneak into his bed together tonight!
Why does it have to come to that?!
Mikan!
Rito? What's he doing here?
I told him earlier that
we'd be going home together.
Mikan!
Are you having any trouble walking?
How's your temperature? Are you okay?!
I-I'm fine! I'm feeling better now!
Really? You don't have to act tough, you know!
I'm not!
And keep your voice down.
You're embarrassing me!
This is just like when we went to the pool.
Wipe your face, my stupid brother.
How am I stupid?!
You just are.
They're putting on an act.
Come on, wipe face!
Anyway, Kujou Rin-san...
might be worth checking out.
Something wrong, Kotegawa?
No...
Wh-Why does he have to be my first love?!
What do you think you're doing?! Don't you have any shame?!
I'll never accept this!
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to randebu shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
Her True Face in the Darkness.