Thanks, Momo.
You saved me.
Oh, don't mention it.
I just happened to see the whole thing happen.
My goodness. Onee-sama's inventions always cause so much trouble.
But they can also...
I-It's been so long.
I'm glad to see you're doing well, Eve.
I'm Golden Darkness now, or Yami-chan.
I'm no longer the person you once knew.
R-Right.
Y-You're mad at me, aren't you?
For leaving you behind.
The organization was going to eliminate me that day.
I planned to take you
with me and run away.
But they were one step ahead of me.
Eve!
The best I could do was save my own life.
While wandering from planet to planet,
I learned that the organization was
destroyed and started looking for you.
But I couldn't find you.
The rumors of Golden Darkness, who was feared among those in the underworld, reached me a few years later.
I knew right away that it had to be you,
but I didn't want to believe it.
You were so cheerful and kind.
I can't even begin to imagine how much despair you've endured to end up living that way.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Things like that won't make a difference.
Your apologies won't give me a fresh start in life,
nor do I intend to shun my identity as Golden Darkness.
Only one thing is on my mind right now:
I am glad to see you're alive.
That's all that matters to me, Tear.
Oh, she's leaving.
Yami-san's so reserved.
She should've hugged her or something.
You can't ask for too much.
Each of them has a sense of
guilt toward the other.
Mending a broken relationship isn't so simple.
But eventually,
even if it takes some time...
they'll be back to how they used to be.
Mea!
I heard my older sister's class has
a new teacher who looks just like Yami!
Wanna go see her later?
Yeah, sure.
I heard she's got huge boobs, too.
Aren't you interested?!
Tearju Lunatique.
Golden Darkness has denied her life as a weapon
and foolishly tried to live as a human being.
Wow!
How can I get boobs like that?
Let's go, Nana-chan.
Huh? Wh-What's wrong, Mea?
I wanted to talk to her!
That girl was...
Hey, Mea!
Where did she go?
Hey there, Yami!
Have you seen Mea?
No.
Oh...
Did something happen to Kurosaki Mea?
Nah.
It's not that something happened.
Nana, is Mea your friend?
Being with my friend,
or rather, being with Mikan,
makes me feel alive.
You're...
Hey, have you seen a girl named Kurosaki Mea around here?
Kurosaki?
She has red hair.
No, I haven't seen her.
I see.
Mea!
Where've you been?
I was using the bathroom.
Oh.
Did something happen?
No.
What's wrong, Nana-chan?
You're acting weird.
I see.
That really is a bit worrying.
Yeah, she's acting a little different from the last time she was feeling down.
Maybe she's worrying about
something and keeping it to herself.
Should I wait until Mea opens up to me about it?
It might be something she'd rather not talk about in school.
Thank you so much.
It's no problem.
You're Lala-san's little sister, right?
Yeah. I'm surprised you knew.
The girl you were looking for earlier...
Oh, you mean Mea?
Is she your friend?
Yeah, she is.
I see.
Please be a good friend to Mea-san.
I'm home!
Sairenji?
Oh, hello.
What's going on?
Nothing much.
What are you doing, Nana?
Shut up.
It's none of your business.
Nana, Dad said it's okay!
Really? Awesome!
Hey!
Hello!
Sorry about the surprise visit.
I don't mind.
I'm not sure what's going on,
but I'm always up for having some fun.
Look forward to it.
Nana-chan is a good girl, isn't she?
She's always so lively.
Yeah!
Is this really my room?
Looks nice, doesn't it?
Haruna chose the furniture,
and I did the decorating.
Being in a room with bright colors will help you feel better.
It's meant to cheer you up.
But all of this must have been so expensive...
It's fine! Don't sweat it!
I'm a princess, you know.
What are you talking about?
I heard you got six months' worth of
allowance in advance from Gid-sama.
Keep your big mouth shut, Peke!
Nana-chan, where's that thing?
Oh, right.
It didn't turn out too well...
But Mea's new room wouldn't
be complete without it!
It may look poorly done
since Nana isn't very skilled,
but she made it with lots of love!
S-Sis!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Nana-chan.
Thank you.
That's a relief.
You've been acting strangely lately.
Like something's been troubling you.
Have I?
But this cheered you up.
Mea...
Yeah...
So even you don't know about Mea-san or her master, Tearju-sensei?
That's correct.
I don't know the details of every project that was ongoing back when I was in the organization.
But I think it's safe to say that Kurosaki Mea
is a second generation Trans weapon that was based on Yami-chan's development data.
Mass production of Trans weapons...
That was supposedly the
organization's ultimate objective.
As for her master, I can only speculate at this point.
It could be one of the researchers who survived,
or it could be...
I'm sorry. I haven't been very helpful, have I?
Oh no, just having you here is reassuring.
So please take these.
What are those?
Dazzle seeds.
When you throw them on the ground, they'll grow rapidly,
coil around your opponent's body, and restrict their movement.
It was improved to send me
a signal as soon as it sprouts,
so I'll come right away
if anything happens.
Mea's master might try
to do something to you,
so please hold on to them
to be on the safe side.
Thank you.
I'm so happy, Momo-chan.
That girl managed to make friends with someone as dependable as you.
Yami-san is the one who asked me to do this.
She did?
Take good care of Tear.
She really needs to be
more honest with her feelings.
I see.
So clones can have completely
different personalities...
I mean, just look at
Tearju-sensei and Yami-san.
Yeah...
And their busts...
Around that time, Tearju-sensei should've been the same age as Yami-san and I are now.
Environmental factors must have played a big role there,
even though they have the same genome.
I think you shouldn't mention that to Yami.
Well, enough of that.
Don't you think adding Tearju-sensei and Yami-san to your harem
would spice things up?
Yuuki-kun...
Do you want me to wash your body?
If Tear's doing it, then I will too.
Don't tell your classmates about this, okay?
Wh-What...
What are you talking about?!
I'm just kidding!
Tearju-sensei!
Oh, Kokegawa-san!
You were still at school?
Yes. I had a discipline committee meeting.
And...
my name is Kotegawa.
Oh!
I-I'm so sorry!
Sensei, let me know if the boys do anything shameless to you, okay?
Especially Yuuki-kun!
You need to be really careful around him!
Okay.
Shameless things? I wonder what she meant.
Being a teacher is harder than I thought.
Just remembering the students'
names is a lot of work.
At last...
we can talk without being interrupted.
Do you have a moment, Doctor?
Of course.
I've been meaning to talk to you too, Mea-san.
Really? That's a surprise.
What did you want to talk to me about?
This is...
Don't get any closer to Tearju-sensei!
If you have something to say, do it from there!
I'm constricting your
clothes with my willpower.
If you try to break free,
your clothes will rip and
you'll be embarrassed!
I'm the only person who's been in direct contact with the darkness inside Mea-san's mind.
She's a lot more dangerous than everyone else thinks.
As Mikado-sensei's assistant, I have a duty to protect Tearju-sensei!
They really ripped!
I have to know, Murasame-senpai,
did you really think that was enough to make me take orders from you?
I-If that's how it's gonna be, I'll bind
your actual body without holding back!
It's been so long since
I had to deal with an enemy!
How wonderful!
Stop, both of you!
Sensei?
What's wrong, Momo?
Tearju-sensei!
No...
Don't look!
What the hell happened here?!
The seeds sprouted when I fell over!
Is she as clumsy as Rito-san?!
Don't suck on it!
Celine!
I'll untie the ivy!
What an amusing sight!
Mea!
Why are you here?
Don't get the wrong idea, Senpai.
I just wanted to check out
what kind of person Tearju is.
It was Murasame-senpai
who started the fight.
"Don't show any mercy to your enemies."
That's what Master Nemesis taught me.
Master Nemesis?
I remember hearing that name.
Project Nemesis!
It ran alongside Project Eve, which gave birth to Yami-chan and you.
It was a completely separate Trans project.
But I heard that the development failed and the project was shelved.
Is your master...
That's right.
Master Nemesis is a Trans weapon
who was born from Project Nemesis.
The first thing I remember seeing is a destroyed research facility,
and a broken biocapsule.
I walked through the debris, unaware of who I was or why I was born.
That's when I met that person.
Master taught me how to live as a Trans weapon.
How to use my power, things about Yami-oneechan...
It's thanks to Master's guidance that I am who I am today.
Master is the only person who truly understands Yami-oneechan and me. The only one who can guide us,
because we're all weapons.
Tearju, you cut into our relationship.
Do you still think Yami-oneechan should live as a human being?
Yes, I do.
And I hope you live as one too.
If you're Yami-chan's little sister,
you're a little sister to me too.
What are you talking about?!
That's stupid.
I told you that I'm a weapon!
If Master gives the order, I can wipe you out in an instant!
You're living in this town as a human being.
Yami-chan is too, isn't she?
Th-That's only because
I was ordered to by Master,
not because I wanted to.
We don't truly belong here.
Mea...
If you were to leave this town,
I think that would make Nana very sad.
Nana-chan?
Yami too.
You can change.
You keep insisting you're just a weapon,
but you have a heart.
I want to build a heartfelt friendship with you.
You see, I'm the shy type
and I don't have many friends.
Mea...
What about you, Senpai?
If you lick every part of my body,
I might give what you said some thought.
Rito-san, go ahead and do it!
Yuuki-kun, if that's what it takes for her to understand, do it!
I can't!
And Mea! Don't ask me to
do something like that out of nowhere!
I already knew you couldn't do it.
I've figured out that you aren't someone who could.
So you see, hearts aren't so easy to sway.
That's why Momo-chan's having such a hard time with you, Senpai.
So, I'm going to continue to
follow my Master's teachings.
If you're okay with that,
then stay friends with me,
Senpai, Momo-chan,
and you too, Tearju-sensei.
"Hearts aren't so easy to sway," huh?
So, Mea-san,
even though you claim to be a weapon,
you still acknowledge the existence of a heart.
Um...
H-Help me too, please.
Oh.
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to randebu shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
A maiden's feelings.