Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
My love, this impulse, can't be stopped
tomaranai shoudou aijou
You know I'm being serious here
you know honki de iku yo
Let's set this great project into motion
sokkou go on juuyou just project
It doesn't matter how, just make it work
houhou junjo honto dou de mo ii no
Instincts cause the trouble
honnou de torabu tte
It's alright even if I can't be your only one
ne kimi no only one ja naku tatte it's all right
Let's all be happy together
minna de happy ni narou yo
Our love will bloom into
uketomete kureru kono koi wa
The greatest scandal in the galaxy
ginga no saikyou no scandal
There's just one target and that's you
tatta hitori no target sore wa sou kimi desu
Laugh by my side like that forever
soba de eien ni sou yatte waratteite
Please believe in me
shinjite ne watashi wo
Because I'll lead you to paradise
ima kimi ni ageru yo paradise
Jump into the garden of love
tobikonde ai no sono he
Let's dream the best of dreams together
saikou no yume wo issho ni mimasho
Guess what, Master!
I made my very first friend today!
Isn't that wonderful?
I hope your lax lifestyle didn't cause you to forget your true goal.
Of course not!
How could I ever forget?
I need to return Yami-oneechan to her old self.
Right?
Indeed.
Golden Darkness is of no use to me in her present state.
It's essential that she returns to how she is meant to be.
There is but one way to achieve that.
The murder of Yuuki Rito by Golden Darkness herself.
You're kidding...
Is that really what they want?
Yes. I can't think of anything else.
The enemy is definitely out to provoke Yami-san.
They clearly want her to return to being the assassin she once was.
But who? And why?
I don't know.
We don't know anything about Yami-san's past.
I'm only worried that
the enemy might actually succeed at provoking her into switching sides.
Would Yami...
Would Yami really try to kill me?
You really think she'd do it?
Well, I don't think she would the way she is now.
Why don't we cheer up over some coffee?
Excuse the intrusion, Yuuki Rito.
Yami?! Why are you holding a knife?!
Is she really going to try to kill me?
Yami-san!
I brought you an apron.
Here.
Mikan-san, what's Yami-san doing here?
Oh, I promised her before that she could stay over,
so I thought I'd use this chance to teach her about how we cook on Earth.
When I asked Mikan about Earthling culture,
she suggested that I start with cooking.
Cooking?
All right, let's start by chopping the veggies up!
Okay.
What do you think, Momo?
I don't know what to make of this.
Just make sure you don't let your guard down.
You mustn't forget that she's a legendary assassin.
Excuse me. I'm not used to this and my hand slipped.
Seriously?!
You have to grip it properly, Yami-san!
Let me show you first!
Mikan looks like she's having fun.
Doing stuff with your friends is always fun.
By the way, I managed to make a friend at school.
What? Already?!
That was quick!
She thinks it's awesome how I'm able to get along with animals.
I see.
Good for you, Nana.
I'll introduce her to you all when I get a chance.
Not you though, Rito.
You're a beast.
Looks like it was a good idea for them to transfer to Sainan High.
Yes, it does.
You should transfer too!
You could learn a lot about Earth's culture there.
I'm sure you'd have lots of fun.
Really?
Nice going, Mikan-san!
For the sake of Rito-san's well-being, I want to have her in my sight at all times!
Even Mikan-san thinks you should transfer. Why not just do it?
There's still room in my class.
Yes...
Becoming a student there would give me more chances to target Yuuki Rito too.
It backfired!
Oh, come on, Yami-san.
Okay, it's ready!
This tastes great, Yami-chan!
I just did as Mikan instructed me.
Celine-chan, do you like it too?
Why did she put taiyaki in my miso soup?
Does she really expect me to eat this?!
She'll kill me if I don't!
Thanks for the meal!
Rito-san, hold it in!
Uh, I've gotta run to the convenience store.
I just realized I'm out of facial cream.
Pick up the kind of milk we usually get too!
Sure thing.
Rito-san, let me tag along.
Momo-san's back to clinging onto Rito.
This is the facial cream you use, right?
Yeah...
Don't worry.
If push comes to shove, I'll protect you.
I'll risk my life to do so.
Momo...
I can't just let my dear Rito-san die.
I need you for my harem plan.
Don't just say "harem" in public like that!
Are you really serious about that?
Of course!
It's the perfect solution to a lot of our problems,
including the issue of who'll inherit Deviluke's throne.
But I'm—
Remember what I told you? The king is free to have as many concubines as he desires.
And my sister isn't the only one whose happiness depends on you.
Just think of...
I wonder what Yuuki-kun's doing right now.
Yet another week of Yuuki-kun causing me nothing but trouble.
Why do I have to put up with him?
What are you grinning about, Onii-chan?
Huh?
Oh, nothing. I was just thinking that Yuuki is all you seem to talk about.
You're surrounded by girls who love you,
though some of us may feel more strongly about you than others.
You could have us all to yourself, you know.
Even Yami-san!
That's insane!
You have nothing to worry about.
I'll deal with any obstacle that gets in your way.
Nothing smells better than a bouquet of girls.
I'm back.
Yami-san is staying in Mikan-san's room?
I need to wash my face.
Why does Momo have to be so enthusiastic about this?
Learn to knock, perv!
Sorry!
Jeez...
The day's finally over.
Oh, but the night is just beginning.
Mikan-san will come barging in if you make too much noise.
I'm only here as your bodyguard tonight.
There's a chance that Yami-san will try to attack you during the night.
H-Hey! You're supposed to be my bodyguard, right?!
That's right. Nothing but a bodyguard.
So please don't worry about me,
and sleep tight.
Rito-san...
He still won't give in?
Does he still see me as a kid?
After all the effort I put into fixing my hair to look more mature?
Well... that won't be enough to stop me!
Yami?!
Can we talk?
Did she call me out here to kill me?
Today...
Mikan taught me how to cook.
When you cook, you should think about who it is that you're cooking for.
That's the most important part about making delicious food.
I couldn't really understand what she meant.
Chopping vegetables with a knife while thinking of someone...
Is that really...
any different from chopping up an enemy with my transformation ability?
Momo!
I won't let you lay a finger on Rito-san!
I bet you let some shady person talk you into killing him,
but I won't let you do it!
Your intent to kill is strong.
I feel like I'm finally seeing your true side,
Princess Momo.
But you're misunderstanding me.
When I kill Yuuki Rito, it will be at my own discretion.
I have no intention of letting someone else sway me.
Especially not someone shady.
But just now—
I merely wished to ask him something.
Yuuki Rito.
Was the taiyaki miso soup that I made especially for you delicious?
I'm curious.
I put quite a bit of effort into making it, after all.
I-It was a l-little on the sweet side, but...
It was delicious... I guess.
Is that... so?
Now I feel assured.
Good night.
What the hell?
Does she...
Does she like Rito-san more than I thought?
You're creeping me out.
For a while now,
I've been trying to forget my past and start a new life.
I don't get it.
I...
Hello, my big sister Yami.
"Big sister"?
Yeah.
Master told me that you're the only family I have.
So...
I'll do my best to help you complete your mission to kill Yuuki Rito-senpai!
What else is family for?
Doesn't that sound wonderful?
You and I... are family?
Yup!
I'm a murder weapon that was created...
based on your development data!
This is all the proof you should need.
I'll help out any way I can, so let's do our best to kill Yuuki Rito-senpai!
Then we can return to space together!
I'm sure that'd make Master really happy.
Oh, class is starting!
Onee-chan, let's go!
What's up, Mea?
You look pretty happy.
Did something good happen?
You could say that.
I see!
By the way, I heard from a few people in class that you're a transfer student too. Is it true?
Yeah, I came here about a month ago.
But I'm not good at making friends, so I couldn't really fit in.
So...
That makes you my first friend, Nana-chan!
Really? You're making me blush.
I only knew my sister's friends from Earth.
You're actually the first friend I made on my own.
Kurosaki Mea. Like me, she's a a living weapon that was created during the fall of the 6th Galactic System.
If what she said is true, her "Master" must be the one who's pulling the strings from behind the scenes.
But the organization that created me should've been crushed by its enemy after the war.
Did someone survive?
I don't have enough data.
I can only watch and examine her behavior for now.
I doubt we could ever become close like those two.
Yami-san!
I love to read books!
Let's be friends!
You like taiyaki, right?
Don't you think I look like one?
The boys are all over you even though you just got here, Yami-san.
I think that applies to you more than it does to me, Princess Momo.
Oh, not at all.
Has anyone tried to approach you since then?
Just come to me if you think I can be of any assistance.
I can help you with not only battles, but with gathering intel too.
That sounds wonderful, Princess Momo.
But I don't trust you to that extent just yet.
Well, I guess you still don't know me as well as you do Onee-sama and Mikan-san.
Look! Momo-chan's talking with Yami-chan!
She must be worried since Yami-chan's so shy!
Momo's so young and pretty! She's like a real princess!
"Young and pretty," my ass.
They'd be so disappointed if they knew what Momo's really like.
Really?
You bet! She's always putting on an act.
She pretends to be a good girl, but who knows what she's really thinking about?
Be careful around her, Mea.
You know so much about her!
Well, yeah. We're always together since we're twin sisters and all.
Sisters... Always together...
That's wonderful!
Oh yeah! You're staying at Yuuki Rito-senpai's place, aren't you?
You heard about that, huh?
What kind of a person is he?
A beast!
He's a terrible pervert!
He's always sniffing our panties, groping our breasts, and grabbing our asses!
He's nothing but a perverted beast!
A beast...
Lala and Momo like him for some reason.
I have no idea why.
He's that worthless?
Well, he can be kind every now and then.
Didn't you say he was worthless?
Y-Yeah, but I didn't mean completely! He's just...
What was I even trying to say?!
Are you looking for someone?
I'd like to talk to Yuuki Rito-senpai.
I saw him going up to the roof a little earlier.
The roof?
Thanks a lot, Senpai!
I wonder who she is.
I'm so tired.
I've been losing sleep lately because of Momo and Yami.
I'm supposed to become the next king of Deviluke,
assemble a harem, and make Lala, Haruna-chan, and all the others happy too?
This could turn into a horrible scandal if Kotegawa finds out.
You two get along so well.
She's such an honest child.
She probably takes after whoever's been raising her.
I'm sure she does.
By the way, how is she?
The transfer student Yami-chan.
Is she fitting in well?
Well, it's like she's built a wall around herself.
She's making it very difficult for anyone to talk to her.
I thought so.
She can be awkward at times.
You've known her before you came to Earth, right?
Sort of.
Assassins and witch doctors move around in the same circles.
Personally, I'm hoping she can continue to lead a peaceful life.
She's been through so much and only knows what it means to fight.
Please look after her, Momo-san.
Sure.
Yami-chan!
I heard you transferred in as a first-year student.
The uniform looks great on you!
What's wrong?
You seem down.
Unsettling as it is,
I'm struggling to understand myself at the moment.
Isn't that weird?
It's just my own heart.
It must be really bothering you.
I think that not understanding yourself is a pretty normal feeling.
I'm the same.
I'm pushed around by feelings
I don't really understand myself.
Is that really normal?
I think so.
So I say you shouldn't think too hard about it.
Look, it's Yami and Kotegawa!
What's up, Nana-chan?
I'm looking for a friend!
Yami, have you seen Mea around?
I saw her just a few minutes ago.
Are you dreaming, Senpai?
That's perfect.
I can find out what kind of person you are once we're connected.
(shikaku) keikoku ieroo kaado
#
Warning! Yellow card!
girigiri seefu
Just barely made it
(sankaku) kankei no toraburu
Got trouble with a love triangle
autoo
You're out!
kimi wo miru to hansoku shitaku nacchau
Whenever I see you, I just have to break all the rules!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
saa pinchi mo chansu mo matomete oorai
Now's the time to solve all those problems and opportunities
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
youishuutou ruuru wa yomazu ni goo
Let's just go, ignoring all those boring rules
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
kimi ni au tabi zenbu no kimochi
Whenever I'm by your side, all my feelings
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
zutto guruguru shiteru
Just swirl inside of me
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
atama no naka kimi wa dare to nani wo shiteru no
And in my head, I'm just wondering who you're out with right now
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
!
motto waku waku suru reberu tameshite mitai na
I'd just like to try this out in a more exciting way!
u
#
A
kore wa koi da
This is love!
sora yori hiroi umi yori mo fukai
Vaster than any sky; deeper than any ocean
ginga no hate no hoshi no nami ni mo osamarikirannai
Even all the stars in the galaxy can't hold it back
kitto koi da
This is definitely love!
hitei shite mo iukoto kikanai mune no kodou ga takanatteru yo
There's no denying it with my heart beating faster and faster
itsumo doki doki
I'm always so excited!
Next Episode
Each speculation.