Sairenji!
I... need to talk to you.
That day, at Sainan Waterland, I watched...
as Rito-san tried his best to convey his feelings to Haruna-san, only to fail.
That wasn't enough to change my feelings, though.
I decided not to worry about where I stand with him.
I don't mind if I'm his second or third.
Even if he loves me only a little bit, I'll be happy..
But...
Maybe I'd look more mature if I did something nice with my hair.
What should I do?
I'm glad I could tell Lala how I feel, but...
Haruna-chan...
I'm in love!
They all seemed to think I meant I love the pool,
but who knows what they really thought?
How many times have I failed to tell her how I feel?
Rito-san.
Thank you for taking care of all my plant children.
I made some tea for you in the living room, so why not take a break?
Sure. Thanks, Momo.
Huh?
Momo, did you do something with your hair?
Yeah, just a little.
It looks nice.
That's all?
I'll come in for tea after I finish with these flowers.
Okay.
I'm happy he noticed,
but I guess my expectations were too high.
Commence Project
Maybe there's just no spark between us.
There's a step we need to take before I can even think about being his lover.
Momo, you changed your hairstyle?!
It looks good!
Onee-sama, you look like you're in a good mood.
You noticed? Yeah, kinda.
Actually, the other day at the pool,
Rito-dono confessed his love to Lala-sama,
so now she's in high spirits.
Come on, Peke! There are some
things you should keep to yourself!
I-Is that so? I apologize.
But I thought Rito-san loved Haruna-san...
Momo, you knew about that?
Well, it's like this.
Rito loves me, but he's loved
Haruna more for a lot longer.
And you're okay with that?
Of course!
This way, I can marry Haruna and Rito,
and everyone will be happy!
If Rito becomes the King of Deviluke,
then Earth's rules won't matter either!
You know, Haruna's loved Rito for a really long time too.
So I'll cheer them on so that
they can be together forever!
But you can't tell this to anyone!
I think Rito and Haruna each want to hear how the other feels about them.
Amazing... Onee-sama is so pure and optimistic.
It's true that keeping concubines is a usual custom in many lands.
Our father, the current King of Deviluke doesn't have any concubines,
but he's kind of a rare exception.
If Rito-san were to become the next King of Deviluke and decided to take concubines,
he'd be able to share his love with multiple women.
And if I became one of them,
I could enjoy his tender love too!
That's it! That's the path I want to take!
But considering Rito-san's personality, this could be difficult.
I think he only confessed to Onee-sama to clear up any misunderstandings.
He's a prisoner of Earth's traditions, and I need to fix that!
For starters...
That damn Rito...
He just confused me even more.
Love and stuff...
Nana!
What, Momo? Don't sneak up on me like that!
What do you think about enrolling at Sainan High?
For starters, I need to get a better
grasp on his relationship with women.
Principal
All right, Maron, try to keep still.
It's been a while, so I need to wash you carefully.
I wonder what Yuuki-kun was trying to say at the pool.
I can't stop thinking about it, Maron!
It's about time I deflated that inner tube Yuuki-kun blew up for me.
Yui, have you seen the nail clippers?
At least knock first, Onii-chan!
That's not all.
What's really important here is...
how to change Rito-san.
How am I going to deal with this?
So that Rito-san, Onee-sama, and I...
No,
so that everyone will be happy...
Lala's advice about just taking the both of them was nice,
but it all sounds too good to be true.
I'll make it come true.
I'll make your harem a reality!
I wonder about that.
I don't think it's too far-fetched.
What's up, Celine?
Dangerous Sister Love
What happened?!
Celine?!
You're drunk on cola again?
My bad. I left an open bottle in the fridge.
Let's just put her in bed for now.
It'd be a disaster if someone got inhaled her poll—
Mikan, don't tell me that flower is...
Oh no. This can't be happening!
Rito.
Yes?!
Why are you so jumpy?
You thought I'd cling on to you or something?
Are you really okay?
Obviously!
Anyway, I'm busy, so get lost.
That's weird. So it doesn't work on some people?
At any rate, I lucked out.
Wh-What's going on?!
Rito's voice... his face...
My heart won't stop racing!
I heard about Celine's pollen before, but I didn't think it'd be this bad!
This could be a problem.
She's sound asleep.
Oh, really?
That dish looks so good!
Let's cook it for Rito sometime!
I appreciate the thought,
but remember not to put any dark matter in it.
My body's on fire.
I can't even look at him.
Mikan, could you pass my phone?
Huh? S-Sure.
Here.
Thank you!
Our hands barely touched... Why?!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing!
Celine's pollen is really strong.
I should avoid Rito as much as possible until I can get rid of this flower.
Mikan!
Wh-What?
Do you know where the toilet cleaner that we bought the other day is?
O-Oh, that should be under the sink.
Okay, thanks.
Oh no! I tripped!
Are you okay?
I-I'm okay!
I'm so sorry, Mikan-san. I'm such a klutz.
Momo-san...
Did you do that on purpose?
I need to be careful.
Momo-san probably has more tricks planned.
Mikan-san!
What's got you so worked up?
I-I'm not worked up at all!
I see.
I'm glad to hear that.
If you need help with anything, feel free to call me, okay?
Suspicious! She's way too suspicious!
But she helped me and Yami-san when we were in trouble.
Maybe she isn't up to anything, and is just worried about me?
Mikan?
Momo said that you weren't feeling well.
That bitch!
Your face's really flushed.
Do you have a fever or something?
I-I'm okay!
Even if the pollen doesn't affect you, the flower is still blooming.
W-Wait!
No fever, I guess.
You idiot!
Of all the times to check my fever this way, why now?!
I feel like... I'm going crazy!
Rito...
Hey, Mikan!
Rito... Rito... Rito!
Hey—
Rito!
Rito... Rito... Rito!
Hey, what's gotten into you?
Rito!
Mikan!
Onii-chan...
You...
Were you...
I don't care how this ends.
No!
I... I can't believe it!
She managed to stop herself in the end?
No, she probably just isn't ready yet.
I need to make her realize her true feelings.
Mikan-san, I won't rest until I add you too...
to Rito-san's harem.
It fell off.
Nyanderful Life
That restaurant was great.
I'm stuffed!
No one even notices me.
What should I do?
How did I get myself into this mess?
Ten minutes earlier
Lala-san, is that one of your new inventions?
Yeah! It lets you take the form of any animal to play around!
I thought I'd give it to Nana once it's done.
But I'm having trouble with the configuration.
A dog is chasing me!
Oshizu-chan?!
Wait for me! I'll save you!
Lala-san, you dropped this!
I can't believe I turned into a cat.
Lala-san isn't coming back either. What am I going to do?
I don't think I'll be like this forever, but...
Kotegawa-san!
Such a cute kitty!
Come here!
She hates me!
Why?!
I'm a cat, so she can't understand me!
What can I...
I know!
Thanks, Celine.
Thanks.
A cat?
Since Nana-chan can talk with animals...
Sorry for just coming in like this.
Nana-chan, where are you?
Huh?
A cat?
Yuuki-kun?
You shouldn't enter a stranger's home like this.
No! I'm not a cat, Yuuki-kun!
You're pretty cute.
C-Cute?
Yuuki-kun called me cute!
There, there.
This is great.
If I could just stay as Yuuki-kun's cat, that'd be...
Wait! This isn't okay at all!
Hey!
Jeez, you made such a mess.
How did it come to this?!
Come on, stay still.
You got it all over yourself.
Yuuki-kun's naked!
I-I shouldn't look!
I really want to, though...
I can't!
Am I washing it properly?
I've never had a pet before.
Sorry.
I'll be done in a minute, so hold on just a little longer.
Yuuki-kun... You're so kind, even to cats.
Oh right... When I turned into a dog, Haruna washed me like this too.
That was one hell of an experience!
S-Stop, Yuuki-kun!
Don't touch me there!
S-Stop!
What should I do?
A boy is washing my body!
Huh, what?
Hey, stay still!
I'm back!
Y-Yuuki-kun!
Get a hold of yourself!
What's wrong, Rito?!
What was that loud... crash...
Haruna-san, why...
This... This isn't what it looks like, Mikan-chan!
It was all because a cat... I mean...
I don't see a cat anywhere.
No, I had been turned into a cat!
Looked like I just missed the good part.
Huh?
Wait, where did Haruna go?