Stay right there, kitty! Don't move an inch!
I'm coming to save you!
That dream brought back memories...
from when I was in fifth grade, I think.
On my way home from school, I found a kitten stuck in a tree.
What happened next?
What's up, Yui? Got a date with Yuuki?
O-Of course not!
Why does he always tease me like that?
He knows I've never been interested in romance.
Boys are wild, heartless, and shameless.
They've caused me nothing but trouble in my time as a class representative.
Yuuki-kun's no exception.
I'd...
never fall in love.
This shrine...
~Back then, back there~
Is that you, Kotegawa?
Y-Yuuki-kun? What are you doing here?
I'm on my way home from
helping my dad with his work.
He's been having trouble
meeting his deadlines.
O-Oh.
What about you?
I can't tell him I was going to a pet shop to look at kittens.
Look at that.
It's the youth skunk!
Run took it to school the other day!
What's it doing out here?
W-We should probably catch it.
We wouldn't want it to get excited and start releasing gas again.
Y-You're right.
I'm going for it.
Stay right there!
D-Damn it!
Weren't you listening to me?!
This wouldn't have happened if you hadn't approached it with a scary face!
Then what was I supposed to do?!
Hey, it's getting away!
Hurry! We have to catch it quick!
Our clothes and shoes are too big! They'll slow us down!
D-Did you look?!
N-No! I didn't! I-I didn't look!
You're not lying, are you?!
I-I'm not! Th-The s-skunk...
It's Peke!
Oh yeah, we can get Peke to shrink our clothes!
That's strange. I feel like
I've seen you before, little boy.
You see, this and that happened!
Ah, that explains everything.
Mea!
I got a crêpe for you too!
Thanks, Nana-chan!
Is it just me or...
does Mea-san look kind of gloomy today?
How can a Sunday feel this empty without Rito-san?
Is he still busy helping with Father's manga?
Oh, just listen to me! I'm talking about his dad like he's my father-in-law!
We're not related like that... yet.
What are you grinning about?
It's a return skunk!
Momo-chan?
My chest's as flat as a board now!
Yami-san, what's going on?
This is...
I'm so sorry, Rito-kun!
Our skunk ran out when Ren opened the door!
Okay! We're looking for it too!
I'll call you back later!
I'll search over there.
Thanks!
My goodness. How could Run-san keep such a dangerous creature as a pet?
She said it'd be irresponsible of her
to just send it off to space,
so she read up on how to take care of it and kept it.
Run has her kind moments.
So you're taking her side?
Huh?
You know her cell phone number too.
You're so shameless.
What are you talking about?
I know your number too!
And I explained to you already that I never intend to do anything shameless.
Could've fooled me.
I know. You're not that kind of guy.
If he was just a bit different,
then back on that night...
This is so embarrassing.
Kotegawa...
You have some big boobs.
They're only this big because you're always being so shameless.
So I'm to blame?
Then I guess I'd better take responsibility.
Promise me...
Promise me you won't do shameless things to anyone but me.
Can I feel it?
Go right ahead.
Am I nuts? That looks like I wanted things to go in that direction!
There it is!
Did you see that?
Kids these days...
Wh-What do you think you're doing?!
S-Sorry! Let's catch it before it gets away again!
I refuse to admit that a guy like him is my first love!
It's out of gas! This is our chance to catch it! It's now or never!
Hey, don't go up there!
Be careful! Don't move!
Yuuki-kun, you be careful too!
I'll be fine!
I'm good at this kind of thing!
Huh?
I can't do it.
Please... help me!
It's just over there!
A cat?
Why should we care?
You're always acting like a know-it-all.
Find a way to get it down yourself.
Let's go play some games at my place!
Yeah, let's go!
I got my parents to buy me some new stuff.
Cool!
F-Fine! Now that it's come to this,
I'll do whatever it takes to help that cat!
Are you gonna be okay, Onii-chan?
Yeah, no worries!
I'm good at this kind of thing!
Who's that?
I've never seen that boy before.
Gotcha! Don't worry, you're safe now.
Wow, you did it, Onii-chan!
Huh?
Is this your cat?
N-No.
Well, it's got a collar, so it must've run away from home.
I-I saw a poster over there.
I think it's the same cat.
Oh, okay! I'll check it out!
Thanks!
Thanks, Onee-chan!
Let's go!
Okay.
I didn't think there were boys like him around.
Those siblings were...
Gotcha!
Don't run away anymore!
Y-Yuuki-kun!
Yuuki-kun!
Y-Yami?
You owe me one, Yuuki Rito.
Rito-san!
Are you okay?
Everyone's here!
Thank goodness you're okay!
Thanks, Rito-kun, girls!
It sleeps a lot, so I've been able to take care of it despite my busy schedule.
But sometimes it just runs wild.
Want me to keep it in my De-Dial?
My digital space for animals has mountains and forests too.
It could live in peace there.
Really?
Giving it up would make me sad, but I guess it's for the best.
If you ever want to see it, just let me know.
Okay, thanks!
My goodness. She caused so much trouble.
Yeah.
Rito-san was with Kotegawa-san?
I hope I didn't miss anything.
Sainan High School
Yesterday was such a mess.
Yuuki-kun!
Kotegawa?
What is it?
I wanted to ask you something.
Have you been helping with your dad's work since you were little?
Well, I started helping him in elementary school by buying painting tools.
I remember playing with Mikan at the shrine nearby on our way back home.
Why do you ask?
You haven't changed... at all.
Huh?
B-But this and that are completely different matters!
What are you talking about?
None of your business! Forget I said anything!
And don't look!
What?! I have no idea what you're talking about!
~Honest feelings~
Rito.
I need to talk with you. Got a minute?
Huh? Sure.
What's wrong?
Get in a fight with Momo or something?
U-Um...
Hm?
Do you...
Do you hate small boobs?
Wh-Where did that come from?
Your class got a new teacher
with colossal boobs, right?
Do you prefer boobs like hers?
Boobs like hers...
N-No, not really!
You blushed!
I knew it!
I knew it... I'm not good enough.
Calm down! Guys care about more than just the size of a girl's boobs!
You're charming in your own way, Nana.
It doesn't matter what size your boobs are!
Rito...
Do you see me as a woman?
Could this sad excuse for a chest please you?
Th-They're quite modest compared to her twin sister Momo's,
and they might be even smaller than Mikan's.
B-But...
Her face...
She always acts so childish, but it's like she's a completely different person right now.
W-Well?
Damn it! What the hell am I thinking?
J-Just give me some space for a moment!
You're aroused, aren't you, Rito-san?
Enough already!
Momo?
You jackass! How dare you touch my boobs?!
Stop it! You're being too rough with Rito-san, Nana!
Where's Nana-san and Momo-san?
Dunno. Haven't seen them for a while.
So you two used the Roundie Roundie Change-kun to switch bodies?
Yes. Sorry about all that, Rito-san.
Nana wanted to know if you liked small breasts too.
I never said that!
I just wanted to tease Rito!
And I didn't know you were going to take it so far!
Why are you upset? You were waiting so patiently to see what he'd do.
So it was just Nana and Momo's idea of a prank.
Makes sense. Nana would never
seriously come on to me like that.
Aren't you happy, Nana?
Rito-san looked like he was pleased.
I never asked for this!
It's not like I'm interested in him or anything!
Oh really?
You're charming in your own way, Nana.
That Don Juan...
~Budding feelings?~
What are you up to, Celine?
Pretending you're a florist?
I've never seen these flowers before.
This smells nice!
Celine-san!
You should know better than to summon plants out of my De-Dial like that!
Oh my!
It's a Jikido flower!
This is really dangerous. It'll completely change a person's personality if they smell it.
It may not affect you since
you're basically a plant too,
but it'd be horrible if someone else smelled—
Rito-san was here?!
He smelled it and left?
Lala!
Yes?
Lend me one of your inventions!
What's gotten into you, Rito?
Less talking, more lending!
First, I'll use this!
Okay, time to check if this thing works.
You're using it to look at me?
I need to make sure it's not broken!
Come on! Start moving!
Strike a pose or something!
Huh? L-Like this?
H-How's this?
That's what I'm talking about! Show me more!
Then how about this?
Yes! Just like that! Keep it up!
I can see through even the clothes Peke made!
This is embarrassing.
I'm all revved up!
I wanna see more nudes! More boobs!
Off to school I go!
Hey, Rito.
Already leaving for school?
Are you on class duty or something?
Hm?
How about we bathe together tonight for old times' sake?
What?!
Oh hey, it's Rito-kun!
Huh? You sure look excited.
I'm in paradise!
What've I been wasting my time on when
I could've been using inventions like this?!
Yuuki-kun, no running in the hallwa—
What do you think you're doing?!
Why are you always like this?! Look at yourself!
Just looking isn't enough anymore!
I'll climb to even further heights!
Sairenji!
I'll find Sairenji and use this crab-like thing to cut up her clothes!
Then I'll use Winding Rope-kun to...
Stop, Rito-san!
Momo?
Those glasses... You can see me naked, can't you?
He turned evil and has been misusing those inventions.
I can't let things get any more out of hand.
Momo, I've awakened.
Your harem plan is perfect!
With Lala's inventions and your plants,
I can do whatever I want!
I'll do it! I'll become a harem demon!
You can't.
You can't have a harem as you are now.
Smell this sage flower and return to your senses.
Return to your normal, sincere self.
You're kind and you respect girls.
That's what allows you to—
He passed out?
He must've seen something quite intense during his rampage.
You don't have to be in such a rush to become a womanizer, Rito-san.
I'll lead you down the right path, little by little.
I-I overreacted earlier.
But only because you were being so shameless.
You should be careful not to—
Nothing! I saw nothing!
Huh?