We're now checking in candidates who wish to give a speech.
Those interested should come to the EAC office located below the stage.
Yuuki, you're up.
But I don't have the script yet.
Yuu-kun!
Sorry I took so long.
Far be it from me to stop you.
You should follow the path that you believe in.
However, you might find yourself at a dead end.
Should that happen, I'll be there to guide you.
Th-This is the script for the speech!
That means I gave Yuu-kun the...
You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
Results!
Only a few Oojima Rolls left!
What am I going to do? What am I going do?
Only a few more copies of our newest book are left!
The same goes for our garage kits!
Please support Oojima.
What am I going to do? What am I going to do?
Kiba-senpai, what's wrong?
She must be feeling nervous.
The speech she wrote is about to be read aloud in public, after all.
It'll go great! There's nothing to worry about!
I'm sure you did a perfect job as usual!
That's not what I'm worried about.
I need to get this to Yuu-kun!
Oojima Yuuki
Independent
Oojima Yuuki will begin his speech shortly.
What?
Mifuyu?
Already? I didn't even get to review—
Pardon us.
Tatsumi Moheiji will be the one to deliver his speech next.
Don't surprise me like that.
Thank you, thank you!
I am Tatsumi Moheiji, the candidate endorsed by the General Affairs Commission.
That's some boisterous cheering.
As you're all aware,
the rule of the Public Safety Commission will be coming to an end this term.
It is very important that you do not choose the wrong successor.
You see, everyone, there is a great deal of frivolous spending in the current academy budget.
In particular,
the Public Safety Commission, the group responsible for the disgraceful Oosawa Incident,
holds a plethora of unaccounted expenditures.
If you elect me as Student Council President, I'll examine every detail of the budget
and cut all the frivolities!
There might be a certain other
candidate who makes the same promise.
However, I urge you to consider the following:
Who is the person who planned that budget?
He's attacking Shinonome-san!
While the President makes the final approval,
was there ever a dispute regarding the budget planning?
Did they ever oppose the President's decisions?
Never!
Exactly!
The Finance Commission, which blindly passed shady budgets,
has no right to criticize the current administration!
You can say that again! You're the man for the job!
He even planted sympathizers in the crowd!
Thank you for you listening.
Please give your vote to the candid candidate, Tatsumi Moheiji.
Oh, right. I don't have time to be listening to other speeches.
Ms. Shinonome Satsuki, you're on next.
Yes.
Huh?
Shinonome-san...
Let's both do our best.
Yeah, let's do our best.
Giving their speech next is the candidate endorsed by the Finance Commission,
Shinonome Satsuki!
I am Shinonome Satsuki, the candidate endorsed by the Finance Commission.
Satsuki!
Hey, you're back.
Are you feeling okay, Mifuyu?
I... uh...
What happened to Yuu-kun's speech?
He hasn't given it yet.
Mifuyu? What's wrong, Mifuyu?
At a glance,
the numbers may seem to suggest that the Student Council's budget is in good condition.
But the truth is that both the receipts and expenditures are extremely unbalanced right now.
The reason for these inconsistencies can be attributed to
the gradual, systematic changes in Student Council operations.
She's got a big mouth.
How scary.
Not only does she have wonderful and genuine policies
that consider both the school and student body,
but she has the looks and popularity to match.
Her straightforward personality makes her words even more convincing.
However, isn't it a shame that such straightforwardness could also work against her?
My mistake! I forgot we were still rivals, Mr. Oojima.
Yes, to maintain this high degree of autonomy in the long run,
revolutionary changes need to be made.
We can't afford to stay as we are.
I need to focus on my own speech!
"This wish is closest to my heart."
"I know it will never come true, but I can at least dream that it will."
Huh? Was this the speech?
Yuu-kun, wait for me!
I am determined to make bold changes!
"Yuu-kun, you have someone important to you."
"You have Chisato."
Though they may cause me pain, I will not stop.
"Nothing would please me more than to see you two happy."
"But let me say it just once."
Please, everyone!
"Just this once."
Lend me your support!
"I... Yuu-kun, I..."
"I love you!"
What is this?
The script for the speech looks like...
a love letter from Mii-chan!
How stressed out am I?
Giving a speech next is Oojima Yuuki, an independent candidate.
Please get ready to go on, Mr. Oojima.
O-Okay!
I didn't get to review it in the end.
I'll have to give the speech while reading from it.
Wait! Wait, Yuu-kun!
Who are you?
Please, let me through!
We can't!
It's time.
Wait!
Come on!
People, you're supposed to laugh!
My name is Oojima Yuuki!
It's Oojima, not Ooshima!
It's Jima! Make sure you get it right!
Otherwise, your vote won't count!
I just have one thing to tell you guys today!
Elect me, and I'll put an end to the club reform measures!
A whole bunch of clubs are facing budget cuts,
while others face reorganization and mergers!
As a matter of fact, the Food Club I'm in is going to be disbanded!
I'll do anything I can to stop it from being disbanded!
I'm sure you're all in the same boat, so please...
give me...
your votes!
Good! Now that we're all friends...
Let me tell you a secret that I'd only tell my friends!
I call it the Seven Food Club Vows!
Let's go! First!
First!
The polls will close shortly.
Food Research Club
If you have not cast your vote, we ask that you do so promptly.
Now I've done it.
I suck!
Would you stop that?
We keep telling you that you did just fine!
But I don't remember what happened at all.
The reception was pretty positive.
Non-chan was moved, too!
You were so cool that I almost came.
Who knew you'd start talking about the Seven Food Club Vows, then jump to the origins of the universe,
and then to the history of youkan?
Who knew it started from a lamb dish?
What the hell did I talk about?
You may not remember what you said,
but I'm sure everyone who heard it will never forget.
You think so?
Sorry, Mii-chan.
You went through so much trouble to get me the script, but I was too nervous to read it over
and ended up improvisi—
Don't worry about it.
It was far more moving than what I wrote.
Really?
Yes, really! You were amazing, Yuu-kun.
Was I? I'll stop worrying, then.
Excuse me.
Huh? Aren't you...
The webcast of the election special is about to begin.
I'll be reporting live from here.
Huh?
Why are you in a boy's uniform today?
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm a boy, so of course I'd wear a boy's uniform.
It's a different person?
Real-time Primary Election Results
With whom did you entrust the future of this school?
Good afternoon. I'm your host for this ASP election special, Haratachi.
Earlier today, primaries for the Student Council President election were held.
Voter Turnout
With the voter turnout
at 98.4 percent,
Next Round Qualification
Votes
the number of votes needed to
qualify for the next round is 604.
604 votes, huh?
Oh, we already have candidates projected to qualify!
Shinonome Satsuki
They are the Finance Commission-endorsed candidate, Shinonome Satsuki,
Finance Commission
Projected to pass
Tatsumi Moheiji
General Affairs
Commission
Projected to pass
and the General Affairs Commission-endorsed candidate, Tatsumi Moheiji.
They're in a different league.
There's no Public Safety Commission candidate this year,
so usually this would be it for the qualifiers.
But this year, Yuuki's in the race, too!
Now we will be introducing some candidates the ASP picked up on.
Independent
Oojima Yuuki
First is the independent candidate Oojima Yuuki.
It's Ooshima!
His key policy is "name correction."
What?
The message he left for the voters was, "Don't just skip the rest!"
What did you do?
Well, I tried to give proper answers, but she...
Well, I guess it's he now.
What are you even talking about?
Now reporting live from the Food Club room, Mr. Oojima's campaign office,
Reporter Shiohama!
Yes. I am at Mr. Oojima's campaign office.
Yay!
How is the general mood over there?
Yay, yay!
There were some smiles before the votes began to be counted,
but the mood has turned serious since.
I see. Please follow up if there are any developments.
Understood.
Why are we getting nervous over a webcast?
An update!
# votes counted
% votes counted
100 votes have been counted. That's 1.7 percent of the total votes.
Shinonome Satsuki
Votes
Sacchan has such a huge lead!
Tatsumi Moheiji
Tatsumi is in second, unsurprisingly.
Oojima Yuuki
Oojima-senpai, you're in third place right now!
That's eight percent of the votes.
It takes ten percent of the votes to pass the primaries...
...so he won't make it at this rate!
The counting just started.
They probably haven't even touched the votes from the seniors yet.
But...
A good chunk of the seniors vote just for kicks since they'll be graduating,
so the votes are spread outside the three commissions.
It's still too early to tell.
This gets updated every 100 votes, right?
That means there will be about 60 more updates.
That many?!
Another update came in!
That's the 15th update.
Yuu-chan has 138 votes, which is 9.2 percent of the total votes!
That's 0.1 percent less than last time.
Wait, doesn't fourth place have a higher percentage than before?
Shirakawa Ayame
Shirakawa Ayame had 8.6 percent last time, but now she has 8.8 percent!
So there was a serious candidate other than Yuu-kun.
She was trying to appeal to voters with claims of being
a real revolutionary not affiliated with the three commissions!
Where her support and votes are coming from is a mystery.
I investigated the rumors going around, but I couldn't figure out anything.
Even if she gathers over ten percent of the votes, I'm sure you'll be all right, Oojima-senpai!
The thing is, he won't be.
It'll be impossible for him to win if a fourth candidate passes the primaries.
Why is that?
The swing votes will scatter between you and her.
If that happens,
there's no chance you'll win against the other two,
who have a secured group of voters, in the actual vote.
I see.
Another update!
Oojima Yuuki
Ten percent of the votes! Finally!
Finally.
With 94.4 percent of the votes counted,
you have 571 votes.
They could announce you as a projected qualifier any minute now!
He'll really pass if this keeps up!
This is crazy!
The minimum pass line is 604 votes, so you only need 33 more votes!
We'll make it!
We got so many more votes since they started counting the seniors' votes!
But we can't relax just yet!
Here.
Oojima Yuuki
Shirakawa Ayame
Shirakawa Ayame has 9.8 percent of the votes!
Oojima Yuuki
Shirakawa Ayame
Qualification Confirmed
We just got a third projected qualifier!
Oojima Yuuki
Candidate Oojima is projected to pass.
He has become a projected qualifier with 97.7 percent of the total votes counted.
It will be the first time in seven years
First in 7 Years!
that a candidate unaffiliated with
the three commissions has passed!
Now let's connect to the Oojima campaign office.
Reporter Shiohama!
How are things looking there?
We had a moment of rejoicing after his projected qualification was announced,
but it was short-lived, and his campaign staff have returned to the computer
to watch for the outcome of the election.
Does that mean the qualification alone isn't enough for them?
Yes, it would seem they are waiting to see if a fourth candidate will pass the primaries.
I see. Please keep us updated on any future developments.
Shirakawa Ayame has 9.9 percent of the votes so far.
At this point, it's easier to look at the vote count rather than the percentage.
The vote count is 584!
With the qualification requirement at 604,
Shirakawa Ayame only needs 20 more votes to make it, too!
How many votes have yet to be counted?
140 votes are left.
20 of 140 votes, huh?
If it's just 20 votes, it sounds likely that she'll make it.
Jeez, how come we can't celebrate even though I'm projected to qualify?
An update!
99.3 percent of the votes have been counted!
Ooshima-shi got 608 votes!
That means you're qualified!
You're not just projected!
You exceeded the requirement!
Let's celebrate!
Or at least I'd like to.
We have still have a problem, though.
That fourth person is still getting votes.
She has 596 votes. Just eight more, and we're goners.
It's so suspenseful! We can't be sure until the very end!
It's enough to make my stomach hurt.
It's the final update!
% votes counted
Shirakawa Ayame received...
602 votes!
That's 9.9 percent of total votes!
That means...
She didn't qualify!
Yuuki's the only independent!
We did it!
All right!
Hooray! Hooray!
Time for some celebratory drinks!
I'm getting drunk tonight!
I still can't believe it!
Th-Th-This is a miracle!
Well, the rumors did say this would happen.
Oojima, I'm happy for you.
Thank you!
What's up?
Garage and I prepared this.
Money!
Special gift from us two
Is that...
We're donating part of the proceeds from the sales!
We agreed to do this if you passed the primaries.
Mieru! Garage!
Campaigning from now on will take a lot of resources. You'll need all the funds you can get!
Sorry, it's probably nothing compared to the General Affairs and Finance Commissions' funds.
No, don't be sorry!
Thanks so much, you two!
We'll make good use of this money!
Thank you! I'll work even harder for the final election!
Yeah, you'd better!
Our future depends on it!
That's right! Don't let what's to come scare you!
You got it!
Then why don't we cheer one more time?
All together!
Good idea!
All right, in celebration of Oojima Yuuki passing the primaries...
Hooray!
Hooray.
President Mouri, the identity of Shirakawa Ayame, who came in fourth, has been identified.
It seems she received some of the Public Safety Commission votes.
Yes, it was a sabotage attempt by the Katahira Faction.
They won't let things go my way, will they?
Just to be safe, please put a detail on Oojima's person.
Yes, sir!
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"
Next Episode Preview
Summer is the time for ghost stories!
Then let me tell you a scary story.
It takes a lot to scare us!
Starchy carbohydrates are made of glucose molecules stuck together.
What's so scary about that?
Udon, which has 100 grams of flour per serving,
spaghetti, which has 100 grams of flour per serving,
and soba noodles, which has 100 grams of buckwheat flour per serving,
all have as many calories as 100 grams of sugar.
That's scary!
Next time, Episode 7: Camp!
I pray that all those calories go to my boobs!