Looking at these, it's hard to ignore the intensity of the election.
I'll have to brace myself and go for the win.
Do I even have a chance?
What the hell is this?
P-Please help me!
Wh-What the...
You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
Funding!
That scared me.
Sorry, Aomi-san. I wasn't looking where I was going.
Funding!
Were you looking at those?
W-Well, yeah.
You're amazing, Oojima-senpai,
You're going to be the Student Council President.
Well, I haven't gotten there yet.
In fact, I doubt I will.
The fact that you're going for it is amazing enough!
You have my support!
Thank you, Aomi-san.
By the way, what were you doing?
Maintenance for the school.
The factory's closed today,
and I didn't want to waste my free time doing nothing.
I see.
Being a financial aid student must be tough.
Actually, it's thanks to the financial aid system that I can study here.
I have two little brothers, so I would be out of school to work otherwise.
You smell something?
Yeah, something stinks.
Maybe someone didn't take a bath?
People who don't have the money shouldn't try so hard to come to Takafuji.
Are they your classmates?
I'll go tell them off.
It's fine!
This will only get worse if you don't do anything!
It's fine.
Those guys have always been that way.
Always? They've always been like that?
Those bastards!
A-Anyway, can I ask you something?
Huh?
Um, do I really stink?
They always say I stink, so I've started
to think that maybe I really do...
Of course you don't!
They're just harassing—
Please don't just try to console me. Tell me the truth!
A-Aomi-san?
Senpai, please!
U-Um...
Th-Then...
W-Well?
What a sublime scent!
S-So do I stink?
Not at all! In fact...
In fact?
Oh, no, never mind.
Aomi-san, you don't stink at all.
I guarantee it!
That's a relief.
Thank you very much, Senpai!
No, the pleasure is all mine.
Sorry?
Oh, nothing.
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
So it is true that election campaigns cost a lot of money.
We need to find funding.
We don't have any money, after all.
Apparently, the Finance, General Affairs, and Public Safety Commissions—
the three administrative organizations—
receive campaign funds from the school.
Must be nice to be them.
Yeah, it really was a nice smell.
What?
Nothing.
The people who spend a lot of money on an election are special-interests up to no good, right?
We should run a clean election campaign without spending too much.
Nevertheless, it would still cost us money.
For example, how much do you think it would cost to hand out a flyer to every student?
Assuming the copying costs 10 yen per page,
for 6,000 people, it would cost 60,000 yen!
Indeed.
Necessary Spendings for an Election Campaign
6,000 total students
Even with a low unit cost, you still require a large sum of money when appealing to the masses.
They say it costs the city council tens of millions of yen every year
just to send out the dozens of telegrams for weddings and funerals every day.
So as an overall estimate, we'll need at least 30,000 yen.
We should try to get around 50,000 yen if possible.
How about covering it with the Food Club's funds?
You can't.
Club funds are for club activities only.
Using it for the election campaign would be considered misappropriation.
What they don't know won't hurt them.
If it came to light, any victory would be null and void.
Moreover, the group in charge of such investigations is...
...the Finance Commission, huh?
Well, they'd definitely find us out.
Our current options are...
Self-funding
Self-funding, huh?
We'd have 40,000 yen if each
of us contributed 5,000 yen.
5,000 yen?!
I can't! I don't have any allowance left for this month!
I don't have enough at the moment, either.
A couple thousand yen might be reasonable,
but 5,000 yen per person is too much.
Then you'll have to go with the second option.
The bazaar
during the primaries
The bazaar?
The bazaar
during the primaries
The bazaar held during the primaries was originally instituted
The bazaar
during the primaries
as a way of raising campaign funds.
The bazaar
during the primaries
So that's what it was for?
Some years ago, they raised the issue that people without money couldn't even run.
The school doesn't allow part-time jobs.
So they started the bazaar as a way of raising funds.
And before long, the bazaar became the main event.
We'll return the bazaar to its roots and use it to raise campaign funds.
In that case, we'd need a hot item to sell.
Non-chan strongly recommends
sales of the Oojima Roll!
Oojima Roll?
That's right!
Yuu-chan's specialty roll cake that can only be found at the Food club!
Fluffy sponge cake and fluffy cream in complete harmony!
It melts away the instant you take a bite,
filling your mouth with its heavenly
sweetness and refreshing scent!
Then the fruits emerge from the layer of cream
in a symphony of mouthwatering flavor with just the right sourness!
It is, without a doubt, the ultimate roll cake!
It's super delicious!
Oh? It does sound appetizing.
I wanna eat it! Right now!
Ooshima, go make an Oojima Roll!
Why are you still calling me Ooshima even though you can say "Oojima Roll"?
Yuuki!
How much do you think you could earn with the Oojima Roll?
Let's see. Ingredients would cost about 400 yen per roll.
Say we get ten slices from each roll, so that'd be 40 yen each.
If we sold it at 100 yen per slice, the profit would be 60 yen each.
To raise at least 30,000 yen, I'd need to make 50 rolls.
I can't make that many!
What? You can't?
It's impossible!
Even if I skip classes to bake the whole day, I won't be able to make more than about 20!
With 20 rolls, we'd only get 12,000 yen in profit.
How about we increase the profit per slice?
To raise 30,000 yen...
We'd need to sell each slice at 190 yen!
190 yen would feel pretty expensive for sure.
How about freebies to go with them?
If those freebies cost us money,
that would defeat the point.
So it has to be freebies that don't cost us money?
Shaking hands and taking pictures wouldn't cost us money!
Who'd pay to shake hands with you, Ooshima?
You'd have to pay me
for a handshake.
You people...
Oh, I've got something.
Whether you could sell is an entirely different issue,
but I see the general direction of where this could go.
Direction?
A way to sell Oojima Rolls at a high price without adding to our cost.
I'll handle the rest, so you just make 20 Oojima Rolls.
So you're telling me to skip class?
Since that's all taken care of, you should think about what to hand out.
Huh? It's okay to skip classes for an election campaign?
I didn't hear anything here.
That's dirty.
Bring them here.
Wow!
These are things we handed out last year.
Wouldn't it be considered bribery to hand things out for free?
It's perfectly fine if they're recognized
as the candidate's campaign goods.
Campaign goods?
Notice how all these goods have my name and picture on them?
I see.
Goods that leave an impression will help people remember your name.
But goods with Ooshima on them...
Who would want something like that?
I would!
Like a shower curtain with Yuuki-senpai on it!
Shower curtain?
Yes!
You can put it up and get it wet.
Wet with what?!
But we have neither the money nor the time to make campaign goods.
If they aren't worth anything, people won't accept them, even if they're free.
But it'd cost money and time to make something appealing.
Why don't we hand out the snacks we've stocked up in here?
Using snacks obtained with club funds falls under misappropriation.
This is tough.
Yaoi Sticks.
All-you-can-eat Yaoi Sticks.
Right, the Yaoi Sticks weren't bought with club funds!
We get them from Yume for free!
Yume!
Yeah, that'd be great, Dad.
How many do you need?
At least 2,000. If possible, 3,000!
You heard that?
Thanks, Dad!
So we got a hold of 3,000.
They should be here soon.
All right!
Now the question is how to turn Yaoi Sticks into campaign goods.
Okay, done!
Defending your freedom at school.  Oojima Yuuki
It doesn't look much like a pamphlet.
It has the candidate's name and key issues. A very good pamphlet.
Seriously?
Defending your freedom at school.  Oojima Yuuki
Just to be safe, take it to the Election Administration Committee for approval.
Ai, Kii, go ask the Election Committee!
Roger!
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
What a pair of monkeys.
We're not monkeys!
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
But there isn't enough time to make all 3,000 of them by hand.
It'd be quick with sticker labels.
How much do they cost?
About 1,000 yen for a 20-sheet
pack with 10 labels per page.
We'd need 15 sets of that, so that'd cost us 15,000 yen.
That's expensive! We can't afford that!
They're a little small, but you'd only need seven sets if you got the 24-per-page ones.
Hello?
Yeah. Okay. Got it.
The Election Committee gave their answer.
People might take it the wrong way if they fall off, so we have to stick them on firmly.
So we're in the clear?
It's all settled.
So, Hazuki, mind lending us campaign funds?
Teachers are forbidden from giving
financial assistance to candidates.
Lending money isn't forbidden.
All we're doing is borrowing.
We'll give it back once the primaries are over!
Oh? Then for the time being...
Is 30,000 yen good enough?
Why do you keep it there?!
Thank you! No less from the Food Club advisor, Shinonome Hazuki!
Looks like everything is working out fine.
Let's go raise those campaign funds!
Yeah!
W-We have to put labels on all of these?
This is too much.
Never fear!
This is where Non-chan's invention comes into play!
She thought this might happen and developed this helper machine, Harihari-kun!
That machine is going to put on the labels for us?
No, Harihari-kun is a massage machine
that'll gently massage your shoulders
when they're sore from working!
Why is it called Harihari-kun?
"Harihari-kun" is short for
hydraulic suspension-linked, posture control and alignment system-equipped,
multi-hand massage manipulator!
It's a brilliant name that also expresses
how it eases hard, stiff shoulders!
So basically, we do have to put the labels on them ourselves.
If it takes ten seconds to affix one label,
all of this will take ten hours for one person.
However, it'll take only one hour with 10 people.
And the number of people we have is...
I'm a teacher, so I can't help.
Sumiyoshi-san and Yumeshima-kun will come with me to help set up the booth.
Then just five people?
Is Ooshima still not back?
He went out to buy ingredients for 20 Oojima Rolls, so he'll take a while.
Yuu-chan is doing his share of the work!
It's time for everyone else to work hard!
Let's do this!
So heavy.
I should've brought Yume with me or something.
These guys are running just so they can sell stuff, huh?
Isn't this a violation of the Washington Convention?
Hey, hey! What's the meaning of this?!
Yeah, yeah! What's the meaning of this, you twat?
Is that... Shinonome-san?
Hey, hey, hey! What do you mean by "cutting our club funds"?
Yeah, yeah! What do you mean?!
We're a club with a long history of fine achievements! You hear me?!
Whoa, I should stop them.
You've got some nerve, picking a fight with the Air Sumo Club!
"Air Sumo Club"?
Hey! I'm the very first champion
of air sumo, Sorasou Ryuuzeki!
We have a champion! Isn't that enough of an achievement?
Sorasou Ryuuzeki-san!
We've found some suspicious entries in your club expenditures.
Wh-What?
The majority of the club funds are going towards sumo stew,
but is that much stew a necessity for air sumo?
If you intend to practice air sumo, why not eat air sumo stew as well?
Wh-What?
Are you telling us to eat mist or something?
Yes, you should perfect the art of the air.
C-Cu-Cu-Cu-Cu...
Playing air chicken this time?
Curse you!
Hey, bring salt!
Aye, sir!
Get out! Go! Go!
Never come back again! Go! Go!
A-Air salt?
If you'll excuse me...
She was too much for me to handle!
Oh.
Hello.
How many more?
There's still a whole bunch left.
Oojima
Yuuki
Stop
the club
reforms
This is daunting.
Are you okay?
Normal.
I keep finding budgets wasted on trivial things with each investigation.
In order to reduce these wasted resources,
I need to continue conducting investigations.
Even while you're running an election campaign?
I'm still the Finance Commissioner, after all.
The presidential election and my work are unrelated.
You're pretty strict.
But it's undeniable that there are many clubs with questionable activities.
No, that's not what I meant.
You're too strict on yourself.
It's not as bad as you think.
But...
I'm just being stubborn.
Huh?
As you're aware, Takafuji Academy respects the independence of its students,
so most of the administrative authorities rest upon the student body.
The student council is practically in charge of governing a small nation called Takafuji Academy.
If we govern it too leniently, the academy will quickly collapse.
Like I said, you're strict.
I don't think the financial situation of the academy
is severe enough to require so many budget cuts.
Have you thoroughly gone through my manifesto?
You might have focused too much on the club disbanding and overlooked the rest,
but I would appreciate it if you could peruse the entire platform when you have time.
The club reform isn't solely for budget reduction.
Huh?
There are still so many left.
Will I be able to get it all done today?
The Student Council President, huh?
Oojima-senpai is amazing.
Oh?
You know someone that amazing?
Come with us for a sec.
Um...
We want to hear more.
I still have work to do.
You were slacking off just now.
You don't want to hang out with us?
I...
Mii-chan, let me see that.
Why are you in such a hurry?
What's going on, Yuu-kun?
Shinonome Satsuki's manifesto...
Reform of Financial Aid System
Harassment Issue
Here it is!
Reform of the financial aid system?
switch to the scholarship system
Discontinuation of the financial aid system
All that work tired me out.
Yeah, I don't want to see another Yaoi Stick for a while.
But we got all those done on time, and we're almost done setting up the booth.
Now we just need you to do a good job writing the speech!
That'll be tough.
Hm? What's wrong, Yuuki?
He's been like that ever since he came back from shopping.
Aomi-san!
Huh? That's the girl who ran into you the other day.
Aomi-san,
are you looking for something?
No, I'm fine.
Is it something important? Would you like some help?
No. Really, I'm fine.
It's getting dark, so we should look for it togeth—
I'm fine!
Sorry.
I'm... fine.
Really.
Okay, you go ahead and eat.
Sorry. I'll be back as soon as I can.
See you.
You piss me off so much.
Were you trying to show off that you know an upperclassman? Huh?
No, I wasn't...
I bet you gave him the eye.
It would work even better without this!
P-Please stop!
Ew, look at this!
What should we do with this?
Let's throw it away. It's just trash.
Good idea.
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"
Next Episode Preview
Have any recommendations for a homemade snack recipe?
Take some bread crust, deep fry it, and sprinkle on some sugar. It's delicious and cheap!
How about something that looks better?
Take some bread crust and fry it with margarine and sugar. It's delicious and cheap!
No, something that looks more intricate.
Take some bread crust, put it on the stove until it's crisp,
then mix it with sugar, and you get karintou! It's cheap, too!
Something other than bread crust!
Next time, Episode 5: Festival.
You can even make gratin or pudding with it. It's a magical ingredient, and cheap!