To save the Food Research Club,
the invaluable place where he could spend time with his closest, long-time female friend,
Oojima Yuuki decided to take part in the election.
In response to his feelings, his friend agreed to help him with his campaign to the best of her ability,
together with her best friends.
Okay! That's all 3,600 Yaoi Stick-pamphlets!
Yuuki, make sure you get those Oojima Rolls baked by the end of the day.
Got it.
I'll do my best on writing the speech.
Can you handle it, Mifuyu?
Let us know if it's too much.
Yuuki will pull an all-nighter to work on it.
I will?
It's all right. I can manage on my own.
Thank you, Mifuyu!
I'm so glad that you're on our side.
I'm in love with you.
Will you go out with me?
I'm flattered, Yuu-kun,
but I'm in love with someone else.
Impossible!
Too bad!
There's no place in her heart for you!
Oh, no!
You're at it again?
You all get along so well.
One thing led to another and...
Really?
You looked rather excited to me.
Chisato does love Yuu-kun, after all.
Wh-What are you talking about?
There's no way I'd fall in love with this idiot!
No kidding. You can tell that much
from how she works me like a slave.
Ouch!
What's wrong with you?!
You're so hopeless, Yuu-kun.
What? Me?
Why me?
You're just so hopleless.
What exactly makes me hopeless?
I wonder.
Yuuki's insecure nature may have caused him to show indifference toward her when in public,
but deep down inside, just like in the earlier skit...
Wh-Why are you strangling me?!
he was... in love with Mifuyu.
President, please tell me!
Tell me!
Yuuki-senpai?
Yuuki-senpai!
You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
Festival!
All right, time to get baking!
Do your best, Yuu-kun.
This isn't a problem for you, is it?
What do you mean?
I can afford to skip a few classes,
but isn't your attendance at risk of being too low?
It's all right.
I've been in good health lately, so I haven't been absent all that much.
I see. That's a relief.
This is also my chance to repay Chisato for the favor she did for me.
A favor?
It's thanks to Chisato that I can be here today, having fun.
Mii-chan...
When I transferred to this school after being held back for a year due to surgery,
everyone was so careful around me
because I was a year older than them.
They used respectful language and treated me like I was special.
I felt out of place in my own class.
It was both stressful and painful.
Then Chisato came along and saved me.
Need a hand?
She doesn't even think about stuff like that,
so she's able to talk casually with anyone.
Still, it was thanks to her that I started to fit in.
I'm really grateful.
That's why I want to help her out however I can.
I'll do my best to save the
Food Club she holds so dearly.
Yeah. We'll do our best together.
Okay, that's two down.
That's awe-Samantha, Tabitha!
Um... What?
Those were the names of a witch and her daughter on an old TV show. You've never heard of them?
Why do you know something that old?
I'm a year older than you, remember?
I don't think a year would make a difference there...
And that makes six done.
Mii-chan, what time is it?
Just beef-ore the hour!
Another old joke?
From the ramen ad with dancing cows.
I don't get it.
Excuse me.
I am Shiohama Hidaka, a reporter with the ASP.
I'm currently compiling a directory of presidential candidates,
and if you don't mind, I would like to interview you.
S-Sure.
Go on.
To begin...
Your name is Ooshima Yuuki, correct?
No. My family name is Oojima.
Excuse the mistake.
So it's Ooshima...
No, I told you that it's Oojima!
No need to repeat yourself.
But you just pronounced it as "Ooshima"!
I'm short on time, so let's move on.
What is the key policy of your campaign, Mr. Ooshima?
You're still calling me Ooshima!
Please answer the question.
Correct my name first.
That's the most important thing for the election!
So that's the most important.
His key policy is the correction of his name.
That's not what I meant!
Lastly, do you have a message for the voters?
Don't just skip the rest!
"Don't just skip the rest!"
That wasn't the message!
That's all for the interview.
Thank you very much for your time.
Hey, wait!
You misunderstood me!
"Please support my campaign."
"Thank you very much for listening."
That makes eight.
How are you holding up, Mii-chan?
Yeah, I just finished...
Actually, I think it'll take a while longer.
Okay. Hang in there.
Yeah!
How are things coming along, Yuuki-senpai?
Well, we should be able to make it.
What about you?
Well, I swung by to see you
produce some sticky, white stuff.
What the hell?
Oh, Yuuki-senpai...
Your sweet, white cream.
Hey!
Delicious!
Yuuki worked on the cakes slowly so that he could spend more time with Mifuyu.
The two were there, together in peace.
Good morning, everybody!
What's up, Non-chan-senpai?
Yuu-chan, my junior, do you know what an "angel's share" is?
It's the portion of alcohol that naturally evaporates in the aging barrel, isn't it?
That's exactly right!
So you're aware that one Oojima Roll
out of every ten is an angels' share, right?
Who's the angel in this case?
That'd be the one loved by everyone, Non-chan!
The angel here for her share!
There aren't any here for you today, Non-chan.
I'll bake one for you next time, so forget about it for—
O-Okay! I'll give you the ends, so please don't!
You're giving Non-chan the ends from all 20 rolls?
Yes, I am.
I'm busy right now, so please come back when I'm done.
You really are a true-blue friend!
A blue bosom buddy!
Yuuki and Mifuyu shared a slice from one end.
It was sweet and warm, just like
the time they had spent together.
Just a few more!
Should I make some tea, Yuu-kun?
Oh, could you? That'd be great.
You got it!
Hi!
Yuu-kun, how are things going?
Sensei, you're a little too close.
What did you come here for?
Could you be any meaner?
I'm here because I care about you.
You haven't come over to cook for me since you launched your campaign.
I'm lonely!
I can't help it! I'm busy!
Oh, I almost forgot!
I have some business to take care of.
What's up with that clichéd excuse?
Later. Good luck, Yuu-kun.
Yuu-kun, could you do me a favor?
I don't want you to get distracted.
Pay more attention to Chisato.
That again?
I want both of you to be happy.
You mean you want Chisato to be happy, right?
Don't worry. I'm looking right at her in my own way.
Yuu-kun...
Excuse me!
I was dispatched from the Election Administration Committee!
My name is Aomi Isara!
You're...
Aomi-san!
Dispatched?
A financial aid student is assigned to
each candidate for errands and the like.
Then you're my...
Yes! I'll be helping you from now until the end of your campaign!
I'm glad to be able to work with you!
It's an amazing coincidence that I was matched up with you when there are over a hundred candidates.
Yeah, really.
This could be fate.
Just kidding!
That's...
Oops.
A-Anyway, let's do our best!
Right! I'll be giving it my all!
Takafuji Academy
Primary Election
Everyone, it's a pleasure to be working with you!
Likewise. Help make Yuuki win!
Of course! I'll give it my best!
But man, we're lucky to have landed a spot right next to the event stage.
The president arranged it for us.
Oh, that's our president for you!
Guys!
It's starting soon!
Takafuji Private Academy's
primary election begins now!
Takafuji Private Academy
Primary Election
Start!
No running!
Please keep things moving!
Stay in an orderly line, please!
Don't push!
It's so lively.
Is it like this every year?
Look.
I'll take one of each poster!
Shinonome-san's manifesto audio CD, please!
Give me ten of them!
She's so popular.
Just what you'd expect from the Finance Commission.
We're back!
Where have you guys been?
We got some campaign goods!
Aren't they goods from other candidates?
Why are you helping the enemy?
It's fine. Just think of it as a little reconnaissance.
So whose goods did you get?
So obvious...
This looks ridiculous!
No less from the General Affairs Commission.
Huh?
They're pretty good.
They'll be tough to beat.
Tough to beat? This guy?
You're selling goods here, Ariake, Garage?
It's in return for them being the
President and VP of your support group!
Wait. You didn't know?
You're the one who made that backroom deal!
I'll be selling figures and garage kits,
and Ariake-shi will be selling doujinshi.
We don't have enough space in our club stall!
Food Research Club
Oojima Yuuki
All right, guys! Are you ready?
People will be pouring in soon!
Yuuki, you go get ready for the speech!
Yeah, leave it to me!
Crap, I left the script at home!
What? You haven't memorized it?
There's no way I could memorize a script that long!
I need to go over it at least one more time before the speech!
I have the file, so I'll go print another copy.
Sorry about this. You're a lifesaver, Mii-chan.
You can count on me.
All right, guys. Let's do this!
Food Research Club
Oojima Yuuki
Bazaar
Please support Oojima Yuuki!
Please vote for Yuu-chan, or Oojima Yuuki!
O...
Oojima...
Vote for Oojima.
Keep at it, Morishita-san!
Please line up here!
The newest one and England x America!
Okay, the newest one and England x America!
That'll be 2,000 yen!
Don't forget to vote for Oojima Yuuki!
Snakes and crabs, two each.
Two sets of snakes and crabs!
That will be 13,000 yen!
Make sure to vote for Oojima Yuuki!
O-Okay! I will.
It was the right choice to have those two sell goods.
Wasn't it?
Oojima...
Oojima... Pamphlet.
Vote... Please.
She's improved!
The real deal begins when
we start selling Oojima Rolls!
Done!
"Yuuki gently embraced Mifuyu,
and their lips..."
Wait. Why did I print this one?
What am I so flustered about?
Oh, no! I need to hurry and print the script for the speech!
The super popular Oojima Roll is now on sale!
It's 300 yen per slice!
300 yen?!
We said that even 190 was pushing it, so why?
It was Chii-chan's idea. A cosplayer of the buyer's choice will feed it to them!
That makes it worth 300 yen?
Can you two link arms?
Wait a second!
If you want to take photos of us...
...buy an Oojima Roll bundled with the photo ticket!
Then we'll take...
...any pose you want!
Starting at 500 yen each!
Oojima Roll!
It's 500 yen with the photo ticket?
What do you think?
Huh?
I came up with the cosplay idea!
Isn't it working pretty well?
Wh-What's with the getup?!
Don't I look adorable?
Hey, I could see your underwear!
It's okay! It's just my swimsuit!
Does that really make a difference?
Chisato, you're up!
Coming!
Yuuki-senpai!
Hm?
What do you think about my dress?
N-Not you, too!
He's kind of cute!
He looks like a girl!
That's the guy, right?
And that one is the...
What's with them?
Yumeshima-kun, Ooshima-kun,
you're up next!
For what?
What is this?
Just stand there and feed each other.
Say, "Open up!"
Like this, please!
What the hell is this?
That looks like you and me.
We sold them for 1,000 yen each, special requests included.
I'm counting on you guys!
Guess we have no choice.
You look way too happy about this!
This is all to collect campaign funds!
Anyway, open up!
This is so hot!
He's a tsundere!
W-Was that good enough?
I'm prepared to take requests for this page if it's for the campaign.
What do you think, everyone?
Do it!
Hell no!
We're now checking in candidates who wish to give a speech.
Those interested should come to the EAC office located below the stage.
Interested parties come to the stage
Speech Candidates Check-in
So it's time.
Yuuki, you're up.
But I don't have the script yet.
Yuu-kun!
Sorry I took so long.
It's fine. It's Yuuki's fault for forgetting.
Here you go.
Thank you, Mii-chan!
I really do love you!
Um...
I...
Oh, I mean, I'm in love with someone else.
Too bad! There's no place in her—
Wait! We don't have time to fool around!
There's a place for you over there!
Right!
Hold on!
All right!
Kiss!
Get going!
All done, Mr. Ooshima. That way, please.
It's Oojima.
So you're Mr. Oojima?
Huh?
I'm Tatsumi Moheiji, the candidate endorsed by the General Affairs Commission.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
O-Okay.
If I'm not mistaken, your Food Club manifesto
aims to preserve the freedom that club activities currently have.
I take it that it's in opposition to the Finance Commission manifesto?
Yes.
I see! My policies and your platform are in perfect alignment.
I'd appreciate your support after the primaries.
Huh?
We share an anti-Shinonome stance.
We're thinking along the same lines.
No, I don't intend to end my campaign at the primaries.
I entered this race to win.
I intend to make it through the primaries,
so I won't be able to support you afterward.
Far be it from me to stop you.
You should follow the path that you believe in.
However...
"However"?
However, you might find yourself at a dead end.
Should that happen, I'll be there to guide you.
Please support me when that time comes.
Mr. Tatsumi, you're up next.
I wish you the best of luck. Until next time.
That bastard...
Good work!
Please support Oojima Yuuki!
Are you feeling all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. Thanks.
Relax for the time being!
I guess I'll have to throw this away at home.
Th-This is the script for the speech!
That means I gave Yuu-kun the...
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"
Next Episode Preview
Snacks are delicious, but they can be scary when you have to watch your weight!
It's surprising how some snacks are really high in calories.
A bag of potato chips has as many calories as a bowl of soba noodles, for instance!
It's easy to go way over a standard meal if you snack without thinking!
There are low-calorie snacks that can help!
Like what?
Tell us!
Agar jelly, konjac jelly, and tokoroten!
They're all wobbly!
Next time, Episode 6: Results.
Whoa! My belly fat started going all jiggly!