Okay, are you ready to go?
No.
Don't be selfish.
Mommy needs to go to work soon.
Please?
No! I don't wanna go!
Oh, Chisato-chan!
Eat it.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Wait up!
Here, eat it.
Here!
Hey...
Eat it!
How is it? Is it good?
Yeah.
Eat it!
I don't want it.
Huh?
I don't want chocolate.
I don't want it.
I don't want to share a chocolate bar with you.
Sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'll give you chocolate!
You can have some chocolate!
So please!
Don't disappear!
Don't disappear! Don't disappear!
I'll give you chocolate!
So promise me!
I won't disappear.
I'm not going anywhere.
I promise.
I'll always stay by your side...
no matter what.
You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
Complications!
Yuu-kun is okay, so don't cry.
You're still crying?
Yuu-kun! What did they say?
They said I'll be fine, but they want me to come back tomorrow for a reexamination, just in case.
I see.
I'm so relieved that it wasn't anything serious.
Huh? President Mouri?
Hey, Chisato?
Excuse me!
Oh, if it isn't Sacchan.
Is it true that Oojima was involved in an accident?
He got hit by the store truck.
He jumped out so suddenly that they couldn't stop in time.
So how is he?!
He didn't really get hurt. He's doing just fine.
Yeah.
Thank goodness.
He's such a troublemaker.
I feel sorry for the guy who hit him.
But it's great that no one got hurt.
He had me so worried. I was prepared for the worst!
He really needs to take care of himself. The election's in full swing, after all.
I-I agree! He was so careless and made everyone worry.
Stupidjima!
S-Stupidjima?
I'm calling him Stupidjima because he's stupid! Is that a problem?
H-Hi.
Y-Yuu-kun. Are you all right?
Y-Yeah. At least... one of us is.
You live next door.
I can't unlock the door like this.
I kinda want to get changed.
Isn't this Morishita-san's?
"Kana"?
What about food?
I want to use the restroom.
I want to take a bath.
Sorry, Chisato. I really am.
It was my fault.
I didn't know that would happen.
I'll be more careful.
It must've been a big shock for you,
but try to be more understanding.
Please.
Let go of me already.
I know! I know what you're getting at!
But what am I supposed to do about it?
Liar.
You said you wouldn't go anywhere.
You promised me.
I'm not going anywhere!
Liar.
I'm not lying!
I'm right here!
I'm here for you right now!
Liar...
Liar, liar, liar, liar...
Liar!
Eat it.
Eat it...
Eat it!
Please eat it.
Eat it and tell me it tastes good.
Eat it and forgive me.
Don't leave me alone. Stay by my side.
Please.
Please!
Who... am I?
Who am I to you?
What?
Am I just a replacement for Daiki-kun?
That's not it!
That's exactly it!
You don't see me.
You see Daiki-kun through me.
That's why this isn't love.
You mentioned how you felt so far away from me.
I feel the same way.
Yuuki...
I won't eat it anymore.
You should eat it yourself, Chisato.
I can't be a replacement for Daiki-kun anymore.
Why? You said that you'd stay with me!
I am with you!
Not as Daiki-kun, but as Oojima Yuuki!
So you should be the one to eat it, not me!
You want to be with me, right?
You want to see me, right?
I can be Oojima Yuuki, right?
I-I'm back, Morishita-san.
Oojima.
Welcome back.
Wh-Where is everyone?
Not here.
I see.
Oh, right.
Are the updated approval ratings out?
Presidential Candidates' Approval Ratings
Latest
Shinonome Satsuki
Oojima Yuuki
Tatsumi Moheiji
Undecided
Presidential Candidates' Approval Ratings
Latest
Shinonome Satsuki
Oojima Yuuki
Tatsumi Moheiji
Undecided
Things are looking pretty good for us!
Oojima, not a happy color.
Because our President isn't coming?
That's half of the reason, I guess.
Half?
Half of it is because of Chisato.
The other half...
is pretty personal.
Oojima...
Oh, I almost forgot.
This is yours.
Sorry. I took it with me by
mistake after the accident.
I fixed it to make up for that.
Oojima, you knew how to fix it?
I looked up how to online.
It wasn't too hard.
What was that song?
I don't know.
Huh?
I only learned how to play it.
Did a person named Kana teach you?
The name carved on the back.
This is Kana's.
She gave it to me.
I see. You must've been good friends.
Kana is my best friend,
but I suddenly lost contact with her.
She went missing?
I came to Takafuji to find Kana...
But...
So she's a student here.
Where are you, Kana?
Kana!
President, what's the matter?
Oh, please excuse me.
I nearly lost my balance and tripped at the entrance.
O-Okay...
By the way, what happened to your campaign manager?
I couldn't get in touch with her.
Um, well...
She wasn't feeling well, so she's taking the day off.
I see.
She asked me for advice yesterday, and there's more I'd like to discuss.
Advice? On what?
Oojima-kun,
is it true that you want to address the discrimination against financial aid students in your manifesto?
Huh? Y-Yes.
I'm still formulating the policy, though. I'm not sure what to do.
Please discard that policy.
Please don't touch on matters concerning financial aid students in this election.
But there are students suffering—
This is not a request. It's an order.
Are we clear, Oojima-kun?
We're cooperating with you to get you elected.
We're not supporting you so that you can push for acceptance of your personal opinions.
That's so...
It's possible to resolve the issue after you get elected,
but you won't be able to do anything if you lose the race.
Admirable calls for change will achieve nothing unless you have the means.
Do you understand how to go about making your ideal a reality?
The President's still supporting that guy?
He's wasting his time. All the arrangements have already been made.
Okay, don't worry about a thing.
I'll protect the Takafuji tradition.
Rest assured, Katahira-senpai.
Oh, yeah. On a related note...
Hatsushiba General Hospital Emergency Entrance
I have a request.
Ooshima-san, please come to the accounting desk.
It's Oojima!
S-Sorry!
Huh? Haida-san?
O-Oojima-kun!
I'm so sorry! Did it hurt?
No, I'm just having trouble with my contacts,
so I'm here to see an ophthalmologist.
I see.
How about you, Oojima-kun?
I was in a small car accident.
Hey, it's not that big of a deal.
That's not it. I just dropped my contact.
Huh?
Where?
It probably fell around here.
Where is it?
Where...
Excuse me, Haida-san.
I'll see you later!
What's the meaning of this?!
This isn't what we agreed on!
I accepted your conditions!
Who is he talking to?
I am a member of the Public Safety Commission.
I understand that.
However, this is an entirely different matter!
This was a legitimate deal!
A deal?
It's entirely Oosawa-kun's fault that we had to withdraw from the election!
It has nothing to do with me!
Oosawa...
From the Oosawa Incident?
That was the condition!
Please don't abandon Kana!
Kana...
I understand. Give me some time to think.
Good-bye.
A dead end?
Oogibashi Kana
Oogibashi... Kana?
Sorry!
Is this the Kana that they were talking about?
What business do you have with her?
P-President...
What's this?
Enough.
There's no point in subjecting him to this.
Promise me you won't put up a struggle.
If you do, we'll remove your handcuffs.
Sound good?
Yeah.
So how much have you figured out?
Huh?
Answer me honestly.
I don't want to resort to violence, and if possible, I'd like to remain on good terms with you.
I am a former Public Safety Commissioner.
I can't hold a candle to Oosawa-kun, but I'm capable of being merciless, myself.
You're asking about how much I know about Kana-san, right?
Indeed.
Oogibashi Kana.
She owns the harmonica that Morishita-san carries around.
You made a deal to recover her consciousness.
Oosawa's involved.
I've made a grave blunder.
I was certainly very startled at the time, but I can't believe I failed to notice that I was being overheard.
What is this about?
What are you people doing?
If you really want to know, I'll tell you everything.
However, there's no going back once you hear it.
F-Fine by me.
All right.
We, the Public Safety Commission, maintain security on campus,
but we can't possibly keep every part of this large school under control.
So we use less than admirable methods.
Less than admirable?
They're called S-agents.
Put simply, they're spies.
Spies?!
Attending the school as normal students, they secretly keep an eye on other students
and provide the Public Safety Commission with intelligence.
This system allows the Commission to deal with issues before they develop into serious incidents.
Once an S-agent completes their orientation and training, they are assigned to an officer.
Oogibashi Kana was one of the agents assigned to me.
The other one was...
Morishita Michiru.
Would you like me to continue?
I've already told you far too much for you to go back.
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"
Next Episode Preview
We're conducting a survey.
What kind of snacks do you like?
Tasty snacks.
What about the kind of snacks you dislike?
Untasty snacks.
All right, let's try a different question.
Which do you prefer, Western sweets or Japanese sweets?
Normal.
No, that doesn't answer the question!
Next time, Episode 11: "Investigation!"
So you're fine with anything edible. Got it.