You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
The celebration of our miraculous victory in the presidential election didn't last long.
Crossover!
I soon found myself nearly overwhelmed by my new responsibilities as the student council president.
Thank you for your support
Oojima Yuuki Wins the Election!
But I've made it through the challenges of the week, and now it's the long-awaited weekend!
Thank you for your support
Oojima Yuuki Wins the Election!
But guess what?
Thank you for your support
Oojima Yuuki Wins the Election!
I'm here spending my day off helping Chisato make sweets.
Let's see.
How about making one of these?
A decorated cake, huh?
You can't even make a proper rice ball.
You definitely can't bake a cake.
You're so rude.
I might be a bad cook, but I can make a good rice ball.
If you ask me, making a rice ball doesn't count as cooking.
Whatever.
Then...
how about this?
Fruit mille-feuille?
Even pros have trouble with those!
Why don't you start off with simple sweets that anyone can make?
Like what?
Let me think.
What's this?
Kuzuyu.
Ah, it's mild and delicious!
Even you should be able to make this one with some practice.
Will you stop teasing me already?!
It's just potato starch and sugar dissolved in water!
Why would I even need practice for that?
Go ahead and try making some, then.
Told you.
You're just not cut out for cooking.
Take it slow and start with something simple—
I suck at cooking. I know.
But we're having a party tomorrow for our election victory,
a big party to celebrate saving the Food Club.
Chisato...
I did my part as a team member.
So I want to make something for the party!
There it is.
Let's make some cookies.
It's hard to mess those up.
Yuuki...
We'll be using a simplified recipe, though.
Thanks!
Hello!
Oh, is Pekojima-kun not here?
Shinonome-san!
There you are!
I saw you this morning, so I figured you'd be here.
I'm drafting a budget for next quarter.
Care to help me, Pakojima-kun?
Oh, um, today's not really a good...
Sooo sorry!
He's already booked for the day!
He and I are making sweets for the party tomorrow! Just the two of us!
So he's not going anywhere.
Thanks for stopping by, though.
You have student council work to do, don't you?
Better get a move on!
You can't monopolize his time like that!
Pokojima-kun is the student council president now!
Since he kept his campaign promise and stopped my club reforms,
he has to cut expenses, secure new sources of revenue, and solve various other problems.
He can't spend all his time on club activities!
I'm ordering you as president of the Food Research Club!
You became a member of the Food Club, so you'd better obey!
I'm not just a member of your club. I'm also the student council vice president!
It's only natural that I'm concerned about student council affairs.
But we already made plans. Didn't we, Yuuki?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Regardless, you're the student council president.
Don't you think you should prioritize your student council duties, Pikojima-kun?
I guess you have a point.
Who asked you?
What?
Excuse me!
Huh?
Ayu-chan!
Ayumu-san!
Hey, Sacchin!
And long time no see, Chisato-chan!
What a coincidence.
I didn't know you two knew each other.
What? You know them, Shinonome-san?
Matsuri-chan and I go way back.
Really?
Ayu-chan's my cousin.
Wow!
So I was right!
I had a feeling that you all knew each other.
You can't expect everyone you're friends with to know one another.
So what brings you here today?
Um, we're here to give these back.
And those are...
our school uniforms?
Oh, the ones I lent you.
There was an event at our school
where we ran a uniform café.
We borrowed those Takafuji uniforms for the waitresses to wear.
Takafuji uniforms are cute and popular, after all.
Everyone loved them.
Thanks a bunch, Chii-chan!
You're welcome!
Were you making sweets?
Oh, I was teaching Chisato how to make cooki—
No, he wasn't!
Pukojima-kun has student council business to attend to, so he has no time to fool around!
We weren't fooling around!
We were doing official club activities!
I hope you're not saying those are more important than his student council duties.
That's exactly what I'm saying!
I'm not going to hand Yuuki over just because you went through all the vowels!
Quite an interesting situation we have here.
I have an idea on how to settle this.
Why don't the two of you have a contest?
A contest?
Right!
It looks like you're fighting over Oosh—I mean, Oojima-kun.
The two of you make sweets,
and whoever's Oojima-kun likes better gets him all to herself!
N-No way! That's not your call to make!
She's right.
I-I refuse to make sweets.
Really?
Because I think Oojima-kun is just dying to try your sweets. Isn't that right?
Huh?
Well, yeah, I'd love to try some.
I think it's a great idea!
Chii-chan will get to practice making sweets, too!
It's killing two birds with one stone!
I can lend you a hand if you need it.
If you need another judge, I can help.
And there we have it!
A sweets contest between Chisato-chan and Sacchin!
Drum roll, please!
I'll help you out since you aren't very good at cooking, Chii-chan.
I've got your back, Sacchin, so don't worry!
Prize
I'm getting a strong feeling of déjà vu.
All right, let's get started!
Ready...
Start!
You kinda dropped the ball on that one, Ayumu.
Do your best!
I will!
I'm sure we'll make delicious sweets.
I don't think I've ever seen you worked up over something like this, Sacchin.
Oh, really?
Yeah, you're never like this.
I wonder if this means what I think it does.
I-It doesn't!
You're... mistaken.
Well, if you say so.
In for a penny, in for a pound!
I'm gonna make something that'll take his taste buds for a ride!
I'm surprised you want to learn how to make sweets.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but...
are you trying to get good at cooking for your beloved Oojima-kun?
Oh, is that it?
Y-Yeah. You could say that.
So, yeah...
I really can't afford to lose.
I really want him to tell me that mine's good.
So please...
help me out!
You can count on us, Chii-chan!
I'll do whatever I can to help!
By the way, Sacchin, have these grown even bigger?
C-Cut it out, Matsuri-chan!
Wow, they're so soft!
S-Stop!
I-I mean it!
S-Stop it, Matsuri-chan!
Stop! Please!
No!
Sorry!
I can't control myself!
What are you peeping at?
Food Research Club
All righty, then.
First, heat the butter in the microwave until it starts to melt.
Until it melts? Okay.
Switch on!
Only until it starts to melt.
You don't want it to melt completely!
I know that!
I'm watching it closely.
It's taking a while.
Hey, don't just eyeball it!
Prize
Huh? Why not?
The butter will keep melting after you take it out!
Once you see it melt, it's already too late!
Oh, I didn't know that.
Oh! It's all melted.
Too late!
So what do you want to make, Sacchin?
Well, let's see...
My family runs an old Japanese sweets shop, so...
You're going for Japanese sweets, then?
Actually, no.
I'm going to make the most out of this opportunity.
I don't get to have Western sweets very often, so I'll make some now!
Don't get me wrong. Japanese sweets are certainly wonderful,
but Western sweets have certain charms that you can't find in Japanese sweets!
I can see these charms because I know all there is to know about Japanese sweets.
You could even call them the brilliance of Western sweets!
Vibrant colors, mellow fragrances, and rich flavors!
A refreshing change from the simplicity of Japanese sweets!
So what exactly are you gonna make?
Western sweets, of course!
Specifically?
So many sweets! Jackpot!
Someone save me!
The butter's all melted.
Okay, now take the hotcake mix and...
...just pour it in, right?
Don't pour it all in at once!
It'll be really hard to mix!
I just dumped it all in.
Did I ruin it?
Well...
That depends on how much effort you're willing to put into this.
I-I'm exhausted.
Way to go, Chii-chan!
Well done!
I knew you could do it!
You could've saved yourself half the effort if you hadn't screwed up earlier.
All right, let's roll out the cookie dough.
With this, right?
Yep!
Make sure the thickness is even!
I know!
There we go!
One... two...
One, two...
I think I'm... getting the hang of this.
This is starting to...
feel like real cooking!
Don't forget to make it even!
I heard you the first time!
Knead, knead...
Knead it to death, yay!
I'm glad you're enjoying yourself, but how's the thickness?
Uh...
The thickness is...
about one millimeter.
That's way too thin!
You couldn't even use that for crêpes!
It's adorable!
Hanako-san the toil—nose ghost?
Does it look okay, Ayu-chan?
Yeah, it looks fine!
You're really making progress!
Now all that's left is decorating!
They're so cute!
Mao-chan, you're a natural!
No, I just...
What are you looking at, Haida?
Oh, no!
Are you two okay?
We're sorry our machine malfunctioned on you.
You can wear those for the time being.
Sorry about this. We had just returned them, too.
I'm so sorry.
Man, I can't get over how cute Takafuji uniforms are!
Huh?
Mao-chan, did your boobs grow again?
N-No, they didn't!
If only Onii-chan were here! He could've seen you in this adorable girls' uniform!
Rikuto-san?!
Can I come in yet?
Okay, time's up!
Are you two ready?
Chii-chan's team made homemade cookies!
Sacchin's team made a layer cake!
Let's decide the winner!
It's judging time!
Now, the main judge, Oojima-kun, will taste each entry!
He can try yours first.
What?
No, he should try yours first.
What makes you say that? Not feeling confident?
Right back at you.
If you're confident, why don't you get him to try yours first?
Going first will give you an advantage since he'll be hungrier!
I-I don't mind going after you, then.
What's wrong, guys?
What's the holdup?
We won't be able to decide the winner if neither of them goes.
Hurry up and get Oojima to eat them.
Have some of this and calm down, you two.
That's...
Could that be the famous...
Oojima Roll, my specialty!
Ooh!
I made it for the party tomorrow,
but it wouldn't be fair to only judge what the two of you made.
Is it okay for me to have some?
Of course! I have a lot more.
I'm having some, too!
So this is the Oojima Roll!
This is absolutely divine! It's so delicious!
It melts in my mouth!
This is leagues above anything an amateur could make!
You could start your own bakery right now!
I guarantee i—
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Now that you've all calmed down, let's resume the contest!
Let the judging begin!
So who's going first?
Wait!
I-I think we should call off this contest.
I-I agree. We don't need to go through with this silly contest.
C-Competing like this won't help either of us.
I-Indeed! Conflicts are always unproductive.
You can't just call it quits now!
Think of all the effort you put into making these sweets!
But...
I can't bear to have my cookies judged by someone who can make this marvel!
Exactly! I'd be too embarrassed to listen to you comment on my cake.
Stop trying to weasel out of this!
In entering battle, one must have the resolve to see things through to the end.
A warrior does not go back on her word!
I'm not a warrior, though.
No complaining! You're already in the contest!
Be brave, Chii-chan!
G-Good luck!
I don't have the patience for this!
We aren't getting anywhere, so I'll decide who goes first!
Who'll go first? Eeeny, meeny, miny!
Sacchin and her cake will go first!
What?!
You could've at least finished the rhyme.
Let the judging begin!
It's delicious!
It's really delicious, Shinonome-san!
Thank you, Oojima-kun!
You're up next, Chisato-chan.
It's good.
You've outdone yourself, Chisato!
R-Really?
You bet!
I bet the other Food Club members will love these cookies, too!
Are you all right, Chii-chan?
I-I just felt so giddy...
Well done!
Thanks!
Okay, let's hear the results!
Ooshima—I mean,
Oojima-kun will announce his judgment!
No need for that.
Huh?
I lost this contest.
What?
What do you mean?
My approach to this contest was to make a cake that Oojima-kun would find delicious.
It wasn't just for the sake of competing.
I also wanted to make Oojima-kun happy.
But when Oojima-kun ate my cake and said it was delicious,
I was the one who felt happy.
Shinonome-san...
I think Sumiyoshi-san felt the same way.
The person who ate the food is happy, and the person who made the food is happy, too.
Don't you think that's wonderful?
That must be what sweets are really about.
I never knew this and tried to disband the Food Club for its lack of conspicuous achievements.
Considering how long it took me to realize something so obvious,
I must admit I wasn't qualified to take part in this contest to begin with.
Thanks for today.
The Food Research Club strives to make others happy.
It's a wonderful club activity.
Took you long enough.
Hold it!
You may've thought that was a nice note to end on,
but we have yet to try Sacchin's cake and Chisato-chan's cookies!
This layer cake is delicious!
These cookies are very good, too.
What? Really?
Oh? You haven't tried them yourself?
No. I was kinda scared.
One trick to cooking well is to keep tasting it as you make it.
Here you go. Open up.
It's good!
See?
We "make others happy," huh?
Oojima Yuuki Wins the Election!
Thank you for your support
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"