Daiki.
Daiki, wake up. Come on.
I've got your favorite chocolate.
I'll eat it all if you don't wake up.
Wake up.
Wake up, Daiki.
I'll give you my half, too, so wake up.
Wake up.
A dream?
Oh, shoot!
I'm leaving now!
And you're up!
Our campaign for the main election starts today.
We don't have even a second to waste on resting.
Come on, hurry up.
Do I need to help you change,
Daiki?
What's wrong, Yuuki?
What are you staring at?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
Get up already, Yuuki.
You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
Public Safety
Commission
Accident!
We, the Public Safety Commission,
have been the ruling party for many years now.
However, we've unfortunately been forced to withdraw from the election this year
as a result of the incident involving Commissioner Oosawa.
As maintaining our rule is no longer an option,
we must begin planning for next year's election immediately.
There are three candidates this year.
Finance Commission
General Affairs Commission
Independent
Oojima Yuuki
Tatsumi Moheiji
Shinonome Satsuki
Oojima Yuuki
Tatsumi Moheiji
Shinonome Satsuki
General Affairs Commission
Independent
Primary Election Qualifiers
From the Finance Commission, we have Shinonome Satsuki,
and from the General Affairs Commission, we have Tatsumi Moheiji.
As we know from our experience, the ruling party has the advantage in an election.
If we allow any other commission to ascend,
our prospects for next year's election will be dim.
However,
if the independent candidate Oojima Yuuki, who has no ulterior motives, is elected President...
The Public Safety Commission will support Oojima Yuuki.
One of our officers, an intelligence operative, is already on detail.
Take care to not let anyone learn of this.
Especially not...
the Katahira faction.
You should've printed the flyers before we had to leave!
That's not the candidate's job!
We're understaffed!
You could've just had Yume do this—
I'm sorry! I didn't see you!
Are you okay?
I'm completely fine.
Are you sure?
Oh, are you a candidate?
Oh, yeah, I am.
Maybe you've heard of me.
I'm the first candidate not from any of the three commissions to pass the primaries in seven years.
Nope.
No one knows about you because you're not working hard enough.
I'm sorry. I haven't been to school in a while, so I don't know much about this year's election.
Oh, that explains it.
My name's Oojima. Oojima Yuuki!
Oojima Yuuki-san? You have a very nice name.
Thank you very much!
I'm running for true Academy reform!
I hope you'll lend me your support!
Yes, of course.
You were laying the nice guy act on pretty thick back there.
I have to get along with the voters.
So it's not just because she's a girl?
What are you—
Isn't that...
That was a dirty trick!
Don't blame me just because you didn't notice sooner.
You always do things like this!
You should analyze your opponent better next time.
Keep getting distracted that easily, and someone
might pull the rug out from under your feet.
Nee-san!
Good morning, Sneakyjima-kun.
Where did that name come from?!
Because you were eavesdropping on our conversation like a sneak.
You don't like it?
Of course not!
So what's the matter this time?
I thought you made up with Sensei.
She tricked me.
Huh?
That match was mine!
Match? Do you mean the shogi game from yesterday?
Yeah.
When I played out the game again at home,
I realized that I had mate in just a few moves!
Oh.
I was so wrapped up in her story.
She must've started talking about the past to distract me!
You wanted to find out about her past,
so it doesn't really matter who won, does it?
That's not what I'm talking about!
You were the winner's prize for that match.
No, never mind.
Never mind what?
What are you guys talking about?
Well, nothing much.
Is she helping you with the election campaign?
Yeah, she's the head campaign manager.
We're not making secret agreements or doing anything in regards to the election, so don't worry.
Yup, it's just as she says.
We were having a conversation concerning private matters.
Yup, it's just as— Huh?!
D-Don't call it "private"!
What's wrong, Chisato?
Nothing.
Why are you so angry?
I'm not angry!
Yes, you are.
I just said that I'm not!
I told you,
I'm not discussing anything election-related with Shinonome-san!
That's why I'm angry!
See? You're angry.
Oh, you!
You're late!
Why did it take you forever to bring those flyers?!
Hurry up before the other students start showing up!
Sorry. Something came up on the way over.
Yuu-kun, thanks for yesterday.
Huh?
Satsuki and I managed to resolve the bad blood between us.
Thank you.
Oh, I didn't do anything.
Oh, no. It wouldn't have happened if not for you.
I'm grateful.
You're too kind.
Attention, everyone!
The main attraction of the day...
Switch on!
Go... Change!
Shoot!
Japan's Best
Leader
This is Non-chan's invention, Stage Champion!
But it really is just as President Mouri told us.
Most of the students will see us as they're coming to school.
Waking up early was worth it!
You claimed this spot for us, Mii-chan?
I did. I can't do much manual labor, so this is one of the few things I can help with.
Mii-chan!
Catch me!
Wait!
Got you!
Onee-chan, that's no fair!
Sure it is!
Mii-chan, I love you!
Will you go out with me?
Yuu-kun, I'm flattered,
but I'm in love with someone else.
Huh?
Chisato?
Y-Yeah! Let's do a good job handing out these flyers, guys!
Are you giving a street speech here today?
Shiohama-san!
The ASP assigned me to report on you throughout the election!
I look forward to working with you.
Same here. Let's do our best!
Th-Thanks.
Flyer team, are we all set?
I'm ready any time!
Normal.
What should we be doing?
I have a very special job, just for you two!
If you put it that way...
...there's no way we can refuse!
So what do you want us to do?!
I want you to power the equipment!
Power it?
All right, guys.
Let's get started!
Yeah!
Yeah.
Gentlemen!
With the rule of Public Safety Commission ending, this year is our chance to rise to power!
We must not miss this opportunity!
Please give this everything you've got!
Yes, sir!
We have a very influential ally this year.
There's nothing for us to fear.
I'll stop the club reforms!
I need your support!
Please support Oojima Yuuki!
Please vote for Oojima Yuuki!
Oojima Yuuki, the true independent candidate, is here to revolutionize the academy!
Oojima...
Yuuki...
wants your vote.
Please vote for Oojima Yuuki!
What's this?
Financial aid students work in election campaigns, too?
No way! Students on aid have the right to vote?
Please give it back!
That would be a problem, wouldn't it?
I will...
Please!
I need that!
Aomi-san!
Yuuki?
Stop it! Please!
What the hell? This guy wants better treatment for people on financial aid?
I hope that doesn't mean using our money.
Hey!
Oojima-senpai...
What are you doing to her?
What's the big deal? She's on financial aid.
You're siding with students on financial aid?
You got a problem with us?
You guys...
Stop it, Yuuki! You're campaigning!
Don't do anything violent!
But...
Hold it in for now. I'm begging you.
That's enough.
We're from the Public Safety Commission.
Show me see your student IDs, please.
We haven't done anything wrong!
Your student IDs, please.
W-We said that we haven't done anything wrong!
We saw everything.
Your student IDs, please.
They all match with their owners.
Student code section seven, relationships with other students, item two:
Respect other people, regardless of their age, gender, or status.
And item three: Violence will not be tolerated.
We suspect that you're in violation of the aforementioned items.
We haven't done anything violent!
Verbal abuse, which can affect others psychologically, is equivalent to violence.
We will follow up on this later.
Please report to the Public Safety Commission when summoned.
What's the matter?
It's all right. It's over now.
Are you okay, Aomi-san?
Yes, thank you.
I can handle stuff like this.
I'm used to it.
I was actually more frightened by the Public Safety Commission members.
The Public Safety Commission?
One time, a financial aid student in my class was taken away by the Public Safety Commission,
and they left her traumatized.
It was so bad that she stopped coming to school.
Is that the girl involved in the Oosawa Incident?
An anonymous source tipped off the Public Safety Commission that a financial aid student
had shoplifted from the school store.
Public Safety Commissioner Oosawa overstepped their bounds during the investigation
and even disclosed the suspect's name despite a lack of evidence.
Consequently, the harassment against the suspect escalated.
Eventually, it grew too much for her, and she stopped coming to school altogether.
It was later discovered that the tip-off was fake all along,
and Oosawa was placed on probation for unjust investigation.
President Mouri recently returned as the Public Safety Commissioner
and holds a concurrent post as Student Council President.
Things calmed down a bit after President Mouri returned,
but the Public Safety Commission has never really cracked down on financial aid student harassment.
What you saw earlier is a rarity.
Oojima-senpai.
Thank you so much for coming to save me earlier.
Oh, no, I didn't do anything.
That's not true. You came to help me, and that's more than enough.
It was very encouraging.
W-Was it?
Yes!
Glad I could help, then.
You were really cool.
It's a shame that I didn't take any pictures.
You flatter me...
Wasn't the financial aid system originally set up
to assist students who excel academically but have financial troubles, like a relief fund?
Yes.
The policy was adopted to increase the student population
without decreasing the school's academic achievement.
The system deploys financial aid students to work at cooperating companies
and uses earnings from that to fund their tuition.
And they're prohibited from working part-time so that they can focus on the work
assigned by the school.
They can't join clubs, either.
They're admirable, hardworking students.
Financial aid students aren't doing anything to deserve harassment!
They should be proud of themselves!
Hey, Mii-chan. I want to add an item to my manifesto.
Will you consider it?
Sure. What is it?
I want to end the discrimination against financial aid students here at Takafuji Academy!
Welcome back, ma'am.
I feel like I'm an executive who was just discharged from prison or something.
Well, I guess that's exactly the case.
Have you been well?
I have! But I had to stay at home while on probation, so I gained some.
Gained what?
Oh, don't you worry your little head over it.
Okay...
Have you been well, Yakumo-senpai?
It must have been so much trouble having to manage two posts while I was away.
Not at all. The Vice President took care of the actual work.
Oh.
It was easier than dealing with me, since I sympathize with the Katahira faction.
That's right. I've heard lots about the presidential election.
Let me hear your story later.
All right.
I, Oosawa Yuina, have now returned as the Public Safety Commissioner.
Dog Pot Club
I'll do my best to live up to your expectations!
We're counting on your vote!
I almost mistook the Dog Pot Club for dog eaters.
And isn't it strange that they're getting off with a budget cut
while the Food Club is getting shut down?
Hey, Yuuki...
What is it?
Is that what you really think?
Oh, I mean, every club has a reason to exist!
They shouldn't be forced to disband or cut their budgets!
Right?
Not that! I'm talking about adding the financial aid student issue to your manifesto.
Oh, that?
The reason we're campaigning for the election is to save the Food Club, right?
Yeah. What's your point?
Then why would you add a policy like that?
Huh?
We have to win the election!
We need a manifesto that gets as many students as possible to side with us.
Can't you tell how much the financial aid students are being harassed?
I can! And that's because the majority of the students look down on them!
That means your policy might make that majority turn their backs on you!
Financial aid students are the minority.
Policies aimed at minorities put you at a disadvantage in elections!
But I can't just neglect the issue, now can I?
Work on it after you get elected!
Right now, winning the election comes before anything else!
But there are people being harassed as we speak!
We need to bring attention to this issue as soon as we can!
Stop it!
Are you so set on this because of your sense of justice?
Or is it because Isara is a financial aid student?
What?
Because you want to impress Hazuki?
Because you want the ASP reporter to praise you?
Because you want to compete with the Finance Commissioner?
What's wrong with you, Chisato?
Don't leave me behind.
Don't go anywhere.
Chisato...
Why? Why are you leaving me behind?
I'm right here with you.
Then why do I feel so far away from you?
Why are we drifting apart, when we were so close?
We're not drifting apart.
I tell you this all the time.
I'll always stay by your side.
I'm not going anywhere.
I promise.
Oh, his approval ratings aren't half bad.
He has the potential to win this election.
So? Do you think he'll side with us?
Yes. His interests match ours.
That's not what I mean.
I'm wondering if he'll listen to me.
He's amiable and enjoys interacting—
You're still not getting it.
I'm asking whether he'll be a puppet president for the Public Safety Commission.
Come on. Did I really have to spell it out for you?
So, will he?
We're only cooperating with him to help him get elected.
So he won't be our puppet!
He's not on our side, then.
He might institute policies that leave the Public Safety Commission at a disadvantage.
Oosawa-kun.
You should know better than to team up with shady people, Senpai.
They're likely to slit your throat while you sleep.
Or I might have to slit his throat.
Just kidding!
See you tomorrow.
The new approval ratings are out!
According to ASP's survey, although it's only by a narrow margin from Shinonome,
your approval rating is highest among the candidates!
Let me see!
Is that data reliable?
What's up with that data? Why is his approval rating so high among the girls?
I'm sure they found Yuu-kun charming.
It's Yuuki we're talking about!
There's a better chance of seeing pigs fly.
That's harsh.
That's the Recycling Club's car.
They're driving so recklessly.
Oojima.
Aren't you gonna play the harmonica?
I'm trying...
but it won't play.
Um, can I see it?
I wonder if it's broken.
Yuuki, what are you doing?!
Huh?
That's an indirect kiss.
What?!
Sorry, Morishita-san!
I didn't mean to!
It's okay...
as long as it's you.
It's not okay!
And why are you blushing, Yuuki?!
No, it's not what you think! I didn't mean to...
What's "not what I think"?
It's like...
Like what?
Well, um, you know...
Run away!
Wait!
No!
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"
Next Episode Preview
Yaoi Sticks taste good.
They come in quite a variety of flavors, don't they?
The vast array of flavors amazes me.
By the way, what's the name of the character on this package?
Yaoemon.
I must say, it's quite the original character.
Normal.
Next time, Episode 10: "Complications!"
Normal...
but strange.