I'm surprised.
I guess you really can't judge a book by its cover.
You're so hard.
You're the one making me do this.
Don't you want to?
I mean, I'm so defenseless right now.
Are you sure?
You can do whatever you want.
Then how about this?
Ouch!
How is it?
It's too much.
Just kidding.
Checkmate.
Well?
You win.
You're a sloppy player, Loserjima-kun.
Please don't give me any unlucky nicknames.
It's good luck for me since we're competing.
You don't like it?
Of course not.
Wanna go another round?
You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
Truth!
Hey, did you find him?
No, not yet.
Truth!
This is so weird.
How did he just disappear?
It's creepy.
Looks like they won't stop until they find you.
How am I going to get out of here?
You have two choices.
First, give up and turn yourself in.
Second, live with me here for the rest of your life.
Third, play some more shogi and wait a little longer.
Weren't there two choices?
You don't want a third one?
Oh, no. I'll go with the third choice for now.
And if it doesn't work out, I'll go with the second one.
Are you sure about that?
What would my big sister think if she found out?
Hazuki-sensei has nothing to do with it.
But you two kissed, right?
I told you that it was an accident!
What if I forced myself on you with a kiss?
Would you still call it an accident?
Kissjima-kun!
Yes?
You make the first move this time.
Okay.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Did you ever hear the reason my sister left home?
The reason she left home?
She just holed up at home one day.
She did?
She also stopped interacting with the entire family.
I asked my parents why, but they weren't of any help.
My sister kept quiet and wouldn't tell me anything.
She went on like that until she left home.
It's troubled my mother ever since.
It still depresses her, even now.
I want to do something, but I don't even know what happened.
It seems like my sister is open with you,
so I thought she might have told you something about it.
No. Sorry, but she's never mentioned it before.
I see.
Now's your chance.
Okay!
Someone might be making rounds, so let's take the fire escape.
You're a lifesaver.
I had a lot of fun.
Could we hang out again sometime?
Of course. I'd love to.
And about what we discussed earlier...
Yeah, I'll ask Sensei about it when I have a chance.
No, not that.
If I were to force myself on you with a kiss,
would you treat that as just an accident, too?
Um...
Well?
I...
Hazuki-sensei!
I feel alive!
Hey, Yuu-kun, you want some?
Wai—
Gotcha.
U-Um...
Sorry, sorry.
But that helped you cool down, didn't it?
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
Guys, did you hear? There was
a pervert at the campsite last night.
P-Pervert? There was a p-pervert?!
He caused a ruckus and
kept a few girls up all night.
We should've captured him and kicked his ass!
I was out like a light, so I didn't even notice.
Non-chan says, "Early to bed, early to rise," so she didn't notice, either!
Japan's Best
Leader
Staying up late is bad for your skin!
You didn't notice anything, Prez?
N-No.
Hazuki was drunk, so I had to take care of her.
I'm a heavy sleeper, so I didn't notice anything, either.
What about you, Morishita-san?
I slept through it.
I thought the camp dorm had very tight security,
but it's actually pretty dangerous, huh?
I bet some dumb girl brought him into the building.
Who could that dumb girl be?
Y-Yeah, I wonder.
It's time for some recreation!
Recreation?
Recreation is an essential element of a camp!
We'll be doing a standard...
test of courage!
Test of courage?
Well, the campaign work is going well, so we can probably afford to play around.
It was developed secretly in the event that it would be needed!
It's the "Freaky, destruction feature-equipped,
self-evolving creature exclusively built for test of courage," a.k.a...
"Bakeru-kun!"
As usual, I can't begin to imagine where your invention's shortened name comes from.
Now, let's go give school ghost stories a try!
Hazuki-sensei?
That one was Aomi-san.
Think they're okay?
Chisato?
Are you that worried about them?
Well, if they're screaming, of course I'd get worried.
That excuse won't work on me.
What excuse?
The hell is that?
A Japanese toilet?
Oh, it's Hanako-san from that toilet girl myth.
So a hand should emerge from inside...
L-Legs?
I don't get it.
Hey! Chisa—
Wh-What are you doing?
Oh, no! It's so scary!
Save me, Yuuki!
Protect me!
What do you want me to do, exactly?
Why aren't you worried about me?
You were so worried about Hazuki and Isara earlier.
It's hard to take this situation seriously.
So you won't worry about me, huh?
That's not what I said.
It's the same as last night!
What? Last night?
What were you two up to?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I know it was you!
N-Nothing much. We were just playing some shogi.
Shogi? Why would you play shogi with Hazuki?
Huh? Oh, with Hazuki-sensei. Right.
Who else were you with?
Um... Well, yeah.
I was with Hazuki-sensei.
But she got so drunk that she passed out, so I took her to her camp dorm.
Really?
What's going on, Chisato?
You've been acting weird lately.
I mean, yesterday...
You don't need act that way. You know I won't leave you.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll be with you whenever you need me.
Yuuki...
But it's not that kind of love.
You understand that, right?
I don't.
I don't... understand.
Oojima-senpai!
Looks like we caught up to you.
Hey, wait!
Wait, Chisato!
I got to bathe in peace for once.
Hazuki-sensei?
Huh?
Oh, here comes the girl's bedroom intruder!
I-I was just mistaken for a pervert and almost caught, thanks to a certain someone!
Then Shinonome-san saved me—
Damn that Satsuki! She's crafty as hell.
There's just no helping you.
Sensei.
Hm?
Why do you hate Shinonome-san so much?
I wouldn't say that I hate her.
Then do you hate your family?
Why did you leave them without—
Did Satsuki ask you to find out?
U-Um, well...
I knew booze was the only thing I could trust.
I can't believe my little sister would make a cuckold of me.
That's not what's going on!
Give me a break from all the teasing already.
You wouldn't even listen to me when I sincerely confessed.
You never sincerely confessed anything to me.
Should I do it now, then?
I love you, Yuu-kun.
Now, what's your response?
Ah... Well, of course I love you, too, Sensei!
You're trying to avoid this again?
I'm talking about the romantic kind of love.
That wasn't a joke, but a serious declaration of love.
I was holding back since I'm an adult and should know better.
Plus, I thought you had Chisato.
But if you're going to date Satsuki, that's a different story.
No, it's not really...
Come on. Answer me already.
Huh? Well...
It's hard for me to respond to your feelings so suddenly,
so could you give me some time to get back to you?
Hey, Satsuki?
It's me.
Wanna fight to see who gets Yuu-kun?
Beat me and I'll even tell you what you want to know as a bonus prize.
How about it?
Prize
Let's have a good game.
I'm surprised you agreed to this so easily.
I thought it'd be a good opportunity to learn what really happened.
But isn't he what you're really after?
Don't tease me!
You're so easy to read.
You think that's enough to throw me off focus?
You must still be drunk.
Yeah, I might even be drunk enough to kiss Yuu-kun again.
Oh, did that manage to rile you up?
You still have a lot to learn about love.
I'm just not loose like you.
Ever the pure maiden, huh?
I wonder which of them you take after.
Did you know? Her mother is the second one.
Huh?
Please don't talk about my mother.
She was my father's mistress,
but she became his wife after my mother passed away.
Stop.
Good for you, Satsuki.
You got to be born after they tied the knot.
Stop it.
If you were born before the marriage, you'd have been the mistress's child.
Stop it!
If that happened, you wouldn't have been able to flaunt being from a well-established family.
I bet you're glad that I left.
Sh-Shinonome-san...
Prize
Are you forfeiting the match?
I'll take him.
Ouch!
Sensei...
Silver to 4I!
Rook to 1H, promotion!
Pawn to 2F!
You're still going?
What about you? Don't run.
Wouldn't dream of it.
Knight to 3G, no promotion.
Just telling me your story won't cut it.
Rook to 8H.
When I win, you'll go back home and apologize to Mother!
You mean if you win.
Knight to 6G, check.
Still think you can win?
Silver to 6G.
Knight to 4I, promotion, check!
King to 6H!
Dragon to 4H, check!
What's wrong? Where'd all that spirit go?
Well, take your time.
What's going on here?
She's thinking hard about her next move.
Hey, got any beer?
Of course not!
Not very considerate, are you?
All right, then... Oh, yeah.
I'll tell you a story so you don't get bored.
A story?
It's from when Satsuki was little.
One time, I hurt my head, and it left a mark.
Right here. Can you see it?
It's pretty big.
It bled a lot, too.
It was bad enough for people to say that I might need a blood transfusion.
That bad?
It was just people talking out of their asses.
I got stitches and turned out fine.
But there was a reason why the adults got so frantic.
I have Rh negative blood.
They were worried that there might not be enough blood for a transfusion.
Then someone close came forward saying that they had the same blood type.
Can you guess who it was?
My mother is Rh negative.
That's right.
No way... That can't be true!
It is true. Your mother gave birth to me.
It was her.
No way...
Th-Then you and Shinonome-san are blood-related and share the same two parents?
It could just be a coincidence!
A child can be born Rh negative even if the parents are both Rh positive!
There's even more undeniable proof.
Long before I was born, my late mother
had her uterus removed due to an illness.
When I found out, our father resigned himself to telling me everything.
When my late mother became unable to bear children,
he was already having an
affair with Satsuki's mother.
Many of his relatives pressured him to
abandon his wife, who couldn't bear children,
so he could marry his mistress.
That's just...
But he couldn't just abandon his wife.
So he settled for having a baby with the second woman.
That's me.
I'm the mistress's child.
To fool the relatives, he took me in to raise as his legitimate child.
It must've been tough for his first wife.
She may have even hated me deep down.
But I can only remember her showering me with love.
She must have really loved me.
With her body as weak as it was,
she eventually succumbed to her illness.
Before I could even mourn, the second wife came in,
and Satsuki was born not too long after.
Since I got myself a cute sister, I chose to just get along with the family.
But I couldn't keep that up after learning the truth.
I found out by accident when a drunk relative let it slip.
It was more than just shocking.
I didn't know how to face my own family anymore.
Half panicking, I struggled to figure out what to do,
and my confusion turned into rage.
I couldn't forgive anyone in the family.
So I left.
I mean, if I just let it go...
If I let it all go and accept her as my biological mother...
What does that make my late mother?
We would have an authentic, blood-related family.
It'd be as though my late mother never existed in the first place.
But that's just wrong! I couldn't bear it!
What would her life have amounted to then?
She didn't even do anything wrong!
If I accepted the truth about our family,
it would... it would really be like she never mattered.
That's why I'll never forgive that family.
I've made up my mind.
I only have one mother. The one who passed away.
That's the way it has been and always will be.
I'm sorry! Onee-chan, I'm so sorry!
I had no idea.
You've been through so much, and I...
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I'm sorry.
No one's blaming you, Satsuki.
You really had nothing to do with it.
But... But...
Satsuki.
Onee-chan!
I'm so sorry.
He secretly met with Shinonome late at night?
Oojima is quite the troublemaker.
If Shinonome were to use this against him...
No, if she were after something like that, she'd use the pervert incident.
It'd be troublesome if others found out about this.
That goes double for the enemies closest to us.
The Public Safety Commissioner will return next week when his suspension ends.
Prepare to hand the tasks over to him and keep an eye on the Katahira Faction.
Yes, sir!
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"
Next Episode Preview
You usually get cravings for sweets when you're thinking hard.
The brain runs on glucose, so they say that you may even perform better when you eat sweets.
But they also say that eating too many monosaccharides
can lead to a rapid rise in blood sugar levels,
which causes excessive secretion of insulin, making you sleepy.
They say that's because
monosaccharides are absorbed quickly,
so the insulin secreted can decrease blood sugar levels too much
and make you sleepy due to hypoglycemia.
Next time, Episode 9: "Accident!"
Regardless, I still want sweets.