Starting today, the club room is our campaign headquarters,
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
and I will be acting as campaign president.
We're finally getting things in order.
Non-chan is very excited!
We have to make flags for our speeches.
Let's make posters first.
I'd be more than happy to be the announcer.
I can't help out directly since I'm a teacher,
but I can at least lend you some advice.
Vote... for...
Guys!
My candidacy form has been filed!
Well, then let's get into campaign mode!
Right!
Well? What should I do next?
Um... What should he do next?
You're smiling right there, I could even reach out with my hand,
But even if you're so close I could touch you
I'll just pull it back and hold it in because I don't need to
And pretend that I don't know about my feelings about to explode
Even when the sky is cloudy and crying
Above them the skies are clear and bright, wherever you go
When the signal changes,
Raise your hands in the air and give a shout
Take me with you to the future,
The one that you thought you'd never go because you were so scared
I found that you and something in you can shine so brightly,
So look straight ahead of you right now
I'll take the first step there with you
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
Strategy!
As part of Takafuji Academy's presidential election process,
Second Debate
Final Election
Strategy!
Second Debate
Final Election
Strategy!
Second Debate
Final Election
Strategy!
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
the school will hold a primary prior to the actual election.
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Second Debate
Final Election
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
First Debate
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
Flow of the Presidential Election
Primary Election
10% or more votes to pass
If we don't pass the primaries, we can't run.
Primaries, huh?
That's where all of the bubbly candidates pop.
Bubbly candidates?
They're the weak candidates.
They have neither popularity nor budget, and their policies are inadequate.
Even if they ran, they'd pop like bubbles.
That sounds just like Ooshima!
That's why we're here thinking of ways to prevent that.
You need at least 10 percent of the vote to pass the primaries.
That's 10 percent of 6,000 students,
so we need 600 votes.
How are we supposed to get 600 votes?
By...
making a good manifesto, I guess.
We need something that can easily attract anyone.
In that case, how about increasing the club budgets?
Let's double the Food Research Club's budget.
Non-chan thinks a snack allowance would make everyone happy!
An alcohol allowance would be nice.
Cash allowances might lead to corruption,
so how about making snacks free?
Free Yaoi Sticks.
All of those are just distributing favors.
I'd never win with a manifesto like that.
The problem is that we don't have any know-how on campaigning.
It'd be really helpful if we had someone with experience.
We don't know anyone like that.
Excuse me.
Wow! Yakkun, long time no see!
Isn't he...
...President Mouri?
It's been a while, Non-chan.
You've grown.
Of course. Non-chan is a senior.
It's only natural that I'd grow.
I've grown to exude the charms of a woman.
Great. If that's the case, your future should be very interesting.
Obviously!
Are you friends with the president, too, Non-chan-senpai?
Yes. Yakkun was in my class during our freshman year.
Wait. You're friends with the president, too, Yuuki?
Yeah... I guess.
You're running in the election, yes?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Thanks to you, I guess.
Actually, my visit today is regarding that.
Huh?
Let me be frank.
Would you allow us, the Public Safety Commission, to assist Oojima-kun in his campaign?
What?
A-Are you serious?
I am.
But why me?
If you're after his body, you're too late.
Yuuki-senpai's body,
from the top of his head to the tips of his toes, already belongs to me.
Would you be willing to share him with me?
Yume!
Right.
They wouldn't offer to help unless there were something in it for them.
That's correct.
Our offer to help stems from a selfish reason.
A selfish reason?
Yes.
The Public Safety Commission
does not wish to relinquish the position to either Finance or General Affairs.
Why don't you wish to relinquish the position?
Even if you guys can't run this year, you should be able to try again next year.
An election is typically won by the party in power.
Once the regime is handed over, it is difficult to get it back.
So, if an independent like Yuuki is elected president,
everyone will be on the same level for next year.
Precisely.
But why choose me?
There are plenty of other candidates.
That's because you have the
potential to pass the primary election.
I do?
Yes.
The other day, Shinonome's manifesto was disclosed,
and according to our research, her
approval rating dropped by 10 percent.
10 percent?
How did that happen?
There are minor reasons, like putting too much emphasis on financial-aid policy reform,
but mainly, there are many who oppose the club reforms.
The students in clubs that would receive budget cuts are against her now.
Basically, if we show we're against the club reforms,
we can get their support.
On that point, the Food Research Club, which would be disbanded instead of just receiving cuts,
would appear as a reactionary
candidate and quickly gain support.
But if the General Affairs Commission proposed the same policy before us,
they'd be the ones getting those votes.
The General Affairs Commission would begin their true campaign after the primaries.
They would also release their manifesto to attack Shinonome's weaker stands, too.
And then? How would the votes look?
With the votes from the clubs set for reform and our votes, around 400.
We'd need to make up the rest.
400?
Then it's another 200 votes...
...which is 25 votes from each of us?
We should be able to work something out if we ask our friends.
Non-chan actually knows a lot of people.
Non-chan can get us lots of votes.
And I'm sure some other people will put votes in for us on the day of the election...
...so this might be easy after all.
I don't mind that you're enjoying yourselves,
but I hope you understand that garnering the aforementioned 400 votes is possible
only if you cooperate with us.
We understand.
We know that we can't do this on our own.
But what do you mean by "cooperate"?
The Public Safety Commission is on probation, right?
That being the case, we can't
lend you any of our members.
However, we can lend you the know-how regarding the election that we've acquired.
The know-how?
Yes.
The know-how of someone who has previously won.
Isn't that fascinating?
We should definitely ask for it.
What are you saying? We don't have to ask, right?
Exactly. We are the ones who are asking.
See? We have the high ground here.
We don't need to make any rash promises.
Regardless, you shouldn't be so haughty to someone offering us help.
Don't be ignorant, Yuuki.
The president isn't doing this out of the kindness of his heart.
It's possible that he plans on making a puppet government out of you.
That's quite the accusation.
Nevertheless, I understand that it's
difficult for you to trust me so suddenly.
I would like to propose a limited contract until the primary election ends.
And if you begin to trust us somewhere down the line, we'll extend the contract.
Deal!
Thank you very much.
We won't let you down.
Make sure Yuuki wins.
You can count on me.
Oojima-kun.
Y-Yes?!
I look forward to working with you.
Same here. I look forward to it.
Yumeshima-kun, let's do our best together.
Yes, let's... come together.
Sarue-san, I look forward to working with you.
Yes.
Monzennaka-san, I look forward to working with you.
Sure.
Non-chan, let's win this thing.
Let's go win!
Kiba-san.
Yes.
I look forward to working together.
Yes, me too.
This is what you call a life-saver.
Don't relax just yet.
Morishita-san... right?
Let's work together.
A mere 400 votes
is much less than what the Public Safety Commission is capable of.
I don't know what you're up to,
but don't involve my kids in your skirmishes.
I would never.
Can I believe you?
Of course.
They're all very good kids.
Take care of them.
I will do my best.
|
Manifesto
For starters, we'll save the manifesto for later.
We're not handling that first?
No one would look at the
manifesto of a bubbly candidate.
How are we going to do this without a manifesto?
It is not necessary for you to place first in the primaries.
You only need to gather the 600 votes required to pass.
To do that, you should focus on the most salient policy in your campaign.
"Protecting the clubs," right?
Precisely.
So first, Oojima-kun, please visit the clubs faced with budget cuts and ask for their support.
Okay. I'll get right to it.
One moment, please.
In your visit, please bring a female club member.
A female club member?
Yes.
There are many clubs with more males than females,
so it'd help to have a female student there to smile and make the request.
That's a good idea.
He's a pro. A campaigning pro.
So who wants to come with me?
There must be at least a hundred of those clubs, right?
And I'd have to be stuck with Ooshima the entire time.
You guys...
No one else wants to,
and I am campaign president.
I'll do the job if no one else wants to.
There you have it.
With that out of the way, can someone else handle obtaining signatures?
Signatures... What for?
People that take the time to sign are less likely to betray us.
They would, to some degree, feel bad about lying.
Even if it's impossible to determine, they're still likely to vote for us.
That job sounds just as tedious.
Yeah.
Hey, guys...
Do you actually feel like helping?!
By the way, this job is most effective when done by pretty girls.
I'm going to get signatures!
Me too!
Oojima
Yuuki
Election
Headquarters
They're gone.
A pro...
He's pro at making people do as he wants.
I'm just getting started.
A-An election committee?
Yes. A committee that supports Yuuki from behind.
It'll consist of clubs targeted by Shinonome.
We'll be fighting against people that have the support of
the Finance Commission and the General Affairs Commission.
However, we don't have that
kind of support for ourselves.
Th-That could pose a problem.
That's why we need an election committee.
I want you two as the committee's president and vice president.
President and...
...vice president?
Please? You guys are our only hope.
But this basically means that I can't just vote, right?
That's right.
We need you to go to each club and set up the election committee.
Isn't that your job?
We want it to form as a volunteer organization.
It shouldn't appear as though the committee were forcibly formed.
I see.
Still, this is a lot to be responsible for.
We're begging you, Ariake, Garage.
Please! The results of this election would depend on this committee.
I got it! I have a great idea!
This and this is...
That is a very good idea.
Right?
Chisato, we'll help under one condition.
Come here for a sec.
Please give us your signature.
Please!
Let's see...
Make this part more concise and easier to read.
How does this look to you?
You've got balls to actually come here alone.
I'll show you who the real boss—
I don't have time to deal with your foolishness.
Come on!
At least say, "I have no interest in being a boss, but I will never forgive—"
What do you want?
Can I get my bonus in advance, Ms. Finance Commissioner?
I'm not responsible for that. Talk to General Affairs.
Don't be so cold.
Even if we have different mothers,
I'm still your beloved sister, aren't I?
If you don't have anything else to say, I'm leaving.
Are you disbanding the Food Research Club to annoy me?
Of course not. I wouldn't let my private life influence my public duty.
It's a decision I came to after a thorough examination.
All right, that's a relief.
If it turned out those kids of mine were in trouble because of me, I don't know what I'd do.
Will that be all? I have a meeting with the election committee.
Oh, how you've grown.
That's my sister.
Your mother must be so proud.
It's not enough.
I must surpass you.
I must become the student council president that you couldn't!
Oh, really? If you hate me that much,
why not just fire me?
At this school, teachers are pretty much hired by the students.
It'd be a simple task for the
Finance Commissioner, wouldn't it?
Didn't you hear me? I won't let my
private life influence my public duty.
So, you wouldn't mind firing me privately?
Well, do what you want.
Good luck with the election.
I'm a teacher, so I'll support you without letting my private life influence me, too.
Man, I'm exhausted.
I never thought that talking to strangers could take so much out of you.
You lazy bum.
Then, just for you...
Huh?
What is this?!
We're taking a break, right? Get me some coffee.
You're making me go buy it?
I gave you the money, didn't I?
You're my property, so no complaining.
Jeez... Treat me preciously if I'm your property.
You want the usual?
Yep.
You are precious.
Hm. I wonder what I should get.
You're running for president, aren't you?
Oh, Shinonome-san.
We're rivals now, Powjima-kun.
What exactly is "Powjima"?
I thought your name started with "P,"
but I must have been slightly mistaken.
It doesn't start with "P," and you're more than just "slightly" mistaken.
Let's have a fair election.
Right. I don't plan on losing, though.
You're very confident.
Until next time.
What are you grinning so hard for?
Crap.
So this is what was keeping you! What are you doing, playing nice with the enemy?
No, it's not what it looks like!
You didn't tell me you were friends with the Finance Commissioner!
Well, there was this thing with her bike...
Huh? What about it? You haven't told me anything!
Oh, right. Chisato! Canned coffee!
I want to eat nikujaga~~!
I'll wait for you~~~
Nikujaga...
Don't try to trick me! Explain yourself!
What's going on between you two? Tell me! Tell me!
Onions, carrots, shirataki, kidney beans, garlic...
There should be some pepper left.
Oh, I forgot to buy some beef.
Huh? Is that Morishita-san?
Oojima-kun?
Ayumu-san.
Shirataki... Are you making curry tonight?
You don't need shirataki for curry.
I thought you were substituting it for meat.
I wouldn't do that.
I got it! It's stew!
With shirataki instead of meat!
I said I wouldn't do that!
Thanks for coming.
Time to eat.
It's so good! I haven't tasted your cooking in two weeks.
Food prepared by other people sure is delicious.
That's something only a person who regularly cooks should say.
Don't be so petty.
Where are you? Are you out?
Chisato
Chisato?
Yeah.
Did she say, "Hey, Yuuki! Where'd you run off to?!"
Out with my mom for dinner
Sending...
Message Sent
Something like that.
It must be hard having a such a jealous girlfriend.
She's not my girlfriend.
Are you really not dating her?
I'm really not.
Tell your mom that I said hi.
Then how about dating me?
Please don't make jokes like that.
You're a man, and I'm a woman. I don't think it's impossible.
It's impossible as long as you keep up that look
that gives away how much fun you're having teasing me.
Huh? Was I making that kind of face?
Well, you do something like that again, I'd stop coming over.
Yeah, yeah.
But I still don't get why I did something like that.
It's because you were drunk.
I wasn't drunk!
If I were, I wouldn't remember.
I still remember how Yuu-kun's lips feel.
S-Stop that!
Well, I still want Yuu-kun to make me dinner,
so I'll be careful to not get on your bad side.
I'd be very grateful for that.
Thanks for the dinner.
The nikujaga was very delicious.
You're welcome.
Well, see you later, Yuu-kun.
Good night.
kyoushitsu no madobe de nagameru
In the classroom, looking out the window,
yasashii yuugure no sora
Watching the sky fade softly into twilight,
furimukeba kimi ga egao de
I turn around, and there you are again
kocchi wo miteta
Looking at me, you smile
issho ni kaerou itsumo no
"Let's go home," you always say,
toomawari wo shinagara
Going all the places we go every day
mada sukoshi todokanai
Your fingers are just a step away
yubisaki ga tada setsunakute
But deep inside me, it hurts not holding your hand
ano hi kimi to meguriaeta kara
In my heart, I found all these hopes and dreams
takusan no yume wo mitsuketan da
Because on that day we happened to meet
nakitai toki demo
Even when I wanted to cry,
itsumo soba ni ite kurete
You always stayed right there by my side
doumo arigatou
I want to thank you so much
no-to ni kaita himitsu no pe-ji wa
What I wrote on that page I hid from you
zutto iezu ni ita kotoba
Were the words that I just couldn't say
ima kaze no naka zutto sasayaku yo nee
Now they float forever as whispers on the wind
kiite kimi ga daisuki da yo
Listen close, it says, "I love you so much"
Next Episode Preview
You know how there are both sweet, sugary snacks
and salty snacks like crackers, right?
You can split them into categories like that, yeah.
But sometimes there are snacks that have both sugar and salt,
like the salty crackers with sugar on top or candies with salt on them.
Those are delicious because of how the sweetness and saltiness complement each other.
Oojima-senpai, you think so too?
Next time, Episode 4: Funding.
I also like cookies baked with margarine.